Previously on Travelers.
We got a mission
to save people who were
gonna die from the flu.
The Director's antiviral didn't work.
That's impossible.
We're all infected, aren't we?
I want to go over the antiviral
data one more time.
Maybe we made a mistake.
I remember this,
but I don't remember writing it down.
How do you not remember?
What did you make me do?
The Director would never
order that mission.
Who said the mission
came from the Director?
So Forbes,
all those people with the FBI...
...Are all Faction?
You're murdering over two billion people.
The mission comes first.
Where's the quantum frame?
He asked you a question.
Pfft.
Do it. It's what I want anyway.
You've been doing what we want
for months,
why stop now?
How many members of the Faction are here?
It could be anybody we meet.
And there could be thousands
more in the quantum frame.
That's why the Director
wanted us to destroy it.
The Director ordered
you to build the thing.
I mean, how can you people
not see the irony of that?
You just follow it blindly,
no matter what.
That's the difference between us.
No. The Faction abducts innocent people
and overwrites them.
That's the difference between us.
What you do is murder.
What you do is opportunism,
like taking hosts just before they die
is so ethical?
Yeah. That's exactly what it is.
Hey, guess what?
Everybody is going to die.
Some sooner than others.
When we're from,
everybody in the 21st is long gone,
and for what they did to this planet,
good riddance.
Here's what's gonna happen, Jenny.
We're going to stop this pandemic,
and then we are gonna hunt down
every member of the Faction in the 21st.
The Director's shut down in the future,
and most of your team will be dead
in less than two weeks,
so good luck.
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
If you're done questioning her,
I'd like to take a few tissue samples,
run some tests.
Please. Whatever you need to do.
We should send out
an S.O.S. on the deep web
and let other Travelers
know what's going on.
They'll be monitoring our backchannels.
If the Faction's overwritten
every single federal agent
that was in that room
with the quantum frame,
I don't have those assets to use either.
Okay, this is not that complicated.
I'm saying
the Director can fix this.
We need to fix the Director.
The Director exists in the future.
And its reactor is already shut down.
Those are big problems, Grace.
The plan's already in place.
When it became apparent
that the grand plan
would take longer than
our initial projections,
the Director sent a team
to refine uranium as fuel
to extend its operational life.
A few kilos would be enough.
All we have to do
is take the fuel to the location
where the Director
will eventually be built,
and it'll be there when the time comes.
Without the Faction knowing.
How the hell are we gonna do that?
Whoa! They outsmarted us!
Whoop-dee-doo! Get over it!
They can't outsmart the Director.
Even if we can just get it
back online for a few seconds,
that's all the time
it'll need to take back control.
And you know where this uranium is?
Pull up a map.
Oh!
It's hot in there.
Ever think you'd hear yourself
complain about the heat?
No.
Radiation, maybe.
You really want to lose another game?
Who the hell is that?
Who are you?
I'm 4112.
What're you doing here?
I just received orders
to provide backup at this location.
You can lower your gun.
Backup for what?
Damn. I was kind of
hoping you could tell me.
I'm sorry, guys,
squeaky little kid took me by surprise
when she first started talking.
I missed the whole first part.
Yeah, messengers are weird.
Yeah, she said something
about uranium, maybe?
Yeah, you heard right.
We're refining it.
Fuel for the Director.
So how the hell
do you guys get it to the future?
We don't.
Yeah, we make it here in the 21st,
then we put it away for the Director
to find it in a few hundred years.
Yeah, we're right on schedule,
so I don't know what we need backup for.
Yeah?
How much have you produced?
2.4 kilos.
Why... Why did you do that?
Show me where.
Thank you.
We're clear.
It's in there.
Take it all.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Shh...
It's okay.
Hello?
Hey, Sarge.
Yeah, no, I'm sorry, my son's sick,
and I had to, uh...
Yeah, no, no, I understand.
Yeah, I'll come down as soon
as his mom gets home.
Okay. Thanks, Sarge.
Yeah. That's it.
...yet to be named virus.
It has infected thousands
of people around the world,
with the highest infection rates
among the most vulnerable:
pregnant women, children, the elderly,
and those with lowered immune systems.
Many are turning to emergency rooms
in hopes of treatment,
but infection rates are on the rise,
with nearly every hospital bed
in the city now occupied.
The mayor is expected
to make a statement shortly,
however, the epidemic
has city and state authorities
suggesting that everyone
stay in their homes.
What did he do to me?
We just took some blood
and tissue samples.
You're still intact.
You understand, don't you?
No.
You used me.
Look, come on.
I was on a mission, just like you.
We want the same thing.
We just go about it a different way.
We forget about...
the protocols and the Director,
and all those limitations,
and we just do what needs to be done,
what's right.
Like Calloway and Aleksander.
That's very different
than murdering almost
a third of the population.
To save everyone else.
Not a bargain I can make.
Well, it's done.
There's no going back now.
We're not giving up just yet.
You should.
Your people won't be able to stop this,
and there's nothing an historian can do.
Just think about
the time you've got left.
Let's get out of here.
When I found you,
you had swallowed a bottle of pills.
Why?
Guilt?
I feel no guilt at all.
This is for the greater good,
and I can't believe you don't see that!
Then why the pills?
Because I was trying to end it
before the virus ran its course.
You feel sick now.
It's only gonna get worse.
This virus is designed
to keep the infected alive
as long as possible...
to help the spread,
make the authorities think
that it's not as serious as it really is.
So when people start to really die,
it's too late.
And the last days of it
are not something I want to go through.
Well, now you're gonna suffer...
Along with everyone else...
for every last minute.
They're keeping a pretty low profile.
I think that's the idea.
Okay.
Watch our six and listen in on com.
Copy that.
Who is it?
3468, on a Protocol Alpha mission.
3224. What's going on?
We need to pull up the delivery.
It's urgent.
Is this a joke?
No.
The reactor won't need
more fuel for hundreds of years.
It's the here and now
we're worried about.
This "flu" that's going around
is about to become a pandemic.
And what's that got to do with us?
Let's talk inside, shall we?
All we have is in the lab down the hall.
But I still don't see
what refined uranium
has to do with a pandemic.
Boss, this guy picked
the wrong random Traveler number.
3224 died six months ago.
These guys are all Faction.
Well, I wish I could
tell you the whole plan,
but, you know... protocol two.
No.
I don't know.
I'm gonna need more.
Like what?
Something in writing?
The Director isn't good enough for you?
You could be pretending
to be somebody else.
I am pretending to be somebody else.
It's in the job description.
Are you new here?
No.
I just don't want to see uranium
fall into the wrong hands.
Well, neither do we.
Hands on your head.
Door.
Show him where it is.
Long gone. Have a look for yourself.
Trev?
Any of your team
showing any symptoms yet?
You look like you're in the early stages.
Where did you take it?
Even if I told you,
the others would know,
and they'd just move it to a safe place.
Some of them are on their way here now.
You're more than welcome to wait.
No sign of uranium in the lab.
Shit!
Feel better?
No.
I do.
Come on.
This been tested?
Soup's safe, Bob.
I promise.
How'd you know my name?
Why does no one ever
recognize me with this thing on?
It's me.
David?
You shouldn't be here.
Well, where else would I be?
All my friends are here.
Soup's delicious. I tested it myself.
It'll make you strong
and fight that bug that's going around.
I've got to get back to my team.
I've done about all I can
for Boyd at this point.
I wanted to give you these.
They're not programmed
to affect the viral load,
but if she starts to go
into organ failure,
they might buy you some time.
Thank you.
Aren't nanites by directive only?
Well, with the Director down,
I figure the discretion falls on me.
Boyd's a good medic. We could use her.
We'll do what we can.
Good luck.
I'd be willing to trade information
in exchange for those nanites.
I thought you wanted to die.
Not if the cure's right in front of me.
I'm not stupid.
You're the control. You get nothing.
- Well?
- There was no uranium.
Just the Faction...
waiting for us.
Why are you looking at me like that?
You're the one that sent us there.
Aw, that is so insulting.
Yes, I did!
Because we absolutely need it
and time is short.
You need to find out
where it is and go get it.
They're a step ahead of us, at least.
We need another option.
There aren't any other options!
We need to get the Director back online.
The Faction has been
planning this for a long time.
So we gotta think outside the box.
There's a military base
just north of here.
N.S. Wallace.
You're thinking nuclear weapons?
That's nowhere near the box, Philip.
But that's ideal,
from a fuel perspective.
A few hundred years is nothing
compared to the half-life of plutonium.
It would be difficult.
Closer to impossible!
And if we've thought about it,
then Faction probably has too.
Well...
doesn't sound like
we have much of a choice.
I got you some groceries
so you don't have to go out
for the next few days.
The store was a madhouse.
I heard there's looting going on.
Yeah, a few assholes.
How're you feeling?
I'm okay.
Hot. Headache.
Temperature's up near 100.
Let's cool you down.
The news said this was an epidemic.
Is it really that bad?
Hopefully that's
a bit of an overreaction.
Doctor, what can you
tell me about the virus?
What is it?
We're not sure yet.
They're working on it.
But you...
are sick, and you need to rest.
So much so,
that while many of the symptoms
match the common flu...
What do you know?
How sick am I?
Grant?
I don't know.
Okay, what do we do?
The safest place for you is right here.
"Safest"? Okay,
now you're starting to scare me.
Maybe we should go to the hospital.
Not where you want to be right now.
Look.
The next couple days,
it's gonna be hard for me to get home.
Couple of days?
I will try to...
What about you? You're gonna be exposed.
I've got to support
the people who are trying to solve this.
And you've got to take
your meds and rest,
and give your body...
and that baby
the fuel that they need.
Okay? That means fresh fruit,
not salted meat.
Do you have to go so soon?
The sooner I go,
the sooner I come back.
I love you.
So?
Took all night, but they're done.
Good work.
How's everybody holding up?
We can nap in the car.
When I left, you were afraid
the device wouldn't have enough range.
Yeah, we fixed that.
How does it know when to activate?
Well, the Director is programmed
to broadcast an emergency signal
if it's ever powered down.
Which should trigger the device
and activate it.
"Should"?
Do you want me to go over
a list of things
that could go wrong with this plan?
No, thank you.
It'll work, boss.
We're good to go.
All right, then let's gear up.
Road trip!
How is she?
Uh...
Her viral load's holding steady,
but she's not getting any better.
The nanites will help, right?
Could help.
Could make things worse.
The Faction planned this well.
It's hard to know what contingencies
they've thought of.
Use Grace as you see fit,
but keep your eye on her.
And... take care.
You too.
Hey, Bob?
I brought you some soup.
Bob?
Bob!
Oh no!
Hey, Carly, it's me.
I'm getting worried about you.
About Jeffrey...
Listen, I'm sick as shit. Please...
Call me, let me know where you are,
that you're okay.
Your son says "hi" too.
You're a hypocrite.
You're all high and mighty
about sacrificing lives
to save the future,
and then treat me like a lab rat.
You did this to yourself.
This is a waste of resources.
I should be programming the nanites.
- Not yet.
- Why not?
Because I want to see
if the anti-serum will work first.
I'm close.
Boyd will be dead before you're done!
Well, she's my patient.
We both know,
in the time we come from,
medical nanites more or less replace you.
Okay, if you want to be helpful,
why don't you use your computer
and hack into the CDC
and find out what kind
of progress they've made.
The who?
Hack into them too, if you'd like.
Like either the Center
for Disease Control
or the World Health Organization
is gonna know how to deal
with a virus designed in the future?
Let's contact the 15th century
and hire an exorcist!
Would you just please stop talking?
You little power-tripper.
I am trying to save your life!
Well, you're not doing a very good job.
I feel awful.
Where are you going?
To the bathroom.
Hi. We're, uh...
This is a designated exit, sir.
Oh.
Sorry. Uh...
W...
What's he doing?
Just his job.
Everybody relax.
All these guys could be Faction.
If it goes down,
I'll take the booth guard.
Easy! We're not gonna get our warhead
if we start shooting people.
We're trapped in here,
and there's cameras everywhere.
Everybody, calm the hell down.
Base is under quarantine, sir.
I'm aware of that.
I'm Special Agent
Grant MacLaren from the FBI.
I've got a meeting with Captain Garcia
on urgent business.
All appointments have been canceled...
Vice Admiral Donahue
arranged the meeting,
so I assure you, the meeting
has not been canceled.
Check again.
Carly.
I see it here now, sir.
Great. And the gate?
Just waiting
for your passes to print, sir.
Building four.
On your right.
Appreciate it.
What?
You all right?
No, I'm dying,
but I still need to go
to the bathroom periodically.
Well, you've been in there for a while.
I was just concerned.
I'm fine!
Did you see where she put the nanites?
In there.
What're you doing?
Shh.
Shh-shh-shh-shh.
Captain Garcia?
Special Agent MacLaven from the FBI.
It's "MacLaren."
Your pass says "MacLaven".
Agent MacLaren
knows his name, Ms. Jackson.
Should I issue a new pass?
He won't be here that long. You can go.
That doesn't sound promising.
It is what it is.
I'm sure the Admiral relayed
the urgency of our request.
And your pass says MacLaven.
People make mistakes.
Our request isn't one of them.
How does that particular warhead
possibly help prevent a pandemic?
I'm not authorized to explain.
Shame. I'd pay good money to hear it.
While you're deciding
whether to help us or not,
a deadly virus is spreading worldwide.
You're being a little
melodramatic, aren't you?
The flu kills people every year.
It's far worse than what's been reported.
There are millions of
people infected already,
even if they haven't
presented symptoms yet.
And it's spreading exponentially.
The Admiral's email said
you'd be coming in with CDC personnel.
Is that supposed to be you?
They're specialists.
Uh-huh.
This is making less and less sense
the more I hear.
If you'd like to call
the Admiral, I'm sure...
Not necessary.
My orders were clear.
The warhead is being separated
from the torpedo as we speak,
for what good that could possibly do.
It's being loaded
directly into your vehicle.
I just don't like
ordnance leaving my base
without an explanation.
Trust me when I say
you're helping to save millions of lives.
I hope I'm one of them.
I feel like shit,
and so do half the people on my base.
I will personally make sure
that the people on this base
are among the first
to receive the antidote
once it's ready.
David.
You should go home.
Yeah, I'm just gonna sit for a bit.
You've done your fair share.
Government's getting serious.
There's looting going on.
Looting?
I saw a movie a few months back
where something like this happened.
It was very believable.
But I never bought the looting.
"Hey everyone's getting sick,
so let's...
let's break that window
and steal that TV."
I-I don't get that.
Me neither.
I mean, you get a pretty decent TV
for next to nothing nowadays,
compared to what I got mine for? God.
David.
The expensive part is the cable.
David...
Go home.
Yeah.
No, I-I'm waiting for Marcy to come by.
Maybe I should go home.
It's a good idea.
I should've swung that friggin' ax.
Forbes would've shot you.
30% of the human population...
Including all of you.
Boss, you can't blame yourself
for not being able
to foresee the unthinkable.
That's why they call it "unthinkable".
Can't think it.
Still, I know how you feel.
I'm the one that provided
the Faction with the virus.
You were drugged.
Again.
Stop. It's done.
You know, I've been wondering about that.
Maybe the Director can undo this.
How?
The future can only send
a consciousness back
as far as
the most recent Traveler, right?
And Travelers are arriving all the time,
all over the world,
as part of the grand plan...
but the last one
had to have been months ago...
before the Director went down,
before all this happened.
The Faction might not be able
to send consciousness back
or establish a T.E.L.L.,
but messengers count.
It's still a transfer
of information from the future.
He's right.
Messengers cause
the same ripples in space-time
as Travelers.
And we know
the Faction has sent messengers recently.
They thought of everything.
Well, guys, on the bright side...
We're almost home.
Hard to believe
where we're walking right now
is under a kilometer of ice
in a few hundred years.
The domes get built right over there.
We've only ever seen the shelters
from the inside.
What's wrong?
Aw, shit. Marcy!
What happened?
She shouldn't be
having respiratory issues
at this stage.
You didn't trust me. I had no choice.
What'd you do?
I instructed
the nanites to pull the virus
into red blood cells,
where it can't survive.
She should be getting better.
The Faction predicted
that countermeasure.
The virus blocks red blood cells' ability
to carry oxygen.
She's suffocating.
Turn them off!
Deactivating the nanites
will be like flushing them
down the drain!
Turn them off or she's gonna die.
Either way, they're useless now.
There, she's better.
No, she's not better!
She's right back to where she started.
They've been ahead of us this whole time.
Did you not think the Faction
was gonna factor in nanites?
This is all because you didn't trust me!
Why should I?
You're alive because of me.
And perfectly healthy.
Am I?
When you reset me,
you left out some things.
What'd you leave out, Grace?
This is what you want to talk about
when we're all dying?
I'm not dying! You are.
Oh, god...
Oh...
You've reached
Special Agent Grant MacLaren...
Want to take a break?
No, I'm good.
Okay. Come on.
Almost there.
Guns on the ground!
Secure the warhead.
Where are you taking it?
Somewhere it can't power the Director.
Oh, come on.
Of course we knew
you'd try something like this
when you didn't get the uranium.
Don't beat yourself up!
You're a good team, and we need numbers.
We should be working together.
I don't think so.
The Director had its chance.
Didn't change a goddamn thing
in the future!
Other than create the Faction.
The future we came from,
you all died in
the collapse of shelter 41.
Why can't I wrap my head
around that shit?
Why am I not surprised?
All right.
Thanks for the plutonium.
We'll make sure to put it to good use.
Let's go!
Plutonium?
What... You think we brought
a nuclear warhead in here?
I thought you said
that they were watching
all of our communications.
There was a typo
in my Admiral Donahue email that...
it may have thrown them off.
When I wrote "Mark 45
warhead" instead of, uh...
What was it? Mark 46?
- Oh! Oh, right.
- The 45 was nuclear.
That makes total sense.
Except the Mark 45 torpedo
was decommissioned in 1976.
On a Wednesday.
Never in a million years
could we get a nuclear warhead
from a U.S. naval station.
Your friends just walked away
with a conventional Mark 46
antisubmarine warhead.
Totally different.
Carly, I think they're
far enough away now.
Device is in place and activated.
Turn around.
Come on, Mac.
I'm unarmed.
You really think you can
kill me in cold blood?
I really do.
_
Aah!
I'm Traveler 4991.
It worked.
The Director's
back up and running.
The cure has been sent to the 21st.
The encrypted beacon
on the device activated
Almost the moment power
to the Director was cut off.
It took some time
for us to find and recover it,
but we got to it without them knowing...
Even when we broke through,
the energy source was only capable
of powering the Director
for three seconds.
Enough time for the Director
to reroute the power to itself
through the network,
cut off the Faction's
access to the reactor,
design the cure...
to win the war.
How many Faction are still here?
It's impossible to know
how many were sent
into the quantum frame.
The Director won't have
a T.E.L.L. for all of them.
Kat?
Grant.
I have been so worried.
I've been trying to call you.
I know, I'm sorry, but all the work
we've been doing, it's paid off.
You're gonna be okay.
I'm so sick.
.Don't say that if it's not real
No, I promise, we've had a breakthrough.
Watch the news.
I-I'll be... I'll be back with you
as fast as I can.
I'm worried about the baby.
I'll be back tomorrow at the latest.
Maybe sooner.
He didn't answer.
We did it.
That means we should be
able to wake you up soon.
One, she can't hear you.
Two, I can't believe
you're giving her the cure first.
I'm standing right here!
Boyd is far more sick.
Am I at least next?
No. The newly arrived Traveler
in her very sick host body, then you.
Oh, just admit you hate me.
Kat?
Sweetheart, hey. Hey, wake up.
Ohh... you're home?
And I've got something for you.
Come on.
What is it?
No, I can't take any medicine,
in case it affects the baby.
I got this directly from the CDC.
I made sure to ask.
It's perfectly safe.
It works really fast.
I'm going to let you sleep.
No. Can you just lie with me
for a bit?
Just for a minute.
I would like nothing more.
Jeff?
Jeffrey? Jeffrey!
Carly?
I know you were trying to call.
I had to get this first.
It's the treatment for the virus.
What? Where did you get it?
It doesn't matter.
It'll cure you both.
I was so scared.
I didn't know what to do.
You didn't come home.
I didn't know what to do but hold him.
Ohh...
Give him to me. I know.
I'm supposed to go to work
soon as you got home, but...
Okay. It's okay.
Just rest a while first, okay?
I know. I know, I know.
Yeah, I think I will.
I know.
The cure was developed by scientists
at the Center for Disease Control,
and is now being mass produced
and sent to health officials
all around the world.
It's being estimated that...
Marce!
...will be all but eradicated.
Did you hear that they cured this thing?
...death rate is expected
to drop significantly...
Ah, you're probably the one
that came up with it.
Not this time.
Did you stay inside?
No.
No, I was helping out
at one of the shelters.
David... you could have been exposed.
Yeah, I was.
The people I work with
are the first ones to be forgotten
when something like this happens.
You're not gonna give me that, are you?
Only if you're sick.
Speaking of sick...
This man I know just collapsed
while I was trying to get him soup.
Your pulse is good.
And while they were wheeling him out...
I felt like one of those minor characters
in a movie that does not end well.
And I thought to myself,
"Marcy's gonna give me shit
if I end up dying from this."
Because I can't help myself.
You mean from helping others?
Yeah, but isn't that what you do too?
Open your mouth.
Your way of doing things...
ith... ith more imprethive.
Right. Well, you're not sick.
Well, maybe you should
give me the shot anyway.
No symptoms.
If you were exposed,
it means you're immune,
so find your friend who collapsed,
and give this to him.
Okay?
Yeah.
What, you're leaving again?
I have other patients.
I just... I wanted to make sure
that you were okay.
Wow.
House call.
I'll be back later, if that's all right.
Don't wait up.
Yeah, I probably will.
I thought you were going home.
Just back to check on my patients.
How are you guys feeling?
Oh...
Much better, thank you.
Good.
You'll be happy to know that
the CDC has set up treatment centers
to disseminate the antiviral en masse.
And Jenny...
that is, Jenny 3.0...
is coordinating deliveries.
Marcy?
Oh, yeah.
She woke up a while ago.
Hey.
How're you feeling?
Mm. Like shit.
But I'll live.
I'll also live, thanks for asking.
I still haven't heard
from the other two members of my team,
but I'm hoping...
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com