Previously, on Travelers...
Tell me about me.
I'm just trying to find
the missing pieces.
Someone like you does not happen
to someone like me.
It could be the early signs
of a placental abruption.
- I need a favor.
- Yeah. Of course.
One that breaks protocol.
Give me one of her folic acid pills.
If we're going to swap out
a medication to prevent a miscarriage,
it'll need to look identical.
Traveler 3326, open memory chain 71985VX
and store the following sequence...
...biosynthesis of the glycoproteins...
3326...
access memory chain 71985VX...
Write it down.
That's all of it?
Philip?
Is that all of it?
Is it error-free?
Yes.
Is it good?
It's great. Can you move?
How did you get in?
Little girl named Chloe.
I said I would send it to you.
Yeah, well, something like this,
I have to see for myself.
Those stereoisomers are going
to be difficult to reproduce.
We're gonna have to do it in batches.
We're leaving.
Sure. Good work, Philip.
Ohh... Oh. God.
What did we do last night?
We were going to your place.
We did.
We did?
This is disturbing.
You hit the drops pretty hard.
Mm...
It's never felt like this before.
It'll pass.
We need to talk.
This has to end.
What?
This.
Us.
What?
I got a new mission.
What mission?
Sorry, Philip.
Lightning struck.
So "goodbye"?
We never see each other again?
I... I thought we had a connection.
Right.
I am your connection.
That's not what I meant.
That should last you a few months,
if you use 'em
the way you're supposed to.
Jenny.
Jenny!
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
Okay. It's almost over.
- Okay.
- It's 100.6.
It's high, but manageable.
I know, I know, I know, I know.
So, um...
alternate between these two...
acetaminophen and ibuprofen.
It should manage his fever
or whatever pain he might be in.
That's it?
That's it.
He should be fine in a few days.
You hear that, baby?
Auntie Marcy says
you're gonna be all right.
Ahh.
Stay for coffee?
Sure.
Okay.
So I'll put him down.
Philip.
You've been quiet lately.
Yeah, not much to say.
Well, some people
find talking about it to be therapeutic.
It has been two weeks.
You know that doesn't make
a difference for me, right?
I remember every detail
as if it just happened.
Okay, good chat. Ahem.
Who is it?
0115.
3326.
We were given orders to meet you.
You must be Graham.
Yeah. Come on in.
You boys hungry? I got soup on.
No, thank you.
Smells delicious.
You have a lovely home.
It's just temporary.
Driving up and down the state,
making hand-offs.
A long mission.
Well, roll out's been
longer than expected,
but I ain't complaining.
I got to see three eagles!
Hopefully you're done soon.
Yeah, well, your team's
one of the last on the list.
Excuse me.
Here you go.
What a lovely couple.
Thank you for coming
and checking him out.
I know I probably sounded crazy.
No, you don't sound crazy.
You had a natural maternal instinct.
I don't know about natural.
It's not like I'm really his mother.
Yeah, you are.
In every way that means something.
You guys have bonded.
Who would've thought that would
happen to somebody like me?
You mean a soldier?
Maybe you've changed.
Maybe we all have.
I mean, I have to believe
that we are more than
just our consciousness.
At least, the one we came here with.
Maybe that's...
Maybe that's the better part of us.
It's funny, you said something like that,
the night that you, uh...
Um...
What?
The night that I was reset?
What did I say?
Mac didn't tell you?
Well, he said that it was
the only way to save my life.
It was.
So?
I really didn't have any choice then.
You thought you did.
What... What does that mean?
I shouldn't have said anything.
No, Carly.
We just didn't know
it was gonna happen so fast.
Are you saying that
it happened against my will?
I don't know.
We thought you had more time.
So did you.
You said you wanted to go home,
because you wanted to think about it.
What could there possibly be
to think about?
I mean, I'd be dead.
I know, that's what I said at the time.
Now I'm beginning to understand.
This is exactly how
it happened last time.
Kat... you've been taking
your medication,
you've done everything by the book.
It's gonna be all right.
Ohh, stop saying that.
Hi. Apologies.
The, uh, the printer was down.
How are we?
Ahem.
Kathryn, the, uh, latest ultrasound,
it looks good.
It looks really good.
The dark spot's completely gone,
which means that it was probably nothing
or maybe just a mistake with the scan.
You and the baby are fine.
I'm sorry...
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Now, I want you to stick
to the calcium-rich foods,
the folic acid, and...
'Kay.
I'll see you in a few weeks.
Okay.
Thanks.
'Kay.
Thank you.
Hoo...
What was in the package?
An antiviral.
Historically,
this is the beginning
of a minor flu outbreak
that kills 70,000 people worldwide.
That does not sound "minor" to me.
Percentage-wise.
We're not wired to think
in "billions" of people.
Over a few months, an antigenic shift
allows the virus to mutate,
infecting more of the population.
Eventually, the C.D.C.
and W.H.O. get it under control.
Must be why they provided
a broad-spectrum antiviral.
This will inhibit
the development of each of its mutations.
Our mission is to save
three of the people
who, historically, don't make it.
Are there any more?
Jeffrey's already been
through the worst of it.
You need to protect yourself.
Couldn't we have gotten the pill version?
These are the host candidates?
Jordan Lam, Annie Kapoor,
and Brittney Palmer.
Personal trainer, a flight attendant,
a travel blogger.
Prime hosts that must
have spread the virus.
Well, let's make sure
that doesn't happen.
Are you gonna do the whole class?
Just waiting for the right opportunity.
Hi, Brittney.
I'll be doing your vaccinations today.
- Okay.
- You can take a seat.
That's it.
Have fun in Europe.
Thanks.
Mein Asthma.
_
Oh!
God. I was stung by a freakin' bee.
Me too. I think.
Are you allergic?
No. I'm not.
Good.
...As reports are increasing
of an unknown flu strain
that seems to be rapidly spreading
throughout the country.
The World Health Organization
describes the condition
as "atypical influenza"
and confirms five cases
have been reported...
- ...In the Pacific Northwest.
- It's starting.
Good. Nice work, everybody.
Protocol five until further notice.
We need to talk.
Hello, Miss Day.
When's the last time
you heard from the Director?
The school board director?
What are you talking about?
Hey, you're worried about them?
Please! There's literally
nothing going on
inside their tiny brains.
The girls are thinking about
their insipid friendships
and the boys are imagining them naked.
What do you want?
Have you heard
from the Director?
We've had missions.
Well, why haven't I heard anything?
I don't know. Maybe because
you jumped here without permission?
Or maybe because you don't have a team?
Maybe I can join your team.
I could be your computer expert.
Nah, we already have a computer expert.
I could be your vastly-more-capable
computer expert.
Doesn't work like that.
Well, it should! I'm getting bored!
You gonna finish that?
Mm! Fake chicken.
Mm!
Hey have you seen my, uh, my work jacket?
You were supposed to take Jeffrey today.
I know that, but I just got called in.
There's this big bug going around.
So?
So I'm going to work.
What'd I say?
It's what you didn't say.
"Hey, Carly.
"I know I was supposed
to take Jeffrey today,
but something came up. Can you help?"
Well, why do I have to say all of that?
You're his mother.
And you're his father.
We said we were
going to do this together.
Equal partners, remember?
Carly Shannon,
would you please help me out
by taking our gorgeous son
to the babysitter's house
so that I can go to work
as an underpaid,
underappreciated, beat cop
one more day?
Fine,
but you're doing pick-ups
for the rest of the week.
Absolutely.
And your jacket's
on the hook by the door.
Thank you.
See you, little man.
I'll see you, uh, see you tonight.
Hey. You want your ducky?
Yeah, you do.
Oh, ho, ho, ho.
Oh? Where are you taking him?
Hello?
3185. Has your team taken the antiviral?
- Yeah.
- 'Kay, let us in.
Oof!
Where's Marcy?
Hi. This David Mailer.
Please leave a message.
Hi, David. Um, it's me, Marcy.
Just wondering
if you wanted to maybe
get together to talk.
Marcy, you there?
Uh, so, if you'd like to,
just give me a call back.
Okay. Bye.
Marcy?
Yeah, Philip, go ahead.
We need you at Ops.
Boyd showed up with one of her teammates.
What's happening?
I don't know.
She said it's some kind
of viral infection.
There's growing concern
for an outbreak of a new flu strain
that has infected a number
of people in recent days.
While much is still unknown
about this virus...
Hey, Sarge.
I never got my assignment.
Connicker, what are you doing here?
I'm filling in.
Yeah, right.
This flu is kicking us around.
You get your shot yet?
No. Not yet.
Well, you better get on it.
You covering McAllister or Boyd?
McAllister.
Hospital.
Top authorities are expressing concern
over the intensity of the symptoms
and the speed in which the virus
seems to be spreading.
So it presents like classic flu...
fever, sore throat, headache.
Yeah, but it's not the flu.
He received
the same broad-spectrum
antiviral we all did.
Okay, a virus that's not the flu...
Um...
Meningitis? West Nile?
I checked those.
I checked them all, actually.
There's no match.
Well...
...Okay, well, if it's a virus,
we can identify which one it is.
I've checked every gene sequence
for every virus in the 21st
and every century after that.
Are you saying that it's a new pathogen?
Yeah. Unknown in this time or in ours.
How is that even possible?
"O, my love, my wife!"
"Death...
"Death sucked the honey of thy breath,
have no power yet upon thy beauty."
Seriously, you guys?
How old are you?
Go ahead, Trevor.
"...Upon thy beauty.
"Thou art not conquered.
"Beauty's ensign yet
"is crimson in thy lips
and in thy cheeks,
and death's pale flag..."
Trevor? You there?
...Aye.
Good. Okay, okay.
Take it from, um...
You in class?
Mm-hmm.
"Dear Juliet, Why art thou yet so fair?"
Okay, you need to leave.
You might be infected
with a dangerous pathogen.
Keep your distance
from other people and get outside.
- What's happening?
- Just go now.
We're skipping to the last section.
One final embrace,
one last kiss, and then...
Go, now. MacLaren's waiting for you.
I got to go.
You don't have to kiss, just read.
Don't! Don't touch me!
I'm sorry... I got to go.
Hardly even looks like a virus.
No, you kind of expect something
pleomorphic.
Spherical capsid... radial symmetry.
That's what's infected us?
That's what we're trying to determine.
Oh, good! I need blood from both of you.
What do you call it?
Mm. We haven't got that far yet.
Boyd's viral count
is up in the hundreds of thousand,
her teammate's up over a million.
Here. Seems to be tied
to the antiviral mission somehow.
We got it two weeks before you did.
Heath's immune system
was already compromised.
I had to remove one of his lungs
after a mission blew up
near the beginning.
His antibodies
are showing no cross-reactivity,
his body just keeps amplifying it.
So how do we get it under control?
Heath!
- Little help?
- Guys!
We need to sedate him!
Keep holding him down!
I can't get a BP.
There's no pulse.
One, two... three, four...
five, six, seven,
eight, nine, ten.
11, 12, 13, 14,
15, 16, 17, 18, 19...
Stop CPR.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven,
eight, nine, ten.
- One, two, three, four...
- He's gone. Marcy.
- ...Five, six...
- Marcy!
He's gone.
I'm sorry.
Come on.
Let's get you off your feet.
You need some rest.
I think it's a little late for that.
So...
how's it looking?
We're all infected, aren't we?
Not all.
You, Philip, and Carly have it.
You and I somehow rejected the virus.
What?
Each of your blood samples
has a viral load between 500
and 1,000 copies per milliliter.
Ours is zero.
What about antibodies?
Trace amounts.
Somehow, we're immune.
How is that possible?
It's hard to say,
without running more tests.
So, if we're immune,
can't you create a blood serum?
We'll try, but we might be
running out of time.
If this started with the mission,
we can't be the only ones.
Check the deep web
for any other teams
reporting the same symptoms.
If it's transmitted
through air particles and fomites,
that means there's a good chance
you've infected everyone
you've come into contact with.
Are you sure?
Outside of an immunity,
we're predicting an infection rate
of over 40%.
40?
Call everyone
you've come into contact with.
Tell them to stay inside.
Boss, you're gonna want to see this.
Traveler teams from around the world
are reporting the same sickness.
They've been
transmitting it this whole time.
If I get you more of the antiviral,
can you analyze it?
See what went wrong?
Possibly, but I'm running low
on ethidium bromide.
It's a controlled substance,
it's not something you can get
on short notice.
What about your hospital?
Yeah, the lab should have some.
I'll text you a name.
You two, track down the team
that handed off the vials,
I'll go to the hospital.
I've got to get my son
from the babysitter's.
Carly! You're infected.
The best thing that you can do
for Jeffrey right now
is stay away.
Hi, David. Um, it's me, Marcy.
I was just wondering
if you wanted to maybe
get together to talk.
Uh, so, if you'd like to,
just give me a call back.
Okay, bye.
David?
Marce! Hey!
Sorry, I just got your message.
I was out riding.
Uh, I'd love to meet up.
Um, where are you right now?
I'm at home.
Okay, don't leave.
You coming over?
No, David. Uh...
A dangerous flu is spreading.
Like SARS?
Worse than that.
W...
Wait. What-what? Where are you?
I'm-I'm safe. Just...
Why do I get more worried
every time you say that?
David, you don't
need to worry about me, okay?
Well, I do, I worry about you.
And I worry about my clients,
most of whom...
don't have a home to stay inside of.
David...
Just stay home.
I've seen how bad this can get.
Marce, I'm sorry.
Thank you for telling me,
but I've got to go.
David!
...And reporting
a wide range of symptoms,
from common flu ailments,
like headache, fatigue, and fever,
to, in rare cases, more extreme symptoms,
including redness
and bleeding around the eyes.
At this point,
health authorities
are advising the public
to stay home if they don't feel...
Where are you headed?
Home.
When you get there, stay there.
There seems to be a bad flu going around.
And tell everyone you know, all right?
Sure thing.
...Officials have been able to determine
that despite being referred to
by most as "the flu,"
this is not actually
a new strain of influenza
but rather a new virus completely.
The origins of the virus...
Mac, where are you?
It's all-hands over here.
I know, listen.
Did you receive an antiviral
in the last two weeks?
Yeah, I had to save some hosts.
Any of your team sick?
Yeah. Three of us. Why?
We've seen Traveler reports
this is happening all over the world,
and I think
we are the primary transmitters.
Shit!
I have my team tracking down
the antiviral, to run some tests.
All right, well, let me know how it goes.
In the meantime,
the CDC's setting up shelters,
Wakefield wants us
to meet up with the National Guard.
I'll text you the address.
Look, I'm on my way to the hospital.
I'll have to meet you in 30.
All right.
Graham?
Graham! It's Trevor.
I'll go check the back.
Sure.
Hi. Sorry. Can you tell me
who's in charge here?
What do you need?
He's got a bad fever, a headache.
He needs to see a doctor.
Well, he's not gonna get one here.
The E.R.'s been in overflow for an hour,
and people with the flu
are being sent home.
He'll be better off at home.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Nurse, he doesn't have a home.
Well, he's better off anywhere but here.
You his family?
Case worker.
How many people
are you caring for right now?
Uh...
Officially or unofficially?
Wait here.
Oh. Here. Um...
It's not much,
but it's better than nothing.
Thank you.
Yeah. Be sure to keep one for yourself.
Thank you, that's very kind.
Take care!
Agent MacLaren!
David.
Is Marcy here?
No.
Maybe you could pass
along a message for me?
Could you ask her
to come by the shelter a little later?
These guys are in rough shape.
I'll pass it along,
but her hands are pretty full right now.
Yeah, I bet.
Excuse me! Why are you taking her?
We were here first!
I'm not taking anyone, sir, relax.
We've got a kid here!
How bad is it?
Okay. I'll let you get to it, then.
Remember to ask Marcy...
I will. Good luck.
Yeah, you too.
Pupils are sluggish.
Intracranial pressure?
I mean, that would explain
the headaches and the seizures.
We could try mannitol,
or skip straight to a cerebral shunt.
Great.
Isn't that your specialty?
Funny.
We got company.
Let me in!
I can't, we're sick.
So am I! Let me in!
One of those teenage
petri dishes got me sick.
What's all this?
We got a mission to save people
who were gonna die from the flu,
but the Director's antiviral didn't work.
That's impossible.
There's also an outbreak
in Shanghai and Berlin.
Hey, Mac, you there?
Go ahead.
We found the delivery team,
but no antiviral.
The supply was cleared out
and the team had been assassinated.
What?
There was no sign
of struggle or forced entry.
Wh... Are you thinking inside job?
It wouldn't be the first time
a team turned on each other.
Right?
None of this makes any sense.
Okay. I'll see you back at Ops.
She doesn't look good.
Not helpful.
Hold this above her head.
None of this matters
in the long run.
The Director will fix it!
Didn't fix him.
Traveler incoming.
Ah! Told ya!
Here comes the cavalry.
It's good to see you. We need help.
Everyone does.
All right, let's have the cure.
We can chat later.
- There is no cure.
- What?
Of course there is.
We're from the future.
Several teams are working on a viricide,
but so far without success.
I'm here to talk to Philip.
I want to go over the antiviral
data one more time.
Maybe we made a mistake.
I don't know what you're talking about.
The formula you wrote on the wall.
It allowed us
to synthesize the antiviral.
It's right here, look.
I remember this...
but I don't remember writing it down.
How do you not remember?
That's impossible.
When did this happen?
About two weeks ago.
You were with 4514.
Jenny.
What?
I had a headache
and she told me it was from the drops.
She must have given you
a memory inhibitor.
Oh, God.
Please tell me what is going on.
Just go get her!
Hello?
Hey. It's me.
What's happening? Are you all right?
Grant, have you seen the news?
No. I-I haven't.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yeah, just feeling a bit...
shaky, I don't know.
Probably just the news making me crazy.
Can you come home?
Not... Not yet. Look, just lie down, Kat.
And stay inside! Okay?
Okay. What about you?
Are you gonna be all ri...
Well, look at this.
Grant?
I gotta go.
I just... uh, I'll call you soon.
Come to get a look at
some real police work?
Carly's worried about your son.
You need to pick him up and go home.
You running errands for her now?
I thought that shit was over between you.
It was never what you thought it was.
And, right now,
this is about something bigger than that.
You need to pick up your son,
Jeff, and go home.
Hey, it's Marcy. We need you back at Ops.
We know the source of the antiviral.
A Traveler named Jenny. Philip knows her.
I'm on my way.
Mac, it's been over an hour.
What are you doing here?
We're late. We gotta meet
with the National Guard.
You'll have to do it without me.
We need you.
My team comes first.
Jenny!
Chloe!
Jenny?
Oh, no... no, no, no, no, no.
No, no. Jenny. Hey, hey.
Hey! Hey.
No. No, no. No. No.
Are you sure about this?
Do I have any other choice?
All right.
Her vitals are good.
Ohh...
She's stable.
Okay.
Carly?
Shit.
Shh. It's okay. I got you.
I got you, I got you. It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
Shh-shh-shh. It's okay.
You know, when I was a kid,
my mom would make me chicken soup
when I was sick.
Not exactly sure
why it was always chicken soup.
Vera!
Hey, I was trying to reach you.
I said no doctors!
- Okay. No, no...
- Don't touch me.
No. It's David. See?
Hi!
You okay?
Yeah.
All right. You got something to eat?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
I'll be around if you need me. Okay?
It's okay, big man.
We're gonna get through this.
We're gonna be fine.
You're a fighter.
Just like Mama.
Just like Daddy.
It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
Hey.
I sense that doctor you sent me to
likes you a lot.
Where's...
what's-her-name, Jenny?
They should be back any minute.
Philip knows her how?
Ah. Okay. So what's this?
I'm trying to determine
the pathogen's reproduction number,
based on hospital databases,
social media updates...
Here. Let me show you something.
An "r-nought" indicates
how infectious a virus is
by determining the rate
of secondary infection.
If it's less than one,
the virus will quickly die out.
If it's greater than one...
We have an epidemic.
So what are we dealing with?
Let's put it into perspective...
Influenza has an r-nought of one...
...With an incubation period of two days.
Chances are you'd infect
one person in a day,
then they'd go on
to infect one more, and so on.
This virus has an r-nought
of at least two,
with an incubation period...
of 10 days.
14 days ago,
10 traveler teams across the world
transmitted the virus.
So that is...
Potentially
150 people on day one...
330...
...on day two.
I don't like where this is going.
So, based on the data I pulled
from people already reporting symptoms,
and factoring in
the exponential growth rate...
Over 4 million people
are currently infected.
Tomorrow, it'll be almost 10.
Most of them aren't showing symptoms yet,
but they will soon.
So how long before
the death rate starts to climb?
A couple of days.
I need some help out here!
Clear off that table.
Marcy, I don't know if she's breathing.
She took pills.
Get her up here.
I got a weak pulse!
What'd she take?
Oxycodone.
Hey. Hey, hey, Jenny.
I'm here. I'm here.
You're at Ops. You're safe.
You're safe.
You overdosed. I found you in your room.
Hey! Listen to me. Listen to me.
The mission is in trouble.
No, Philip.
The mission went exactly as planned.
What?
What do you know?
It won't change anything.
What did you make me do?
My team...
they tried to record messengers...
...but any incoming signal
caused static on our devices.
We needed a historian.
And someone to synthesize the catalyst.
No.
I was directed to create an antiviral.
Actually,
you were directed
to expedite genetic recombination
of the historical pathogen.
You created the new virus.
No, no, no. She's delirious.
The Director would never
order that mission.
Who said the mission
came from the Director?
The future I left
was divided
between those loyal to the Director
and the Faction.
Both sides fighting for control,
back and forth.
When you reset the Director,
we lost the ability to access the 21st.
We lost the past, we lost everything.
We had no choice
but to shut down the reactor.
We've had missions.
Received messengers.
And that's all. Only messengers.
Without the Director's processing power,
consciousness transfer isn't possible.
So...
before power was cut to the Director,
in our last moment of control,
we sent everyone we could to the 21st.
All at once.
Into the quantum frame?
How many?
The frame is capable
of receiving and storing thousands.
So Forbes,
all those people with the FBI...
Are all Faction.
Every mission we've done since...
...Has been for them.
The Faction has our own plan.
Overpopulation
is the single greatest threat
to the 21st century.
The Director wasn't capable
of seeing the natural solution.
How many people are gonna die?
The virus is genetically engineered
to preserve 70% of the population.
The future will survive.
And those of us who die, including me,
will have made a great sacrifice.
70%?
Jenny, you're murdering
over 2 billion people.
The mission comes first.
Take positions
around the device and stand by.
What the hell is that?
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com