Previously, on Travelers...
The Director gave me a new mission.
We're going to make you
whole again, Simon.
One of the first things that Simon did
when he arrived
was create a whole new physical layer.
Our back channel on the deep web.
He's watching you.
Simon, what are you doing here?
I helped build the first one
in the future, too.
We're aware of your phone call.
We want you to keep that appointment.
All you need to do is lead us there,
and we'll do the rest.
This is a message
for Agent Grant MacLaren.
He must come alone and on time,
or I will never be heard from again.
Seven months ago,
my consciousness was sent
from the distant future
into the body of Special
Agent Grant MacLaren
moments before he would,
historically, have died
in the line of duty.
Since then, I have assumed
his life, his work...
his marriage...
pretending to be a man
very different than myself.
In truth, I am Traveler 3468,
one of thousands of Travelers
around the world
who have come from a time
when life is all but wiped out,
to save humanity,
to change the path.
I know how that must sound,
especially to you, Kat...
but it's true.
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
Good afternoon, Agent MacLaren.
Where is she?
Perrow? She's safe.
Though her neck might be a little tender
after having to remove the com
she allowed you to plant.
Let her go, Ingram.
Of course.
Soon as we put this to an end.
I'd like to propose a truce.
You kidnapped
and tortured my team,
killed Travelers all over the world.
I needed to know if
the Director was still after me,
and that suspicion was confirmed.
My mission was to die
immediately after my arrival.
By surviving,
I committed a crime
against the Grand Plan
and was condemned to death.
Is that fair?
Not up to me.
No.
No, it's up to the Director,
who has no understanding,
no forgiveness,
no soul,
because it is a machine.
I am tired of running.
Take a selfie, you can end it right now.
To me, the digital age
has created a prison around me,
one that's been...
shrinking over time.
It's no way for my son to grow up.
Are you trying to get sympathy from me?
No. No.
No, I want your word
that you'll leave me alone
while I prepare my affairs
and face my accuser.
That's not going to go well for you.
I have no illusions.
I know exactly what's going to happen.
I stole 16 years
that I wouldn't otherwise have had,
and in that time,
I created a precious life.
My son shouldn't have to pay
for the mistakes of his father.
Do I have your word?
You don't have my anything.
That's not actually true.
Grant, please help me!
You son of a...
If you freaking hurt her...
3468,
if you want to see your wife again,
follow this simple instruction...
Stay out of my way.
He showed me a video.
She's being held somewhere.
Is she hurt?
I don't know, I couldn't tell.
Boss, he's faked things like this before.
Are you sure it was Kathryn?
Yes, and her phone
goes straight to voicemail.
What does he want?
- A truce.
-  Bullshit.
He said he's going
to show himself to the Director
and face punishment,
but he wants us all to stand down
so he can make arrangements for his son.
Kat is his insurance.
He spent all this time
hiding and torturing Travelers,
only to turn himself in?
I don't buy it either.
Right now I just want Kat to be safe.
Philip, can you trace her phone's GPS?
I can try.
I don't think he can monitor our coms,
but let's be careful.
If he finds out we're looking for her...
What about Perrow?
He claims she's still alive,
but you should all check
on your loved ones
and make sure they're okay.
I'm going to Kat's place.
David's not answering.
Neither is Jeff.
Gary, hey!
I'm just checkin' in. How is everything?
Okay, let's go.
Mom's good, too?
No, I won't be home for dinner,
and I gotta run,
but you guys have a good day.
Please!
I'm sorry for having
treated you this way,
but we needed to remove the device
as quickly as possible.
Where's my daughter?
Home.
I don't believe you.
There's someone
supervising her as we speak.
Hello?
Ava!
Sweetie, are you hurt?
No.
There's a man here.
Are you coming home?
Soon, very soon.
Where are you? You said you were...
I promise you,
Ava is going to see her mother shortly.
There's just one more thing
I need you to do.
David?
Guys, David's gone.
So are Jeff and the baby.
Marcy, the place is destroyed.
What do we do?
Never thought my day
would start this way.
You really want to mount
an inter-agency investigation
into Vincent Ingram?
You're wasting time.
Mac, think this through.
He has them captive.
And he warned you things could get worse.
The man said he was going
to give himself up
to the Director,
let's just wait this out...
And you believe him?
- Why would he go to the trouble of...
- He's psychotic!
He's spent years hunting Traveler teams,
mine included.
They'd be dead if I hadn't used
NSA resources...
Which is one of the reasons
why they're onto us.
What are you talking about?
A few weeks ago, I saw a report.
DOD, Homeland Security,
CIA, the NSA...
It wasn't just my host task force
that was suspicious.
We've been discovered across
all the intelligence services.
Probably worldwide.
Jesus.
They think we're some new
terrorist organization.
Cells in over a hundred countries.
They haven't acted because
they're scared as shit.
Our people at the NSA
and Homeland Security
are concealing us as best they can,
but at this point,
it's only a matter of time
before there are leaks.
Going after Ingram would raise
a red flag we can't afford.
Boss, I managed to unlock
multiple locations from their phones.
The last one recorded
was 3:28 p.m. yesterday,
all from the same place.
Send me the address.
Keep your eye on the back channels.
The rest of you, meet me there.
Mac!
Hello, Kathryn.
My name is Katrina Perrow.
I'm a psychologist.
Where am I?
I'm not permitted to tell you that.
Why are we here?
There are questions
I'm supposed to ask you,
but I want you to know
that I am also doing this
against my will.
They've taken my daughter, Ava.
Now, if we just work together
and do what they want,
they'll let us all go.
Can we do that?
When did you first notice
changes in your husband?
It's all been for the greater good.
The lives lost when Van Huizen exploded
ensured the survival of millions
who would have died
just over a year from now.
Millions of people
who have no idea
how close they came to the end,
and they were saved by Travelers.
That's what we do.
Carly Shannon historically died
at the hand of her drunk,
abusive boyfriend.
And now,
instead of her child being raised
by a dead-beat father,
he is surrounded by love.
My love.
Jeffrey Conniker Jr.
will grow up to be a good man,
and millions of people around the world
won't suffer from the Helios catastrophe.
So do you know what I have to say
about coming here,
and taking this body, and doing our work?
You're welcome.
Shit.
That's Grace's phone.
_
Simon...
you said it wouldn't take long.
Yeah, but that's before
the interface overheated,
and yeah, I knew you were there,
you didn't sneak up on me.
There isn't much time.
I know. I have a clock in my head.
I need more coolant.
Did you bring it?
Everything you need is in this room.
Remember we're doing this for you.
You said "multiple uses."
Multiple transfers.
Yes,
and then we'll take care of you.
David?
David.
Sorry, I'm just...
never been kidnapped before.
I've been held hostage,
but that's a whole...
Please, just...
answer the question.
Uh, yeah.
I am,
was, her social worker.
How do you know about Marcy?
Where is she?
She's safe.
As in...
safely captured,
or safe at home?
They didn't take her.
"They"?
The same people who took my daughter.
I...
That's terrible, I'm...
Then they're after me?
- What did I do?
- David, please...
just answer the questions
if you want us both to get out of here.
Okay.
Is it true that one day
Marcy's cognitive abilities changed,
and for all intents and purposes,
she was an entirely different person?
Yeah.
Didn't that seem odd to you?
Of course it did.
I thought a miracle had happened,
are you kidding me?
How did you justify that change?
I'm pretty sure I shouldn't
be talking about this.
You have doctor-client privilege with me.
You're not my doctor.
David...
She's a doctor.
Marcy Warton?
With the FBI, undercover.
She goes on secret missions...
I've said too much.
And you believed her?
Yeah, I met her boss.
Grant MacLaren.
He's real. I've been to his office.
God, he's gonna kill me.
I cracked in, like, five seconds.
David...
Marcy Warton is not an FBI agent.
She's a traveler
from the future.
A who?
A time traveler.
That is the stupidest thing I've ever...
She was supposed to be killed
by a group of men
outside the library where she worked.
Seconds before her death,
a consciousness was sent from the future,
supplanting Marcy's own,
and that new traveler
survived the attack.
And...
just a few months ago,
that consciousness
was replaced yet again.
She called it memory loss,
but in fact, she was...
overwritten.
Lady...
what the hell have you been smoking?
Hi.
I'm sorta glad I'm not alone here.
I'm David.
Kathryn.
Kathryn...
Are they all right?
Still on whatever drug they gave me.
You don't know any of them, do you?
Uh... okay, wow. Yes.
You do?
Ray?
Ray, wake up!
He got me out of a legal jam recently.
It was weird...
Ray!
Ray! Wake up...
I already tried yelling.
Oh, for God's sakes.
What?
I know him too.
He's a cop.
He interviewed me once about Marcy.
Who's Marcy?
Apparently
a time traveler from the future.
She said my husband was, too.
- Dr. Perrow?
- Yeah.
Yeah, but you don't a actually believe...
Of course not.
Oh, shit...
It's all right, you're not alone.
Where's my son? Where's Jeffrey?
He's just a baby...
He's not with us, I'm sorry.
You're MacLaren's wife.
Agent MacLaren?
You know who I am?
Yeah, I came to your house and told you
that your husband was screwing around
with my girl, Carly.
- Carly?
- What?
Yeah, you don't remember?
No, and I think that's something
I would remember.
So then why would he bring us here?
What? Why would Grant do this?
She's right, I don't think
this is an FBI thing.
How do you know
my husband works with the FBI?
He's Marcy's boss, isn't he?
David Mailer.
You're the social worker creep
that was screwin' around with
the retarded girl, Marcy.
That's a hateful word.
Okay, wait, who the fuck is Marcy?
His client!
One minute she's mentally disabled,
the next minute,
she's whoopin' half a dozen boys
outside the library...
Yeah, she was under cover!
All right!
Enough of this shit!
We talk,
or we get out of here.
Hey!
Whoever the hell you think you are,
you just kidnapped
a Metro police officer!
That's a class-A felony,
and I'm gonna put your ass away!
You hear me?
Do you have be so loud?
Who the hell are you?
Hello. I'm... I'm David.
I'm a friend of Marcy's.
This is Kathryn.
She's married to Agent MacLaren,
who's Marcy's boss.
This is Ray.
He's still unconscious.
The unhappy man is Officer Conniker,
who I'm guessing is
in a relationship with Carly,
who's also a friend of Marcy,
all of whom may or may not
be time travelers.
And you are?
I'm a... high school guidance counselor.
Oh, okay. That makes perfect sense.
Wait, no. Don't you touch me.
No. No.
No...
Where are you taking me?
Let me go!
The lady asked you to let her go...
Back off! No!
Let me go!
Who's he again?
He's my lawyer.
Vincent's sending us something.
Boss!
Grant, in order for me
to be released unharmed,
you must confess to...
being a Traveler on video.
You have one hour to send it to this IP,
or they'll kill me.
_
Shit, not again.
Ray?
David.
Yeah.
We've been kidnapped.
I know that sounds crazy, but...
How much do you owe Vargese?
Vargese, anyone?
We're not sure why we're here.
Does this have anything to do
with the guy in your apartment
who, uh...
What?
Oh... maybe?
What's with Mr. Big and Tall here?
Hey, wait...
Come on, take it easy, what the...
Jesus.
Boss, I have to say this...
If we do this,
it goes against everything
we trained for.
I know.
I'm sorry.
I'm not going to let my wife die.
I feel the same way about David.
Look, listen, listen!
I want nothing more
than to hold my son right now,
but the mission comes first.
If you sit down at that computer
with the intention of confessing,
you will be overwritten.
I think I know how we can do this
and still maintain Protocol 1.
I got my hands on
an advanced rootkit virus
that I can plant in the code
of the video file.
Is it traceable?
Four months ago,
it compromised the Relicus Maxicloud
in Austria for 47 minutes,
and they still don't know who did it.
Do you?
The Faction.
I can track the video
on the back channels
and find his location.
What if it spreads?
I'll know where it goes,
When the time comes, we can shut it down.
Yeah, if the Director
lets us get that far.
I'm still not struck by lightning.
Do it.
Ready when you are.
Seven months ago,
my consciousness was sent
from the distant future
into the body of
Special Agent Grant MacLaren...
Cooling systems at minus 270 degrees.
Superconductor efficiency, 99.8%.
Simon!
It's overheating.
Shut it down!
Simon!
It was supposed to work!
Can you fix it?
I told you, the device requires...
Simon!
Can you fix it?
This was all for you.
All for you.
I'm his only friend?
Man, that is tragic.
The guy travels through time,
becomes a junkie,
and his only friend is a lawyer
with a gambling addiction
who uses him?
I'd like to, uh, keep us on track.
How are things at home?
Where's my son?
Jeffrey's okay.
For now.
What does that mean?
It means if you and I cooperate,
then you'll see your son,
and I'll see my daughter,
but that entirely depends on you.
There are some things about Carly
you need to know.
...In truth,
I am Traveler 3468...
Oh, Jesus Christ, Mac.
We've got it under control.
Clearly you don't.
My teammate at the NSA flagged this
during her routine scan
for Traveler activity.
If any other agent had found...
Yeah, well, they didn't,
and we've taken extra precautions
with Philip's virus.
Now, once we get to Vincent,
we can corrupt the video.
I just need time to flush him out.
The intelligence agencies
already have a target on our backs.
Well, then, let's work together
and get ahead of it.
Those with my specialty
are chosen as infants
in order to develop their minds
to specifically serve
the Traveler program.
Some days I felt like an experiment,
other days like a super-human.
Today I'm...
The Director has kept watch
over my entire life,
knowing the outcome of every decision,
crafting my path forward,
but here,
I see people every day
who still believe in free will.
They don't know any better.
I've taken down bigger guys than you.
Do any of you think
this could actually be true?
What?
A few months ago,
I definitely noticed changes in Grant.
It was truly like
he was a different person.
What they're saying would explain...
Oh, please.
Like time travel is actually possible?
Okay, maybe you could send information
in the form of some coherent energy
across space-time,
but to calculate an exact position
would require an almost
impossible level of accuracy,
not to mention
nearly a billion zettaflops
of processing power,
and then to unpack it somehow,
without entropy,
in a... biological...
What do you do again?
Guidance counselor.
He knows you tampered
with MacLaren's recording.
Now each and every one of you
must record...
your own confessions,
or we will all be killed.
Marcy, I just want to go home.
I just wanna go home.
All right, look, look, look, listen,
we know there's only one way in
and one way out, right?
Now, there's two of them, two of us...
Let's take 'em.
Oh, I can't wait to see this.
Yeah. Yeah, okay.
Next time, we jump 'em.
You take the tall one.
Which one is the tall one?
Oh, my god.
David... It's okay, I got you.
I can't see out of my right eye.
Is it okay?
It's just swollen shut.
"Just."
Try that shit with me.
Wait, wait, wait.
Don't.
I get it. I'm next.
Let's go.
My purpose is to save lives,
whether that's a teammate in jeopardy,
or someone that's part of a mission
ordered by the Director...
but I can't help but think
that I've put one person's life
in more danger than they deserve.
David...
you've suffered because of me,
and there's just...
there's no excuse for that.
I cared enough to leave once.
I should have just stayed away.
I've lowered the temperature in the room.
I know it's cold.
It's bracing, yes.
Is it ready?
Almost.
It's almost done.
For 2,000 years,
mankind believed that God
was created in his image,
guiding our lives, hearing our prayers...
Could you hand me the screwdriver?
But when those prayers weren't answered,
we just chalked it up to His divine will.
But then mankind created
the power to build God,
a machine more powerful
than any human mind could ever be...
It's just, uh, on the workbench...
The fate of our existence
just handed to an AI
with the ability to monitor
each and every shifting timeline,
while we blindly obey its orders
with the belief that salvation will come.
It's the Phillips head...
The problem isn't the fact
that we believed in God...
"It's that we didn't
believe in ourselves."
Fine, I'll get it.
It's time to pull back the curtain
and take control of the present,
to fight for our future.
It's working.
Simon...
We can finally fix you.
A psychologist?
And you actually enjoy
talking to people for a living?
When I'm not under duress.
All right, let's get it over with, then.
When are you from?
What is your mission?
What is your specialty?
What is your Sp...
All right, enough!
You can stop pretending, Traveler 0027.
Shit.
The videos have been
disseminated to servers
in nearly every major city.
Any luck over there?
Locked out of everything.
You said you could control the virus.
Yeah, well, he's pretty good, too.
What are you saying?
What I'm saying is that
I can't corrupt the video files
that are already out there.
The world is about
to find out who we are.
Why isn't the Director stepping in?
We must eventually
find a way to solve this.
If not, it had its chance
to overwrite any one of us
when we recorded our confession.
He's sending us a message.
UDIDs, MAC addresses,
possible coordinates.
He's making us work for it.
He's a dead man.
He's a psychotic recluse!
You're asking me
if time travel is possible.
You say that out loud again,
and slowly.
You've seen it too.
We couldn't get ahead of it.
He sent it to all the major news outlets,
intelligence agencies...
I have to believe
that 21st-century skepticism
is alive and well.
Yeah, for the New York Times, sure,
but this isn't going to be something
that goes away with the news cycle.
The information he has
fills in the pieces
on dozens of Traveler missions
the CIA could never explain.
It's only a matter of time
before they put it all together...
No, the Director
will never let that happen.
Yeah, well, here we are.
What about your wife?
Boss, I think I know where they are.
Sending you coordinates.
This is the same...
What the hell?
If you have any questions
about what you've just seen,
feel free to ask Grace.
She's one of them.
Ava? Sweetie?
Mom!
The man said you're coming home.
I'll be home soon.
I love you.
I love you too.
I wanted to say goodbye.
I'm scared.
Don't be.
You did it, Simon.
The device works perfectly.
Will you stay with me?
If that's what you want.
Thank you, Vincent.
Thank you.
I was part of the original test program
for consciousness transfer...
something we had to master
before we could even dream
of traveling back through time,
and I lived in many bodies,
which makes me one of
the oldest living people
in human history...
I'll never forget what I saw
the first time I woke up...
my former body
with glassy eyes staring back at me.
There was no one in there anymore.
Just a husk.
That image stays with me everywhere I go.
Traveler 5692.
Arrival successful.
All right,
there's two of them, two of us.
It's now or never.
Cancel the plan, cancel the plan!
What are you... Ow!
Where are you taking us?
Though this news is still breaking,
we can confirm that Vincent Ingram,
owner of one of the world's
leading securities firms,
is responsible for bringing to light
what may be a new terrorist group
with cells positioned
throughout the world...
Let me know when you have confirmation
that the device has been moved.
I need to speak with my son.
Hello, Taylor.
Remember me?
Hi.
Did your father explain to you
that you're going to be
living with me for a while?
Yeah, but he didn't say why.
So that we can be free.
I'm Dr. Katrina Perrow,
and Vincent Ingram has been my patient
for the last four months.
For the purposes of this recording,
he has asked me to break
doctor-patient confidentiality.
This is not a subject
one can discuss openly,
because frankly,
it flies in the face
of 21st-century science
and what we currently perceive
to be possible,
but everything you've heard is true.
Travelers do exist.
What do you see?
Nothin' but God's country.
Only reason to take us
out to the middle of nowhere
is to kill us.
Might as well say your prayers.
Do people still pray in the future?
They operate covertly
in cells made up of five members...
...each with a specialty.
Their missions are sent
from an advanced AI
that continuously keeps watch
over an ever-changing timeline.
They are spies, terrorists,
...and they will not stop
until their Director
has achieved its primary goal,
the Grand Plan.
They are our wives, our husbands,
our sons, and our daughters.
They know our secrets,
they know our future.
They gain our trust, our affection,
but it's all a lie.
We must do whatever we can to stop them.
Jesus, Kat, I was so afraid...
Who are you?
David!
Don't... don't touch me.
We can get through this.
I don't think so.
Ray, I am so sorry that
you had to go through that.
I gotta hand it to you, kid,
you were straight with me from the start.
But let's not pretend we're friends.
Please let me hold him.
Stay the hell away from my son.
You hear me?
Grace, are you okay?
I... I don't know.
I'm telling you, this whole thing...
No...
No, I can explain who did this.
I don't want to hear anything from you.
You killed my husband.
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com