Previously, on Travelers...
She uploaded a command while
pretending to save Marcy's life.
You mean you used me.
I have filed a recommendation
for his father to take custody.
Jacqueline, please!
It's not safe.
Pack a bag, go to your mother's
for a few days, maybe a week.
Okay, here I am.
What's so important?
I'm Traveler 4112.
The Quantum Frame, it's being scrapped.
I'm gonna need your help
with a lot of things.
Welcome to the 21st.
I am so sorry.
"How could he be offering
a Whistler chalet,
"a Tuscan villa,
and a Caribbean hideaway,
all for $20,000?"
I've gotta be honest...
I'm wondering the same thing.
Look, I've been doing this a while,
and I have never seen a deal like this!
So which property
appeals to you the most?
Maybe the Caribbean hideaway?
Don't we all
wish we were there right now?
But seven to ten days a year?
That's, like, $2,000 a day.
Yeah!
If you go once!
It's a lifestyle.
Isn't that what
you were interested in, Dale?
Yeah... I said that.
But that was after you said
this would only take 90 minutes
and we'd get a free dinner
at House of Rib.
90 minutes...
No, I hear you.
All right...
I don't know how I'm gonna do it,
but let me go talk to my manager,
and see if we can do better.
Give me five.
When I come back,
you'll have a whole new perspective.
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
Kat!
I thought you said the danger was over.
It is.
Then why are you holding a gun?
You didn't call me back.
I thought you were still
at your mother's.
Why didn't you say something
when you came in the house?
I expected you to be at work!
I've been up all night.
I'm sorry if...
Doesn't matter,
I'm just glad you're home.
I'm not home. I'm just here
to get a few things.
I know the last couple of days
have been insane.
You know, I must have
left a dozen messages.
Until I got yours
at 4:00 this morning,
I thought for sure you were dead.
That's all over now.
What's over?
Tell me.
You know I can't talk about my work.
You've never said my life was in danger!
Because of my work,
I was targeted by a... a group.
And I was afraid, by association,
you might be in danger, too.
It's not the case,
they're no longer a threat.
That's all I can say.
How do I even know that's true?
You're obviously capable of lying to me.
Please stay and talk.
I'll make breakfast.
No, I'm not gonna do that.
Kat! Hey.
What? Are you planning on supervising?
What do you want from me?
I don't want anything from you, Grant.
Not a single thing.
David?
Hey!
I made pancakes.
You probably don't remember
what pancakes are,
but I happen to know
that you like them a lot.
What's wrong?
Uh, nothing, just, uh...
You used to sleep naked when we met,
and I thought maybe you...
Nope.
False alarm.
How long you been up?
Oh, since, uh...
All night.
I was thinking of maybe
watching some TV,
but then you were all wrapped up cozy
on the... on the couch,
and I didn't want to wake you, so, um...
then I, uh...
then I...
Hey, you know what?
Let's switch things up
and-and you sit here,
'cause I'm always sitting on this side.
Oh. Yeah. Yeah.
Thanks.
Good.
Are you okay?
Hmm?
Sure!
I don't know.
No.
I mean, a strange man died
right across from where
I eat my cereal every morning,
and I'm just having a hard time dealing.
David, he was gonna kill you.
That doesn't help.
I was the one that he was looking for.
Well, that definitely doesn't...
David, it's over.
You're safe.
Well, you know that...
does make me feel a little bit better.
I thought your parents
were never gonna leave.
They're just worried about me.
Yeah, but the doctor said
it's just temporary, right?
From the swelling?
Does it hurt?
No.
You really can't feel anything?
Uh-uh.
Nothing?
No.
What about this?
Whoa.
Rene...
The nurse could walk back in any minute.
You can feel that?
Rene...
Please... Please.
I'm still in recovery. I should rest.
I shouldn't get too excited.
Okay... babe. You rest.
I'll see you tomorrow...
and the next day...
and the next.
Do I seriously have to listen to that
tomorrow
and the next day and the next?
I almost pressed the call button
because I thought I was
gonna throw up my lunch.
She's very young.
You're very old.
I can't argue with that.
You really don't feel anything yet?
I mean, the amount of medical nanites
I gave you
was barely above the minimum threshold,
but I thought you'd have
some sensation by now.
With age comes patience.
How are you feeling?
Like I could walk out of here,
but I'll have to fake it for a while,
or they'll think I'm a medical miracle.
Mm!
Besides, I love the food in here.
It's amazing! Right?
Carly...
Carly!
What do you want?
How about you answer your phone?
I'm not here to creep,
just to say thanks.
You can thank your Sergeant.
He's the one that made me
give the statement.
Oh, I did.
Listen, I'm just as upset
about Jeffrey Jr. as you.
I'm not even allowed to see him, Jeff!
No contact.
Me neither.
You didn't know?
Hey, partner.
Everything all right?
I just went into
the wrong bathroom.
Back to basic training for you.
What's this?
Missing persons report.
Doesn't missing persons fall
under local law enforcement?
We come in if there's
an interstate component.
Right.
All six failed to check
out of the same hotel.
Left all their belongings.
"Serenity Inn and Suites."
So... So I guess we have to go there.
Yeah.
We're FBI agents.
Badges and everything.
All right, but, uh...
can you drive?
You just need practice.
Who'd like to start?
Hi. My name is Philip...
and I'm an addict.
Hi, Philip.
You know, the hardest part about this
is admitting to yourself
that you're not strong enough.
Uh, that you can't just stop...
even when you know
what it's doing to you.
I was doing really well, I was...
and then I lost somebody close to me.
Technically, not, uh, "lost" lost,
she's still in my life,
but she's just...
This is impossible to explain.
I feel like she's gone.
At least, a part of her is.
Anyway...
I miss her.
Thank you, Philip.
Who'd like to go next?
Hi.
I'm sorry about your friend.
Thanks.
We need all the support
we can get, right?
I'm Traveler 4514.
The Director assigned me to help you.
You're right.
A little fresh air is nice.
It's important not to get fixated.
Was I fixated?
Yeah, I was.
It's normal to be rattled by trauma.
You just want to make sure
it doesn't tip into
something more serious.
Like what?
Here, let's sit.
Jesus.
I think you're experiencing
early symptoms of PTSD.
That's ridiculous.
Soldiers in battle get PTSD.
First responders
of horrible disasters...
Heightened anxiety,
inability to sleep,
exaggerated startle response.
Exaggerated star...
You just made that one up!
I'm fine!
I mean, technically,
it's too early to diagnose,
but early treatment won't hurt
and it should help, so...
Here. Come here.
Give me your hands.
I want you to close your eyes.
I want you to think about
what happened to you
while you focus on my tapping... okay?
Seriously? Is this a real thing?
'Cause it-it feels a little bullshitty.
Uh, you know what? I'm sorry. I, uh...
Could we just keep walking?
Yeah. Good idea.
You know what?
I'm gonna head back to the apartment.
I'll meet you back there.
Where are you going?
To get something that'll help.
Okay.
So your mission is to help me?
Specifically to... give you this.
Eye drops?
Synthetic compound.
To help with the heroin addiction.
It's invented 20 years or so from now.
Naloxone, buprenorphine...
and some other things
that are even harder to pronounce.
But... it will stop the craving
and curb your withdrawal.
And I'm just getting this now?
Hey, I-I know you were trying hard,
but then you had the setback
when you got captured, they gave you...
How'd you know about that?
The future.
Maybe the Director figured
you'd quit on your own
and you couldn't do it.
There. See?
It's perfectly...
That wasn't funny.
Yes, it was.
One drop per eye, as needed.
Jenny, by the way.
These are amazing.
Yep.
Now what do I do?
Whatever you want.
What are you gonna do?
Did you receive any training
on a simulator?
You had a simulator?
Wow. Okay.
Uh, just loosen up on the wheel,
and try to get out of your head.
You know, sing a song or something.
Doesn't have to be a song.
Just recite something you know by heart.
Uh, list the protocols.
Uh, Protocol 1. Uh...
Mission comes first.
Uh, two, leave the future in the past.
Now, let's turn up here.
Protocol 3...
don't take a life, don't save a life,
- unless otherwise directed.
- Good.
Protocol 4, uh, don't reproduce.
Don't reproduce.
I don't know how the hell
you got to work today.
Uh, just like that.
Yeah, well, Protocol 2
isn't gonna get you out of practicing.
Hold on a sec.
Kat?
You're right. We should talk.
Great. Uh...
Come by the house tonight. I'll make...
I'm staying at Nicole's
while she's away.
I'll text you the address.
Sure. Want me to bring anyth...?
Carly, they took away our son.
We need to be on the same side.
You charged me with assault,
blocked me from getting a job,
told the judge I was an unfit mother.
You have every right to be pissed at me,
but I did those things
because I was pissed at you.
So how about we stop being
pissed at each other,
and see what happens?
When I saw the girl about to shoot you,
I just felt...
I can't imagine what I'd do
if I lost you for good.
Yeah, I guess I never did
thank you for that.
Mm, well, you still haven't.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
So walk us through what happened.
The seminar was going great.
I had two buyers on the hook.
Maybe three!
And then I...
I left the room near the end,
to go get my manager.
We usually offer a slightly better deal
to really drive it home.
Sure.
Except when I came back,
20 minutes later,
they were gone.
20 minutes?
It's a sales technique...
just let 'em stew on it a little bit.
Guess it wasn't such a great deal.
Can you show us the security footage?
Marce?
Hey. My key isn't working.
Hi.
Hey.
I stopped by the hardware store
on the way home,
and it turns out
they were having a big...
...sale on locks.
Yay, "safety."
Why don't you have a seat?
Now, we only use this
for training purposes.
We don't care.
Right.
Can I have one of these?
Sure, yeah, but they're a day old.
Press play, please.
You didn't tamper with this, did you?
No. No, I swear.
You can stop swearing.
Did you have more plans for the group?
We were gonna shuttle them
to our sister location
to pick up their free dinner vouchers.
In the shuttle bus outside?
Yeah. Yeah, why?
Might want to get your brakes checked.
What is this?
This is an eye-movement therapy kit
to treat PTSD.
All right.
Follow the light with your eyes.
I want you to think
about what you were doing
moments before the man arrived.
I was washing dishes.
Concentrate on how you felt.
What happened next?
Drying the dishes.
I-I don't see how this is supp...
This is part of
the desensitization process.
Give me your hands.
Close your eyes.
All right.
He forced his way in.
How did you feel when that happened?
He kept hitting me.
David...
David... David!
No!
David.
I'm right here.
Hey. Look at me. Hey!
You're fine. I am right here.
Okay?
You're fine. You're fine.
Why do you think
that they put a hole in on.
Let's concentrate on
one mystery at a time,
- shall we?
- Um.
New arrivals cause
static on video cameras,
so it's pretty obvious
that it's six new Travelers.
With a total disregard for Protocol 5.
Maybe they're working on mission.
Let's be sure. In the meantime,
we bury any connection to this hotel.
Philip, are you there?
Yeah, go ahead.
I'm leaving what looks
like the scene of a mass arrival...
six people in a hotel conference room.
Do you remember anything about
a group of travelers
arriving today in Bellingham?
Uh, how were they supposed to die?
I'm just guessing, but something
with a shuttle bus.
Brake failure, maybe?
Nothing like that today,
but you know the timeline's
been changing.
Yeah. Or maybe they went missing
for a different reason.
What, you mean like how we went missing?
Let's hope not.
I'll keep on it.
Sorry about that.
Oh, must be a relief.
What?
If you're seeing changes
in the timeline,
it'll mean you won't have
to carry the burden
of knowing everyone who's about to die.
Maybe eventually.
It's amazing how little has changed
considering everything we've done.
I know what happened
with Aleksander Andreiko.
Maybe we shouldn't
be talking about that.
Hey, I agree with what you did.
You saved that kid's life.
You know the Director isn't perfect.
We definitely shouldn't
be talking about that.
Don't forget. We created it.
The Director might not
be able to break rules,
but we can.
What?
I feel like I'm waiting
to be struck by lightning.
Not a black cloud in the sky.
Come on.
Where are we going?
It's a surprise.
Is that any better?
I have no idea.
I have another, different treatment.
Can it be later?
Sure.
Although, sometimes,
medicine is the best medicine.
Cannabis is known to help
with symptoms of...
Absolutely, it's known to.
You need to inhale the smoke.
Oh, I'm familiar with the process.
You know, it's excellent
for memory loss, too.
Hey.
Hi.
Come in.
Wow. This is nice.
You've been here before.
We helped her move in.
Right. Right.
All I remember is boxes.
What are you doing?
Opening some wine.
So, how long's Nicole away?
All year. She's on sabbatical.
What's that?
Separation papers.
They have to be filed...
Wait, wait, wait. You...
You're talking divorce?
You broke your vows, Grant.
And I told you,
it's the worst mistake I ever m...
Shit.
No, don't touch it.
I'm sorry.
You're bleeding.
Yeah.
I'll get it.
Do you have any...?
Yeah, yeah. In the bathroom.
Everything all right?
I got to go.
No, not before
you sign these, Grant. I...
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Trevor? Are you asleep?
Uh... I was.
I was dreaming.
About what?
I was walking in the park.
I don't dream much.
I can tell.
Sorry. I shouldn't have woken you.
I'm just used to being able
to have intelligent conversations
24/7.
I thought you weren't
much of a people person.
Who said that?
Ellis.
Oh.
He was right, actually,
but I was talking about the Director.
Lamenting those conversations
are over now.
I talked to the Director a few times.
I talked to it endlessly.
I don't know what to do with myself.
Protocol 5. You can counsel children.
Please, I said intelligent conversation.
So you miss the Director?
Huh.
I think I do.
Interesting.
You miss her, don't you?
I can tell by the way you look at me.
What you see is my realization
that, instead of saving Grace's life,
I made her last few hours terrifying.
I guess I've cheated death for so long,
I thought that I could do the same
for somebody else.
But I've lived long
enough to know better.
Well, try to understand
that the faction had already
corrupted the Director.
The grand plan was in jeopardy.
I understand.
Ladies and gentlemen...
please give a warm welcome
to our speaker for this evening,
Dr. Edwin Calloway!
You can't be serious.
Edwin Calloway?
Do you know how much hatred
and intolerance this guy inspires?
Immigration...
is the true test of a nation,
because the nation needs to be
strong enough to survive it.
Too much accommodation...
This guy is a racist dick.
I am not watching this.
Shh. Just wait.
How many people here today feel like
this country is headed
in the right direction?
And how many feel like
their cultures and traditions
are being respected
by the people they suddenly find
taking their jobs,
dating their daughters?
Well, there's a reason
you all feel this way...
Their cultures
don't respect your culture.
That's a mistake.
All right. Shut it off.
Shut it off!
You did that?
Still not struck by lightning.
Here.
No, thanks. I feel fine.
Yeah, but do you want to feel amazing?
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Protocol 4, right?
What was I saying?
Uh...
that you should sell the apartment?
Right.
Although, I think you got
to say if someone died,
you know, on the disclosure form.
Just...
Re-stain the floors
and nobody needs to know.
See?
That's why you're an FBI doctor.
Who am I kidding?
I can't sell this place.
All my stuff's here.
Oh, man.
I'm really feeling this.
I don't feel anything.
Hey, Mac?
Whatever it is,
try figuring it out on your own.
I just did. Come on, check this out.
Two of our missing people were
just flagged in Sacramento.
Local PD got 'em
for running a red light.
"Dale Miller"
and "Meredith Gilroy."
Looks like they don't
know how to drive either.
I suggested that these two
were just having an affair.
What about the others?
Technically?
No longer under our jurisdiction.
Local PD took it back.
There's hope for you yet.
Hey.
What is this?
I got a present for you.
Wow.
Looks great.
It, uh, it even covers up the...
Yeah, that's kind of the idea.
I got you a present, too.
Yay, safety.
I'm not gonna be needing those.
I'm not staying.
What?
You can continue
the therapy on your own,
as you feel you need it.
But I can already tell
that you're getting better.
W-When did you decide this?
I was told my living here
was always temporary.
You can't just buy me
a goodbye rug and then...
David...
you went through a traumatic experience.
Yeah, I'm feeling another one coming on.
Well, just keep up
with the treatments...
Don't talk to me like I'm a patient.
I'm responsible for what happened.
You said we were safe.
You are, but...
you'll be safer without me.
How is that even possible?
You're the one who saved me.
And look at the result.
I mean, your anxiety
may never completely go away.
I did that to you.
You asked before
if we were intimate, and...
I didn't know what to say
because, I mean...
Well, I don't know,
because I'm an idiot.
What I should have said was, yes.
We were intimate.
I love you, Marcy.
And you love me.
You just don't remember.
You're right.
I don't.
But I do care about you.
Enough to leave.
I understand
this is a difficult time
for both of you.
But the 72-hour
dependency action was filed
and Jeffrey Jr. will be
in the care of the state
until the next assessment.
That's why we're here.
We need to see him.
Not until the next hearing.
I'm sorry.
Trust that he's in a good home.
I'm his father!
I have a right to see my son.
The action was filed
for Jeffrey's safety.
By who?
It was you, wasn't it?
When we received information
regarding the police incident...
Okay. Hold on.
I was cleared of all charges...
I called you, Mr. Conniker,
and we spoke at length,
but I understand why you may
forget the conversation.
We also tried unsuccessfully
to contact you, Ms. Shannon.
So what do we do?
Based on your current behavior
and your history...
I think it might be time to consider
allowing another guardian
to take care of Jeffrey.
Indefinitely.
I'm not gonna give my son
over to some stranger.
Unless things radically change,
that is going to remain
Jeffrey Jr.'s best option.
Philip?
Yeah!
Just one minute!
Who are you?
This is Jenny.
Hi.
Hello.
Philip, can I talk to you for a second?
Did you bring a 21st-er to Ops?
Well, actually, she's a Traveler.
And that's better how?
So I'm gonna go.
Good idea.
Talk to you later?
What's going on?
I'm clean, Marcy.
That's how we met.
The Director sent her to help me.
A synthesized drug
to help me get off heroin.
I need to know
what this is made of.
Naloxone, buprenorphine,
and some other things.
What other things?
I don't care. It works!
My body doesn't hurt when I'm not high.
I get to have a normal life.
There's nothing normal about this!
Why?
Because I met someone?
You have somebody.
Not anymore.
I'm gonna stay here for a while,
until I find my own place.
Of course.
This place is yours, too.
You okay?
I'm fine.
Mr. Holden.
Mr. Doc.
What's the prognosis?
Still a lot of inflammation.
Do you feel anything yet?
Even pins and needles?
I think so.
It's hard to say.
Well... let's, uh, do the test again.
Ow!
Oh, I felt that.
And movement. That is excellent.
Excellent!
- Does this mean...?
- It means there's hope!
Wow.
Thank you so much.
Would you like me to contact your folks?
I-I would like that very much, yes,
because they'll want to thank you, too.
I'll check in again later
before I go today,
but how about one of these, buddy?
All right.
Hope?
There are medical nanites
designed in the future
swimming through your spinal fluid
that I programmed personally,
repairing the damage.
There was never any doubt.
Well, I wanted him to feel good
about the job that they did.
Well, I want them to bring breakfast.
They're half an hour late already,
and I'm starving.
Thank you for saving me, Grace.
You already said that.
Hi.
Come on in.
Carly, what're you doing?
What do you think?
You're not gonna find anything.
I told you,
I stopped drinking. This is for real.
No, Jeff.
This is for show.
And you better not screw it up...
because this is our one chance
to get Jeffrey back.
Don't worry. It's gonna work.
The big question is,
where do I put my, uh, stuff?
By the couch.
Hey, um, you hungry?
I was thinking...
She's not here, is she?
The bitchy little blonde?
"Marcy"
is out looking for an apartment.
That's why I texted.
You seen this?
His followers went nuts on him,
and then, this morning,
he woke up, shot his wife and his kid,
before he killed himself.
- Philip, I know...
- His wife and child
...Are dead and it's our fault.
You mean my fault.
I mean this is fucked up, Jenny!
No. It really isn't.
None of this would've happened
if you hadn't hacked his presentation.
He probably would've
gone on spewing hate
that led to the deaths
of hundreds of people.
Thousands!
You tell me, you're the historian.
It's not up to us.
I didn't tell him
to kill his family.
All I did
was tell the truth.
And his wife and child?
The world is a better place
without Edwin Calloway.
And I'm sorry,
maybe he took some innocent people
down with him,
but I refuse to feel guilty about it.
Yeah, well, the Director's gonna know.
If the Director thought
what we were doing was wrong,
why didn't I get a messenger?
Orders from another team to back off?
Can you look me in the eye and tell me
what I did was not a good thing?
Kat.
Grant, what are you doing here?
You can't just show up here.
Kat. I know.
What?
That you're pregnant.
What? Did you show your badge
to my obstetrician?
No.
Can I come in?
I saw your supplements in the bathroom.
You went through my things?
Yes, I did,
and you can give me shit for that
after we talk.
I am not doing that.
Yes, you are.
Kat!
It happened the night
of your surprise party,
the one time we made love
in the past four months.
I just found out.
I haven't even decided
to go through with it yet.
It was hard enough before,
when I knew how you felt about me.
You do know how I feel about...
And if I decide not to,
I won't have you standing there
judging me.
This is something we wanted
more than anything.
It's my decision to make,
and I'm gonna do it on my own.
You should go.
So, the Tuscan villa,
the Whistler chalet,
and the Caribbean hideaway...
Three stunning properties
all for the price of two
or three normal vacations.
All right.
I can tell you need
a little more motivation.
I'll go see if my manager
can knock a few dollars
off the purchase price.
I'll be right back.
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com