Previously on Travelers...
We've been abducted.
Why don't you show yourself?
- Wilson!
- Sir.
The road ahead's clear.
I'll be following just behind.
Sir, I could use your help up here.
The blast was substantial enough
to put my driver into a coma,
but we both know it should have
been in the megaton range.
I'm not sure what you're accusing me of.
That it never existed
or somehow you hung on to it.
Either way, we are going
to have a conversation.
Amen!
Moses went to the mountain
for 40 days and nights.
Jesus wandered into the desert
for 40 days,
and so too have we journeyed
across this land,
back to the place
where I first had the vision
of our coming rapture.
- Hallelujah!
- Praise be.
It was here at the shores of this river
that you were first baptized
into my flock.
Amen.
My friends...
it is time.
Hallelujah.
The Lord awaits us!
Aah!
Did we all make it?
Good question.
Anybody here feeling out of place?
Feeling not too bad.
Gang's all here.
Well, hallelujah.
That's got to be a record.
Nurse said you woke up at 0300
and tried to pull out
your ventilator tube.
They called me in to reprimand you.
Yes, sir.
Sorry, I was a little out of it.
Anyone told you you've been unconscious
for a number of weeks?
Yeah, it's hard to believe.
It feels like I was in
the driver's seat of that truck
and then...
I was here.
Can you tell me
what happened that night?
To be honest, sir,
you probably saw more of what happened
than I did.
How's that?
You were following behind me,
like you said.
I spotted your headlights at one point.
I was mostly focused
on keeping the vibrations down
and the road ahead.
And then the car came out of nowhere,
and that woman walked out.
What woman?
You didn't see her?
I radioed you
before I stopped the truck.
She was just standing
in the middle of the road.
I told her she didn't want to be there,
and then the next thing I remember,
I was driving again.
Sir, I know it sounds crazy, but...
All right.
That's enough for now.
I'm sure it'll all come
back to you in time.
Get some rest.
Sir, I know what was
in the back of my truck.
How am I still alive?
I'm going to go find out.
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
Hey.
Someone tried to shabby-chic
a classic barley twist.
Client wants me to restore it.
I brought you the last of the coffee.
Oh, I left that for you
for your traveler's mug.
My what?
You know, that insulated mug
your dad used to wander
around the house with?
Oh... uh, no.
I've had my caffeine ration for the day.
I was thinking about
doing fish on the grill tonight.
Don't count on me for dinner.
Oh.
I was hoping,
since you've been working
so much these past few weeks...
I can't. Not tonight.
All right.
So that's a classic barley twist, huh?
Mm.
Imagine someone treating it like that...
not knowing what they have.
It's impressive what you do.
Why do you think that is, Grant?
You take something neglected, and...
something that's rare and beautiful,
and make it whole again.
Oh. Thank you.
I told Forbes that I'd be early.
Bye, Kat.
Bye.
Patricia?
Oh, no, no.
That's not what you said
you were gonna wear.
Well, I've changed my mind!
No, you know I like you
in that black dress.
All right.
Would you mind? Thank you.
You know, my Humanities
teacher, Mr. Warchowski,
says that in 20 years,
equality between the sexes
won't even be an issue.
Warchowski's the gay one, isn't he?
Not an issue.
No parties while I'm
gone, okay, superstar?
I promise.
I'm serious.
I can tell.
You have a good time, Gary.
I'll be in the car.
And stop calling me "Gary,"
for Christ's sakes.
I'm your father.
You looked lovely in that other
dress, by the way.
Oh, it's just easier, honey.
We've got to teach him some time.
Yeah. Thank you.
Okay, so we are gonna be
home by noon tomorrow.
Bye, Mom.
Thank you, sweetheart.
Bye.
All set?
Yep.
What's wrong?
Is everything all right?
Yeah, you know. Parents.
Prevent Helios,
and we prevent
the beginning of the Fall.
That was the Director's calculation
that started this whole thing.
More than any other,
this is the mission objective
that motivated us
to come back to the 21st.
I know you all just went through hell,
and I wish we had answers, but we don't.
So let's just focus
on the mission at hand.
Marcy?
All right. Uh...
Place the business end
against your bicep like so,
and push.
It's important that you receive
the full dosage. Okay?
You'll still smell and taste
the chemical in the air
within the compound, but I promise you,
this will stop your nervous system
from shutting down. Okay?
What?
Nervous about a little pin-prick
after what we've just been through?
I just have a thing with needles.
Funny. Me too.
Speaking of which...
this isn't gonna interfere with...?
No, you're fine. You can go ahead.
Abductors set back his rehab.
Ah.
One last thing.
It was our decision to take
the antimatter back to Delaney.
It's on us
that the location for this
mission had to change,
so one way or the other,
we are seeing this through.
To the end, if necessary.
We know.
And we're good.
Yes, you are.
If I may?
We, the last unbroken remnants...
...Vow to undo
the errors of our ascendants,
to make the Earth whole,
the lost unlost,
at peril of our own birth.
Okay.
It's time.
Could I take this in my glutes,
or does it have to be my arm?
Not a lot of muscle to work with.
Just stick to the instructions, Becky.
You're our best sniper.
Good to go.
_
Dr. Delaney?
That was fast.
I need you to come with us, ma'am.
Come with you?
That I wasn't expecting.
Where are we going?
I'm afraid I can't say.
No.
No?
Look it up. It means "no."
Ma'am, I'm afraid I'm not authorized
to take no for answer.
Oh, for God's sake,
I'm just screwing with you.
Let's go.
Stay here.
The Major doesn't want
anyone to have access
without his knowledge.
Yes, sir.
Look at all the trees.
Can you imagine
ever seeing so many trees?
I've seen maybe 100 birds.
Oh! There's another one
of those Canada Geese!
Keep your eyes on the road.
All my eyes are
looking for is a rest stop.
Oh. We're on a tight schedule.
Yeah, tell my bladder.
These are your guys?
I thought...
Oh, by all means,
complete that sentence.
Who were you expecting?
Take me back to my lab, please.
You just got here.
Then I want to talk to my lawyer.
Dr. Delaney,
you're a military contractor
operating under military law
during a time of contingency operations.
I am a scientist,
and my contract is with
the Van Huizen Corporation.
Consequently, you fall under
the code of military conduct,
and will be held for questioning.
Sergeant?
I'll need to take this for now, ma'am.
Follow me, please.
Don't know why you'd be nervous.
You're in your element.
I'm just thinking about Jeffrey,
about not being able to protect him.
I never expected to get so attached.
You can't think like that.
You got to stay in the present.
Irony intended.
What about your wife?
Does it bother you
that you may never see her again?
That's not really the present, is it?
That's not really an answer.
Mrs. Bloom? Are you ready?
Now, legally, we need to present
this material before we proceed.
I didn't walk in here by mistake.
I'll be right back with your medicine.
Could I have some chocolate, please?
I hear the liquid is bitter.
Of course.
Oh...
Uh...
Is everything okay?
I changed my mind.
Hi. Remember me?
Another leak in 26, apparently.
I don't see that here.
What? They called, like, 40 minutes ago.
Said it was worse than last time.
I brought the whole crew
out on a Saturday.
You mind if I have a look at that?
The notification would
show up right here
if you had one.
Can I get some help here? A little help!
Officer, your security guard passed out!
- I know CPR.
- I don't know what happened!
Get him on the ground!
He j-just clutched his chest
and his knees buckled!
I hope he's not having a heart attack.
All right.
- Just put 'em in the back.
- Three down.
Police and military radio signals
are jammed outside the facility.
Wind direction?
Same as historical record.
Okay, you guys to the charges.
We'll find Delaney,
give her the antitoxin,
and explain what's going on.
That'll be interesting.
Your reinforcements have been delayed.
Bus got stopped at the border.
Expired passport.
Well, no plan survives
contact with the past, right?
3546 in position.
Dr. Delaney?
Hello?
I mean, it is the weekend.
Well, she said she'd be here.
Does it matter?
We don't need her, but I pr...
No, she's not answering her cell.
It just keeps ringing.
We're in position.
All right.
Go when ready.
Copy.
Hope the wind doesn't change!
It won't for hours.
According to the historical
record, it won't,
but you said it yourself,
we're starting to see changes.
These tanks will be ruptured
by the blast anyway,
and the toxic cloud
would be blown toward the city.
A controlled release
allows for a forced evacuation.
Hands in the air!
Move!
This is Morrison. Come in.
Your radio won't work.
On your knees
with your hands on your head!
Listen! You need to run! Now! That way!
I said on your knees
with your hands on your head!
Now! I repeat, this is Morrison.
And I repeat, your radio will not work.
Five seconds.
Please, kid! Run!
You need to run! Go! Go!
Shut up!
Hands on your head! Last warning!
I'm so sorry.
He's not a Van Huizen employee.
No, he's not.
Boss, we initiated
the controlled release.
The alarm should go any second now.
I regret to report one casualty.
Understood.
I need you back in building 26 now.
We got another problem.
Attention, this is an air quality alert.
All personnel evacuate immediately
or report
to your designated refuge area.
Keep moving! Come on, let's go!
Okay! Keep moving! Keep moving!
Let's go, let's go!
...all personnel evacuate immediately
or report
to your designated refuge area.
Keep the change, Omar,
and head east as fast as you can.
You're late, ma'am.
Did you know that older people
have a hard time getting
cabs in the city
because apparently we tip like shit?
My new friend taught me that.
Ow! Ohh.
Attention, this is an air quality alert.
All personnel...
Traveler 3277?
Yeah. Park the vehicles near the leak
in case a television crew
is stupid enough to try to get a shot.
And then get up on the roof.
It's on its way.
Okay. Got it.
The device hasn't arrived yet?
Well, it's ten minutes out.
Well, then, I'm not late yet, am I?
How far of a walk is it?
Can we get the Engineer transport?
Walk with me, if we've got the time.
I need the exercise.
It's a very simple question, Doctor.
What happened to the antimatter?
If this is an interrogation
fantasy you're living out...
Hardly.
Or worse, your way
of getting me to confess
that I failed again...
This is what it is.
You can expect charges
of mutiny, sedition,
aiding the enemy, and espionage,
and each one carries the death penalty.
I already told you what happened!
The antimatter we actually created
amounted to only a fraction
of what we thought.
I think you sold it!
What? To who?
Russians. North Korea.
Any number of foreign powers.
Wow. You're right.
And it didn't even take
you long to figure out.
First...
I snuck the material out in my purse.
I didn't say I knew how you did it.
I just know you did it.
Major Gleason,
I didn't know how big an idiot you were.
I just knew you were an idiot.
She put a biometric
lock on the material.
Retinal scan. Delaney's.
That's a tough hack.
I guess she didn't trust us.
No, I told her to keep it safe, but...
Not safe from us.
Texted her a heads-up
yesterday and this morning.
Can't reach her.
Do you think she's been taken
somewhere against her will?
That's been goin' around.
That casualty that I reported
a few minutes ago
wasn't a Van Huizen employee.
Wasn't in uniform,
but I'm pretty sure he was military.
I'll look for her.
I'll try and break this lock.
I'm Traveler 117.
The Director says hello.
Welcome to the 21st, Engineer.
Call me Bloom.
It's wonderful to see you again.
Ahh... You too, kid.
How are you coping
with your situation, dear?
Oh, I'm fine, thank you, ma'am.
Uh, it is an honor
to meet you in person.
Oh, please... the honor's mine.
You do know you guys are already famous
where I just came from?
Really?
Not in a good way.
Oh.
There's been a lot of arguments
among the project team over you.
I should know.
I've argued on both sides.
Boy, they ever give you a hard time...
Remind me not to ever
get on your bad side.
Wait! You know who abducted my team?
Wasn't anyone on my team.
They were tortured for days!
I know what happened, dear.
I'm from the future.
I'm sure it was terrible,
but the point is, you found them!
Well, we found them.
Not that that matters anymore anyway.
This is the big day.
If this works...
we're done.
If this works, we save
tens of millions of lives.
Sure we do,
but you're forgetting the oath
you took before you came.
"At peril of our own birth."
The handsome boy gets it.
Uh...
I'm sorry, I don't.
They're so cute when they're young.
Everything up to now,
all these missions,
they've been preparations,
fine-tuning for this moment.
Not that the other work wasn't important
or didn't matter, but...
If we successfully
deflect asteroid Helios 685,
we alter the course of humanity
so profoundly
it's highly probable
that the time we come from,
everything between then and now,
the plagues, the shortages, the wars,
none of that will happen.
Which means it's also
highly probable that...
neither will we.
near the Van Huizen research facility
as a precaution.
While close exposure
is considered fatal,
civic authorities are confident
the toxic chemical leak
will dissipate harmlessly...
We shouldn't have stopped
to take a picture of that dog.
It was a bear,
and it took all of 30 seconds.
It was that damn border crossing.
...but as a precaution,
city residents...
This is Carly. The device has arrived,
and it's being lowered into position.
How's the perimeter looking?
Non-traveler responders keep showing up,
and we keep telling them to leave.
Sooner or later, someone's not
gonna take no for an answer.
I could use those reinforcements.
Well, just keep saying no, Carly.
I don't know what else to tell you.
Copy.
Laser's here. I'm here.
All we need now is access
to the antimatter.
And there's no way to bypass the scan?
Well, Philip's gonna
run a software hack,
but Delaney did an excellent job.
We may be stuck.
Imagine why you're famous.
This isn't really a problem.
With or without Delaney,
we can trigger containment failure
by shutting off its power supply.
Do it that way, and we risk
an asymmetrical collapse
of the magnetic bottle.
Now, would you please stop improvising
for one damn minute?
Power shut-off has always
been the contingency.
An X-ray laser works
by translating
a very specific amount of energy
from an antimatter or nuclear explosion
into a coherent beam of X-rays.
Too much, and you overload the laser.
Too little,
and it won't deflect the target.
This is my swan song, MacLaren.
I would like to get it right,
and I would like to be the one
who turns the key.
I do not care to wing this!
How's your search going?
I just found a car on security logs
arriving at the facility
early this morning
and leaving five minutes after.
I can't identify the occupants,
but I do have a plate.
Good. Locate that car.
We've still got time to get her here.
At least find her eye.
That's all we really need.
I'll be checking
my science project on the roof
if anybody needs me.
She's been like that
for a hundred years.
Don't take it personally.
Yeah.
Private Wilson
suffered third-degree burns
over 20% of his body.
He spent the last several weeks
in a coma.
Whoever intercepted his truck
made it look like containment failed
and then there was an explosion.
How did you let that happen?
Where were you during all this?
Wilson came out of his coma
in the middle of the night,
and I spoke to him.
He told me a woman stopped him
in the middle of the road,
"just standing there."
Damn it.
You just keep getting it right.
The second you left,
I took off in my invisible helicopter.
This is not funny!
If you actually listen to yourself,
it's hilarious!
Your own piece-of-shit
portable containment unit
weighed a couple tons,
and needed a Mack truck
to pull it around.
How the hell would I...?
There are plenty of foreign powers
capable of engineering this, Doctor!
Why would I have waited
until you took it from me
to sell it if I already had it?
A few minutes ago,
you were sticking to your story
that it never existed.
Hey, David, it's me.
Uh, guess it's my turn
to leave you a goofy message.
Um... I just know
how stressed out you get
when you don't hear from me,
so I... wanted to let you know
that I might be away for a while,
and maybe even relocated.
I just don't want you
wondering or worrying
if you don't hear from me.
You know, if it happens,
I mean, I don't know for sure
that it will,
but if it does,
I just want to thank you
for always being there for me
when I really needed someone.
You know, in another time
or another life, right?
Okay, uh...
Goodbye, David.
I spent my life designing that thing.
Now I'm just gonna blow it up.
How's that for the circle of life?
- Oh!
- Are you feeling ill?
My host was dying of cancer.
Whatever pain medication she was on...
I'll go grab you something.
No. Wait.
Are you serious?
One of the best pain
meds there ever was.
I mean, she's... she's not wrong.
The firing window
is 2 hours, 4 minutes,
and 11 seconds away.
All I got to do is turn a key.
I'd rather not do it in pain.
I'll check inside.
Oh. I'm good.
Trev?
What happened?
Progress?
I think my hacking attempts
triggered a silent alarm.
It's pinging to a remote I.P.
Can you I.D. the location?
Hold that thought.
Sir!
It was in her bag.
What is this?
What does this mean?
Hello!
I'll take Marcy.
You send me the coordinates en route!
It means that your people are in my lab
trying to break into
the containment unit,
and they don't know
what they're frigging doing.
The only guy I've got there
couldn't break into his own lunchbox.
Tell me who that is!
Where are you going?
Philip found Delaney.
The Engineer wants her here.
We can't hold them off much longer.
We just need an hour or so.
Give us a head start,
then blow the second charge.
All right. Go get her.
Trevor, blow the main.
Copy.
All right.
Okay, this is a deadly,
toxic gas, people.
Get in your vehicles
and get out of here now!
Go!
Ever get the feeling
you're heading in the wrong direction?
Well, at least we can say we saw a dog.
It was a bear!
It was a beautiful living thing...
out in the world.
Excuse me, Major.
There's a Special Agent from the FBI
who wants to talk.
Tell him I'm busy.
Not to you, sir. To her.
Special Agent...?
MacLaren, FBI.
You're Major...?
Gleason.
You must be who triggered
Delaney's little alarm.
Actually, the Doctor is part
of an ongoing investigation
that the Bureau has
had underway for months,
so you can imagine our surprise
when you show up out of nowhere
and take her to wherever
the hell this is.
This place...
Obviously not
an official military facility,
which is the only place
you'd have any sort of jurisdiction
or the right to question anybody,
let alone Delaney.
All right, so tell me,
who's she selling to?
Selling to?
What're you doing? Major...
- I have good reason to Sus...
- This is not your job.
It is, however, my job.
Do you understand that?
You know what?
I've had enough of this conversation.
Let me see her right now,
before I call your superiors
and tell them you've been freelancing
as a part-time private detective.
I give up. Where is she?
Lock down the building.
Find her!
Gleason, you gotta be kidding me!
My men will find her!
No! They will stand down
and stay out of this!
What the hell is wrong with you?
Who knows what damage you've done.
I've released
all non-essential personnel.
Where are my reinforcements?
They should be there any minute.
Can I get up now?
What's going...
Ow! What the hell is that?
It's an antitoxin
for the chemical leak at Van Huizen.
What chemical leak?
Well, that's part
of a longer conversation.
You found my biometric lock.
Uh-huh. And we're gonna
need you to unlock it.
Finally.
You're late!
Long drive.
You know where you need to go?
Restroom.
Then, yeah, we know
what we're here to do.
Let's go.
...while close
exposure could be fatal...
Sir? You should see this.
...Civic authorities are confident
the toxic chemical leak
will dissipate harmlessly
and soon be under control.
We haven't heard from Morrison?
I can't reach him either.
...clearing the cloud away
from densely populated areas...
Can you guys be somewhere else
for a few minutes?
You're fine. Go back to work.
Oh, you son of a bitch.
I need the squad fully armed
and ready to go right now.
All right, leave two on that bus,
you stay down here.
The rest of your squad
over on that roof.
Yours, over there.
That'll place any attacking force
in a field of fire between you, okay?
Protocol 3 hasn't been waived.
They won't know about Protocol 3.
They're gonna figure
it out pretty quick.
Let me worry about that.
Who's your best sniper?
Uh, Becky.
Becky...
You're with me.
What the hell is that thing?
That's also part
of a longer conversation.
Cutting it close.
There's plenty of time.
I wish.
Me too.
Hi.
Hello.
I heard you the first time! No!
For Christ's sakes,
someone knock the woman out,
point her eye at the damn thing,
and let's get on with it!
And you are?
The Engineer who designed
that thing on your roof.
Call me Bloom.
What is that thing?
Tell her.
It's an X-ray laser.
And we're back to no.
Look! Travelers like ourselves
have been building and
assembling components for this
for over a year.
To do what with it?
There's an asteroid
on a collision course with Earth
called "Helios 685."
It hasn't been detected yet,
but when it strikes the Atlantic Ocean
in 18 months' time,
the wave will knock out
most of the Eastern Seaboard,
resulting in environmental effects,
shortages, and wars
from which there will be no recovery.
How the hell could you
possibly know all of this?
We're from the future.
Just came from there myself.
I don't recommend it.
Why wasn't this asteroid detected?
Helios will be detected
two months from now,
but, by then, it's too late.
If my X-ray laser is fired
precisely 12 minutes from now,
the beam will strike Helios
and deflect it by .07 degrees.
Enough to miss the Earth in 18 months.
A near-miss
that will hopefully
bring the nations of the world together,
and make them realize what
the hell they've got to lose.
You've seen the laser.
You know damn well
the 21st century has nothing like it.
To power it,
you need the energy release
of a matter-antimatter detonation.
The blast radius could be miles wide.
People will die, yes.
Certainly everyone here,
but the laser will translate
most of that energy
into the beam.
Doctor, we would rather
do this with your help...
but we are doing this.
By all means, dear, take your time.
I'm going to exact revenge
on the destruction of the Cetan.
They're coming.
Fire teams, stand by.
A full squad just entered the compound.
We're close, Carly.
You need to hold them back.
Hold who back?
Gleason and his men.
You're up, Doctor.
Stand by.
Now!
Take cover!
Yes, Major! Copy that!
You focus on the officer.
Protocol 3 is enforced.
Good day, Dr. Delaney.
They're not shooting to kill!
Let's go, boys! Take 'em down!
Move, move, move!
You should know
I'm hardest on people
I think have the most potential.
Armed.
Okay. We're armed.
Take Dr. Delaney with you.
The future could use her.
We're not going anywhere. We're
staying till this is done.
If you hadn't brought Delaney here,
I be forced to agree with you,
but there's just time to get her
to minimum safe distance.
The soldiers will eventually
make it inside.
Then there'll be no getting out of here,
and it'll be in the hands
of the Director.
Now do you get it?
Request permission to use deadly force!
Negative, we're coming
out the south door.
Have your teams give cover fire
and meet us on the way.
Orders from the Engineer.
We've got to get Delaney
to safe distance.
Go, go, go, go, go!
Move it! Move it!
I got the door!
Go, go, go, go!
It's medicinal...
I swear.
Cover fire, now!
Carly, come on!
Everybody, get down!
Step away!
I'd tell you to run...
but with less than 87 seconds to go,
we're past that now.
Stop!
- I guess it's too much to ask...
- Stand down! that is an order!
That I be the one
who turns the key when...
Make sure she's dead.
Aah!
Stop!
What are you doing? Soldier!
Soldier, stop! That is an order!
Aah!
Stop! What are you doing?
Soldier!
Stand down! Stop, sir!
Sergeant! No! Stand down!
No. No!
Aah! Aah!
That's time.
Eyes closed!
How will we know if it worked?
I'm not sure it did.
Why?
Because we're all still here.
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com