Previously on Travelers.
Trading one addiction
for another never works.
Are you prepared to do the work?
I have no intention
of playing football again.
- What?
- Trevor!
Imagine someone treating it like that,
not knowing what they have.
This is the mission objective
that motivated us
to come back to the 21st.
Armed.
We are seeing this through,
to the end, if necessary.
How will we know if it worked?
I'm not sure it did.
We're all still here.
Bought something to toast with.
Figured we should celebrate
21st-century style.
The 21st century doesn't
even know we saved them.
Well, there'd be a lot of this
if they did.
You know, a lot of
people died. We should...
Because of them, a hell of a lot
more people are gonna live.
91,462,000 more.
It worked.
In 18 months, Helios is gonna miss.
Isn't that worth taking a moment?
Yeah.
Yeah, sure. I just...
I never thought past the mission.
You know?
I mean, the authorities can call it
a chemical explosion all they want,
but the Russians, the Chinese,
they've got satellites.
They're gonna know it was
an antimatter detonation.
T-This could end up
in the same arms race that
we came here to prevent in the...
Boss...
take the win.
All right. Ahem.
Anybody else's arm killing them?
I told you
the inoculation might
have some side effects.
How about a toast?
You know I'm not big
on speeches, so, um...
May you all live long lives.
Cheers.
Prost, salut, viva, bud'mo, skol.
L'Chaim!
Oh, God.
Oh, that's just wrong.
Ugh.
I'm sorry, guys.
I only had $20 on me.
I really...
And when you say
"may you all have long lives,"
that kinda sounds like there
won't be any more missions.
Well, we may have done
what we came here to do...
created a future
where we're no longer needed.
All we have to do is...
live out our lives.
These lives, I mean.
Protocol 5.
Indefinitely.
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
Afternoon.
Come with me.
What's up?
This has always been solid, right?
Between me and you.
Are you breaking up with me?
No, I'm serious, man, I'm in trouble.
What kind of trouble?
What you got on this afternoon?
More of that.
Not anymore. I need your help.
Well, tell me what's going on!
You've been dropping off the grid
left and right lately,
and I haven't asked one single question.
Now, you're my partner, right?
And I trust you.
Do you trust me?
Of course I do.
All right. Let's go.
_
It's okay. It's okay.
I know. I know.
It's okay.
I really don't know
how you stand this either.
_
None of this fits.
I think I'm getting fat.
I don't think you understand
the meaning of the word.
Well, either I'm getting fat
or my boobs got bigger.
Can you come in here a sec?
Actually, no, I don't
think that's a good idea.
I'm not supposed to...
Come in here. I need your help.
Rene, the lady's right there,
- and she could...
- Okay.
Look at all this stuff.
I've got so much good shit.
Look at this. Open back.
Mm-hmm.
And these pants. Aren't they perfect?
Yeah, they're really pants.
'Kay. Open your coat.
- What?
- We got to go.
Open your coat!
I can't fit this all in my purse.
You don't actually, um,
want to steal all this stuff?
Well, not all of it.
Rene, don't.
Come on! You love this stuff!
Help me.
Do you have these in a size 13?
It's hard for me to find good shoes.
I really like these kicks.
Do you think you could
maybe take a look,
like, in the back?
In the back. Sure.
I thought this stuff got you hot.
Come on. It gets me hot.
Come on, look, Rene,
I'm gonna have to admit a bit of
confusion at this point, okay?
Hey! That's illegal!
So's that.
- Hey!
- Hey! Wait!
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa!
The Director's gonna
make you pay for this.
Excuse me?
You're paying for what they stole.
Aw, shit.
Hey, Phil. Phil?
Hey, Phil.
Come on, man. Don't make me chase you.
What's up?
I thought you were off of that shit.
What am I, getting you
the Percs just for show?
What do you want, Ray?
Why don't you let me take you home?
Come on, man.
I'm going for a walk.
Yeah. I can see that.
Don't have any bets for you today.
Forget about the bet.
You're scaring the children.
Boo.
Sorry.
Come on, let's go.
Walt, what are we doing?
- What is this?
- Just keep it reined in.
These guys don't mess around.
Stop where you are!
Eyes front!
Put the bag down! Weapons down!
Put 'em on the ground!
Okay, we're doing it!
Seriously?
It's gonna be all right.
Get your hands in the air.
Above your head!
Eyes front!
Sorry about that, Mac.
Let's go.
Surprise!
Easy there.
You son of a bitch.
You've got some new moves, Mac.
Jesus, man, I could've broken something.
Yeah, I'm fine.
You still got no chill, man.
Congratulations, partner.
Oh, and thanks for the assist
with the propane.
15 years and they can
still surprise you?
Congratulations.
I swore to myself
I would never eat this shit again.
Well... the body needs fuel, man.
When was the last time
you had like a proper meal?
All I ever see you eat
is Coke and Twinkies.
When did you start
caring about my health?
You see, that's your
problem, right there.
Probably all you've ever had
is junkies for friends, right?
You never had anyone
just lookin' out for you
'cause they care.
You only care because I give you bets.
Yeah, your special abilities,
they play a fundamental part
in our relationship,
that's for sure.
But I'm buying you lunch
'cause I'm a goddamn humanitarian.
Hey, Marce?
In here.
Hey, I couldn't remember
if you liked the green apples
or the red apples, so I just...
Jesus Christ.
What?
What the hell are you doing?
Uh, just a minor surgery.
Nothing serious.
What have you done to yourself?
I've installed a vagus nerve stimulator
in order to minimize my seizures.
Normal people don't
operate on themselves, Marcy.
The Terminator, maybe, but that's it.
This is minimally invasive.
Don't worry, I'll clean up the mess.
It's not about the mess.
The fact that you would
do something like this alone
is insane.
Well, you would've made me
go to the hospital.
Yes! Surgery?
Yes! I mean, look at this place!
It's just a little bit of blood.
No, it's not.
No, it's not! This...
This is a great deal of blood!
How... How do you not...
How do you not recognize this?
I mean...
Oh, come on! I can't...
I can't keep doing this.
Doing what?
Pretending that this is normal.
And it's not just this, it's everything.
I mean, it's... it's the
staying out late all night
without telling me where you are,
it's CPR during phone conversations,
it's the... how about
the phone message saying
that you might be relocating?
"Another time, another life"... what...
And please stop kissing me
to just to shut me up.
That's not fair.
Do you want me to leave?
No.
No. It's... do you know what it is?
Stop trying to do everything alone.
Let me in.
Let me help you with the battle.
Because I can't help but think
that whatever it is you're doing...
it's a battle.
Would you have helped me with this?
Oh, God, no. No.
But...
I am here for you
for anything and everything
non-surgical.
Okay, maybe, like,
minor surgery, like...
Band-Aids.
I can do Band-Aids.
All right, get him up here.
Come on, let's go.
Yeah, get his jacket.
No...
Take your jacket off.
Come on, everyone,
let's hear it for him!
Why?
Why are you taking my jacket?
It's fine. You'll be fine.
Special Agent Grant MacLaren.
In recognition of your many years
of dedication to this Bureau,
the men and women of this division
would like to present you with...
this token
of our appreciation.
Here's to 15 years, bruh.
Come on! Hold it up.
- What are you doing?
- No, no, no, no. Come on.
Here we go.
Yo, Kat, take a picture.
Yeah. Of course.
I can't get in.
Just swipe up.
Did you... Did you change it?
All right. Let's do this.
Big smiles! Come on, man.
Hey. It's okay.
We're just gonna play it
extra safe today, okay? Okay?
Shit.
Hey, Walt.
Hey, sweetheart. How are you?
Mm. Good.
Thanks so much for
putting this together for him.
It means a lot.
Yeah, he's all right.
So how are things?
You look good. Everything's fine now?
Yeah, unless you know something I don't.
Uh, no, it's just that Mac told me
that he took you
to the doctor's the other day.
You know what? It's none of my business.
I never should've said anything.
No, no, no, it's fine.
It wasn't anything serious.
Well, I'm glad to hear it.
Yeah, everything's good.
We're good.
- Should I top you up?
- Uh, yes, please.
There you go. I'm really sorry.
Hey! What the hell was that in there?
Well, I don't know, dawg, you tell me,
because you really botched it in there!
- I did?
- Yeah!
Was I getting you all worked up?
No! It was... It was a terrible plan.
No, no, it wasn't a terrible plan!
- Yeah! It was!
- It's your plan.
No, it wasn't my plan!
It's your plan, Trevor!
We've done it 10 times!
All right? You're killing
me out here, man.
You are so off your game today.
What are these?
Benzos. Your favorite.
This is my mother's medication.
Trevor.
How did you get this?
Are you kidding? Man, don't even.
Are you stealing from my family?
You told me to!
No, I didn't tell you to!
Look, man...
just give me the pills.
No, I'm not giving you the pills.
Just be fair and give me
the pills, all right?
I gave you the last stash!
We had a deal, bitch!
Come on, chill out, guys.
Come on, Trevor.
Your head is still healing.
I'm not in any danger.
No, you're right.
Just give me back the pills,
and you won't be.
Walk away.
Trevor!
Don't.
Yeah, screw you!
What?
Are you okay?
Wha...?
Okay, just sit back.
Close your eyes.
What is this even supposed to do?
This... is connected
to a nerve in your head.
No, it's not.
You know reflexology's
not real medicine.
Okay. Next you're going to tell me
that the hip bone's
not connected to the leg bone.
It isn't.
All right, you know what? I'm j...
I'm trying to help you relax,
so just play along.
Okay. Close your eyes.
What happened here?
Uh, it's nothing.
It's just a reaction from an injection.
An injection of...?
An antitoxin.
An antitoxin for...?
Marcy...
you're seeing things.
What do you mean?
The psychotropic effects
of the antitoxins.
You've been experiencing
them all day, kiddo.
An antitoxin for what?
Sorry, I shouldn't have said anything.
I'm just...
I'm just experiencing some side effects.
Did you have anything
to do with that huge explosion
at Van Huizen?
You know about that?
Well, it was the first mushroom cloud
we've had in the area
in what seems like forever.
It was all over the news.
They said it was
a combination of spilt chemicals
that accidentally combined with...
I mean, why am I telling you?
You were there.
They did say it was just
an accident, though.
They evacuated the area
in time, and no one was hurt.
Marcy.
Marce?
Marcy?
Marcy, look at me.
Hey, MacLaren. Mac. Mac.
We're talking about the time
that we had to evac
out of the south shelter.
Yeah. The emergency alarm goes off,
reveille bell's ringing bloody murder...
People screaming...
...And who comes walking in but 3468...
"Shit!
That warrant was in that other coat!"
There you are, man.
Where's your drink at?
No, no, I've had enough.
Don't quit on me now, Mac.
You'll need courage for your speech.
Nobody wants to hear me talk.
Who wants to hear Mac's speech?
No! Shh!
I got to take a piss. I'll be back.
Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
Just have some Scotch.
Isn't this a great party, people?
You know what you need?
Something to love.
It ain't good for a guy
to sit around that garage all day...
you know, no sunshine, no companionship,
no girlfriend.
You got a boyfriend?
It's not a priority either way.
What about a pet?
You need something to talk to
other than your computer or yourself.
I've heard dog is a man's best friend.
A puppy? Yeah, right.
That's much better!
Puppy's a lot of commitment, Phil.
It takes a whole lot of effort.
You got to pick up their shit.
They bark all the time.
You can't travel anywhere.
A professional gambler like you,
you got to be able to pick up
and fly to Vegas at any time, right?
Right?
Thanks, Ray. She's cute.
You're welcome. Look at her.
All right.
There's one more place
I want to take ya.
You okay?
Yeah. I think so.
Come on, I thought you were gonna
kick that guy's ass.
Yeah, well, look, Rene,
I'm sorry if who I am
doesn't work for you anymore, okay?
No, I like who you are.
To be honest...
I was never really
into that other stuff anyways.
I kind of just played along.
Really?
True story.
Okay, come on, let me
show you something.
Come with me.
I think you're gonna like this.
I know there's a camera here somewhere.
Don't worry.
I won't let them hurt you. Okay?
No. It was a complete waste of time.
I'm gonna have to cut it all out again.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no. Come on.
Slow down. Take a breath.
I am so tired.
I know.
You really want to help me?
Anything.
Not anything. You said no surgery.
Yeah, well, I'm not gonna
operate on you.
I mean, that's where
I draw the line. Sorry.
It's more of a procedure.
A simple one.
Well, see, now, how simple?
Because you said the last one was minor.
You can do this.
I know you can.
I wanted to ask you for a while,
but I was afraid that you'd say no.
Okay.
What do you want me to do?
I know that you're staring at me.
How?
Because I'm highly trained.
How do you do that?
Clear your mind?
Most of the time, it's easy.
But today I'm finding
it a bit difficult.
Am I distracting you?
A lot's changed the last little while.
What? Talk to me.
I thought my life had purpose.
And then, one day,
I woke up
almost surprised to be alive,
and...
I found out that my purpose was gone.
Everything that I've been doing...
has been focused on this one mission.
And now that there's no mission...
I'm just living a stranger's life.
It must be hard
not to be able to play football...
But...
just so you know...
I was never with you
'cause you were
some superstar quarterback.
Really?
No.
It was the size of your dick.
I'm kidding.
- Well...
- I'm kidding.
But honestly...
even if that's not
your mission anymore...
You're still gonna be someone great.
There's the 15-year man!
- Oh, come on.
- Hey!
Now, I was pretty
reluctant to do any of this,
because, let's be honest,
he's a pretty lousy partner,
but enough about his squash game.
Let's hear it for our colleague
and our friend,
Special Agent Grant MacLaren.
Yeah!
Thanks a lot.
Uh, thanks, partner.
Um, it's a great afternoon.
Isn't it?
A lot of familiar faces here.
I can't tell you how strange
it is to know that...
I'll never see any of you again.
Uh...
until Monday, uh, I mean, Monday...
Um, so many stories from our past...
So many I can't talk about.
Teamwork...
is everything, right?
Uh...
The people you work with...
they become your family.
A shared history, a shared mission...
that's... that's what you hold onto.
I, and-and my actual family,
my-my wife, Kathryn. Uh...
She-She holds me up.
Probably literally tonight.
Jesus.
- Ah, ah, no, no. Oi.
- Come on! Come on!
All right.
15 more years!
Woo!
Thanks.
Hey, maybe you should drive home.
Let's go.
Get in here!
Just...
What's going on?
Why don't you tell us?
I, uh...
Trevor, why did you steal my medication?
I didn't steal your medication.
Well, it sure as hell didn't get
up and walk away on its own!
Okay, okay!
Look, Nick stole it.
Nick? What the hell was
Nick doing in our bathroom?
He was under the mistaken impression
that I wanted him to take it.
Jesus! What are you doing?
You're lying, you're stealing,
and now you're doing drugs?
No, I'm not doing drugs.
Well, you look you're high right now!
I'm not high. I...
Take responsibility!
Be a man, for Christ's sake!
What? Like you, Gary? That kinda man?
I told you the truth.
Here's your medication.
Trevor!
L3...
L4...
L5. Right there.
Right there, between L4 and L5.
This is insane.
I can't do this without you.
You've already frozen the site.
It won't hurt as much as you think.
Okay, okay...
Oh, God, I'm sorry.
You're going good.
You're doing good. Keep going.
Oh, God, I... I felt a pop.
I'm sorry. Something popped.
No, it's good. Keep going. Okay.
Yeah?
Okay.
Really?
How much of this goes in?
That's good.
Okay.
Oh, God, it's starting to leak.
You're doing really good. Keep going.
Not really.
I'm kind of fainting over here.
Done?
These used to be your favorite.
Okay.
Oh, shit.
Okay... I need to start
analyzing the C.S.F.
Oh, no. No. Not now. Not now.
Rest.
Just... Just rest.
It's, uh...
pretend-doctor's orders.
Looks clean.
What do you want?
Is this the residence of Ms. Shannon?
Who wants to know?
I'm Jacqueline Peele
with Child Protective Services.
Ms. Shannon,
it would be much better
if we had this conversation inside.
Ms. Shannon, I just have...
- Why are you here?
- ...a few questions for you.
I'm just here responding
to some concerns
that were raised about
Jeffrey's situation here.
Where is this coming from?
Your husband.
Jeff is not my husband.
He's the father,
and we're obligated to follow up.
What're you writing?
Just my observations.
Ms. Shannon, are you
in some kind of trouble?
Who are you, really?
I beg your pardon?
Who sent you?
Who are they?
What do they want from me?
I've already told you, I'm with
Child Protective Services.
Do you have a warrant to be here?
A court order of some kind?
No. This is, uh, an informal meeting,
but if you want me to leave...
Yes. I do.
Now.
All right.
I will have to make a note
that you refused this initial...
- Get out.
- ...Meeting, Ms. Shannon.
Walt seems good.
Yeah, he's a machine.
He said
that you've been paying
more attention to me lately.
Well, that's not so bad, is it?
It's not true.
What's not true?
He said you left work early
to take me to an appointment?
I did?
No, Grant, you didn't.
So what were you really doing?
W-When?
What were you really doing when you were
supposed to be taking me to the doctor?
I'm not an idiot, Grant.
I've noticed the changes.
The diet,
locking me out of your cell phone.
Something's going on.
Tell me. Tell me.
I'm not who you think...
What?
You're not what? Tell me!
I'm in love with you.
I always have been.
No. Stay.
I'm Colin, and I'm an addict.
Hi, Colin.
We'd like to welcome a newcomer.
Would you please introduce yourself?
The kid's shy.
That's okay.
Then why don't you start?
I admitted
I was powerless over my addiction.
I give over my will and my life
to the Director.
And I pray for the knowledge
of the Director's will for me...
and the power to carry it out.
The Director doesn't know.
Thank you, Traveler 7294.
I'm Traveler 3326.
I've been in the 21st century
for five weeks now,
and I'm so fricking tired,
I just wanna lie down and get high.
The other day, we saved the world.
Now what do I do?
I was selected and trained
to remember everything.
Everything...
dates, coordinates,
candidates, people.
Every death. Every single one.
But I can't even remember my own face...
the face I was born with
hundreds of years from now.
But I guess that's okay.
Because that's who I am now...
and I'd better get used to it, right?
I'm Philip,
and I'm from the future.
Go ahead and say it loud, kid.
That's all you got to do.
Makes a difference.
My name is Philip,
and I'm a heroin addict.
Hi, Philip.
_
You do some redecorating?
What happened to
Protocol 5 indefinitely?
Can't Trevor and Philip be friends?
You're at least a hundred years
older than me.
Well, I'm young at heart.
Not so much.
Look, I need a couch to crash on.
That I believe.
Mi casa es su casa.
Thank you.
It's been a weird day.
You have any side effects
from the antitoxin?
Hallucinations? Voices?
Yeah.
Happens to me all the time, actually.
Really?
Yeah.
That's some shit you deal with.
I think it's starting to wear off.
Yeah. Me too.
What is it?
We just received a new mission.
We're back on.
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com