Previously on Travelers.
This should cover
all the benefits that I received
under David's care.
Well, that's blackmail.
I am happy to share you
with your work, babe.
I always have been.
As long as that's all
I'm competing with.
He believes you've been cheating.
- What?
- I've convinced him
to allow you
one more crack at the midterm
under both of our supervision tomorrow.
Is this true, Ms. Shannon?
Have you assaulted Mr. Conniker?
Forget Protocol 3.
I want to kill that man.
I'm not an idiot, Grant.
I've noticed the changes.
Just a sec, hon.
Sure, slacker.
No, really, I got to take this.
Hayes.
Yeah.
Oh, relax.
Manning likes to bluster about ethics
and the environment,
but he'll fold as always.
Besides, this conference
is just a formality.
Once I put the motion through,
it's through.
That pipeline will move ahead
on schedule.
No! No, no, no, no.
We'll be out of that conference by noon
and still make our tee time.
You watch.
God.
I'm sweating like a pig here.
This exercise is gonna kill me.
Oh, honey...
don't be silly.
That isn't gonna be what kills you.
Aah!
Help!
Help! Somebody, help!
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
Mm... that smells good.
Fine grind, organic.
I know it sounds snobby,
but you just wait...
tastes even snobbier.
Thank you.
No problem.
- Everything okay?
- Yeah.
No. Um... It's just...
What?
I don't think I can do this anymore.
Do what?
This, you...
staying here with me.
No, you don't need to worry.
I talked to your boss.
It's not about my job, Marcy.
It's... so, you talked to my... boss?
Uh, yeah, it's settled.
What were you going to say?
This pretending
to be something that we're not...
I keep saying that it's platonic, but...
if I'm being honest with myself...
Oh...
It's okay.
I-I think maybe...
it's best if you found your own place.
Oh.
Um...
I-I didn't realize...
The last thing I want is to upset you.
You should go to work.
And... don't worry about me.
I'll find a place tonight.
I mean, it doesn't...
ahem... have to be tonight.
It's fine.
I understand.
Do you?
Don't leave tonight,
'cause I got dinner...
David.
It is okay.
Just, um... you should go to work.
Excuse me.
- Do you mind?
- Yeah, I do.
I mind what's going on
between you and Carly.
Carly?
Mm. Don't pretend you don't know.
That'll just piss me off.
Right.
And we all know what you do
when you get pissed off,
don't we?
I would not suggest
you try that with me.
Definitely not here.
Okay.
I'll talk to you man to man, all right?
Carly and I had a fight,
we separated,
you had some fun with her...
"Fun with her"?
- I seen you around, all right?
- If you're implying that Carly and I...
I'm just here to tell you
that she's the mother of my child,
and I'm trying to get
my family back together.
But if you're in my way...
Actually, you're in my way.
If you wouldn't mind pressing "down."
Do you think that this is funny?
No, I think it's pathetic.
I've interviewed Carly Shannon...
"Interviewed"?
...On official business, yes,
during which time
the bruises on her arms
and her forehead were pretty
goddamned unmistakable.
Okay, accidents happen, man.
Not anymore they don't.
Does your wife know
that Carly's half your age?
You know, if you were smart...
you'd realize that Carly's
not going to put up
with an abusive, alcoholic,
loser beat cop anymore,
and you'd move on.
I'll wait for the next one.
You don't have your GED?
Uh, um... that should
come through this week.
I, uh, did the test already.
Just waiting on the papers, Mr. Donald.
Uh, "Hank." Call me Hank.
So, do you have
any experience in landscaping?
No, but I'm a fast learner.
Um, okay, this question
is not intended to be in any way sexist,
but it is a requirement
of this workplace,
so don't be offended.
What?
Can you lift that bag?
Where would you like it?
Back on the pile's good.
All right.
Come on in tomorrow.
We'll get you all set up,
and we'll see what you're made of.
Um, I'll, uh... I'll be here at six.
Uh, okay, but everybody else
will be here at seven, so...
Sounds good, Hank.
Sit down, superstar.
School called,
and your mother wasn't here,
so I had to answer it.
You skipped out on another test.
I can explain.
They're suspending you for a week.
I understand.
No, I don't think you do.
Two of your teachers don't even
want you back in their class,
which means you don't have
enough credits to graduate.
I can make up the tests.
No, you've already ditched
too many of those.
Your mother and I have decided
that we're sending you
to a military boarding school.
You're sending me away?
Just for eight months. In Idaho.
You can get your grades up,
learn about responsibility,
and reapply to colleges next spring.
I think we need to talk about this more.
Well, I'm sorry.
It's not up to you.
Gary?
Aren't we talking more?
Gary!
What the hell?
It's a combination
of digital and mechanical.
Not easy to bypass,
but definitely based on our tech.
Well, I hope so,
considering how it was left in my car.
I mean, no interface
or remote signal?
Trying that right now.
You're right.
It definitely opens remotely.
Maybe if I can...
No. Shit!
Uh, if I can use a proxy...
No, that's stupid too.
Hey! If there's one thing you're not...
I'm sorry, boss. My head isn't clear.
Look, if you need a little
to function properly,
I won't stop you.
No. No.
I need to try for
at least a few more hours.
Staying clean is harder than I thought.
How can I help?
I'm getting help, actually.
Support groups.
My friend Ray has been taking me.
A friend? Oh.
Good.
Well, c-can you scan it?
See what's inside?
If this doesn't work,
I'll have to run a few programs,
try and brute-force a key code.
The case is lined.
They really wanted
to keep it a secret from you.
I don't know what I'm supposed
to do with the damn thing,
other than keep it on me at all times.
The Director must have a plan.
Yeah.
What else is new?
Can I help you?
Good morning, Mrs. MacLaren.
Do you have a moment to talk?
About what?
Don't be alarmed.
I'm actually here
about a personal matter.
Hello?
Hey.
Sorry, did... did I wake you?
No. It's okay.
Cool. Um...
Anyway, I just wanted to let you know
when I was going to be around today
in case you needed help
getting your things.
I mean, not that you need help
with your things,
but if you did, I-I can help.
Or I can not be around.
You know, alternatively.
No. Uh... it'd be
great if you were there,
if you don't mind.
No! No, not at all.
Um...
When are you going to be around?
I can be around all day,
if that works.
Okay, well, uh, I will
see you this afternoon.
Okay.
Bye.
Good morning, 3468.
I'm here to brief you on your mission.
You are...?
3112.
You can go now.
Your target is Congressman Bishop.
"Target." What is that supposed to mean?
That's the word the messenger used.
Bishop will be seated next to you...
in First Class.
1A and 1B.
This flight is today.
Is that a problem?
No, I just...
to be honest, I've never
been in an aircraft before.
Shouldn't I have luggage, or...?
You have the case.
Of course.
That's all you need.
Your credentials will
get it through security.
It will open at the appropriate time,
and you'll be made aware of its purpose.
I'm gonna need a little more than that.
I don't have more than that.
If you wouldn't mind dropping me off
where I'm going...
You do know I'm a federal agent?
It's just a few more blocks.
Good morning.
I know I'm a bit early.
I figured I'd get a head start on...
Carly, um...
Our needs have actually changed,
so I'm afraid we don't
have a job to offer you.
Okay. Uh, well,
if you wouldn't mind keeping me
in mind for the future...
Um, we're never
gonna be able to offer you
a job here, darling. Sorry.
Why not?
You know why.
No, I don't, actually.
Sir, I really need this job.
Our background check
revealed the charges on your record.
Assaulting a police officer?
Come on, kiddo.
You don't understand.
He's the father of my child.
And that makes it better... how?
You know, the 21st
has this service called "Uber."
You may want...
It's my wife. Excuse me.
Hey, Kat.
Where are you?
On my way to the airport, apparently.
We need to talk.
I can't right now.
I've just been assigned
escort duty to D.C.
The flight's at, uh... 1:30 today.
You're leaving?
Yeah, it's just for one night.
I'll-I'll call you as soon as I...
Kat?
At least you weren't ordered
to assassinate her.
What the hell is that supposed to mean?
I'm about to attend a funeral service.
What do you think it means?
You can pull over here.
How's it coming?
I'm having a hard time understanding
how one plant
is more important than another,
but I'm doing what you asked.
We need to talk.
Don't think I haven't noticed
that things are changing between us.
You struck me
and now you're sending me away
to military school.
Those changes?
I-I'm talking about
since you quit football.
Since my concussion?
I'm saying...
There comes a time
in every young man's life
when he stops putting his father
up on a pedestal
and just sees him as...
...As the man that he really is.
Exactly. That guy.
- Yeah.
- Look, I just... I just wanted to say...
you know, guy to guy, man to man...
I'm sorry things have gone south
between us, and...
I'm doing my best here.
Oh, and, uh...
you don't have to do that anymore.
Your mother told me to do it
while she was away at her sister's.
Gary?
Is there golf on later today?
1:00.
Maybe we could watch it together.
Here we go. Give me a sec, guys.
Carly, how can I help you?
You can explain why a background check
by a potential employer
showed an assault charge.
Well, maybe it was after
you punched me in my face
and stole my car.
How many times have you struck me?
You know, come to think of it...
maybe it was after
you kicked me in my nuts
outside the babysitter's house.
A witness probably called it in.
Right. Well, I'm sure someone inside
would be interested in hearing
the other side of the story.
They all know I'm a good family man.
What do you want?
I want us.
My son. My family.
Oh, my God. All right, Jeff,
I'm gonna let you in on a secret. Okay?
That night
you smashed my head
into the kitchen counter?
You were gonna kill me.
What're you talking about?
Let me tell you how...
I was gonna open the kitchen drawer,
get out your spare gun to defend myself,
but you were going to be
too strong and too fast.
The gun was gonna go off,
and I was going to bleed out
on the floor.
That is batshit crazy talk.
Carly, you need help.
What I needed was a decent job,
and you just took that from me.
Smooth.
Philip, you there?
What's up, boss?
I'm heading out of town.
I just received mission instructions
through another Traveler.
Where do you want us? I can...
be ready in five.
No, this one's a solo assignment.
I'm flying to D.C.
I'll be out of com reach
when the plane gets above 20,000 feet,
which is a terrifying thought
unto itself,
but I'll check in by cell
once we're on the ground,
about 6:30 your time.
Statistically,
it is the safest way to travel.
While strapped to a chair
moving through the sky,
but thanks for trying.
Good evening.
Hello.
Oh. Hi.
Mr. MacLaren. Perfect.
And just to your right.
Hi! Welcome.
Perfect. And just down the aisle
to your right.
Oh. Sorry.
Sir? I can stow that
in the overhead compartment,
if you like.
No, no, I'll keep it with me. Thanks.
Hi. Welcome.
Perfect, sir, and just down
the aisle to your left.
Hello. Mr. Bishop? Perfect.
And just here to your right.
Hi.
Excuse me.
What a day.
Yeah. Same here.
I'm, uh...
Excuse me.
Jim?
Yeah, it's me. I'm on the plane now.
Just left the funeral.
Well, it was fine. It was a funeral.
Yeah, you know I'm ready.
I've already spoken with the board.
Hayes' death shouldn't
hold up our plans at all.
We'll get the bill signed,
have the pipeline flowing in no time.
Okay, see you back in D.C.
Bye.
Mac?
You've reached
Special Agent Grant MacLaren.
Please leave a message at the tone.
Hey, it's me.
Um...
I really need to talk to you.
It's Jeff.
He is literally sabotaging my identity.
I think you're the only one
that can help.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is your captain speaking.
You'd think the executive class
would be more spacious, huh?
Well, I don't really have
a frame of reference.
First time up front?
Mm-hmm.
Not a lot of difference
at 35,000 feet.
Same paper-thin aluminum tube
as back there.
Paper-thin?
Oh, relax.
You got a better chance
of being eaten by a shark
than being in a plane crash.
Well, then I'm glad
we're not flying over water.
Sir?
I'm gonna have to ask you
to turn off your phone, please.
I'm a U.S. Congressman. It's fine.
Well, it's a privilege
to have you onboard, Congressman,
but we still need you to
turn off your phone, please.
Once we're in the air, you'll
have full access to our wifi.
Thank you.
I tell you, not many perks
to positions of power these days.
Front row.
What do you do?
FBI. Special Agent Grant MacLaren.
Ted Bishop.
Should've known by the suit, right?
I'm just kidding.
So I guess you heard
about Secretary Hayes' death?
Your division handling that?
We are.
Well, good on you.
Oop, we're off.
Oh. Good.
You said I needed help,
and you're right.
I need help with our son.
Right now?
Call it a peace offering.
Carly, I'm not stupid.
And I'm not going to play
babysitter every time that you...
I have a couple of job interviews.
I'm just going to have
to tell the truth.
See what happens.
If you really want to start
mending this relationship,
here's a chance.
Hey?
Hey, big guy.
How much time do you need?
How about you spend
a few hours with your son,
see what it's like?
Hey, hey-hey.
Come on. You can
chill with Dad for a bit.
Huh? Go for some ice cream?
Play some Space Kabob.
Shoot some guns?
I'm just joking.
We're not gonna shoot no guns.
Hey.
Come in. Come on in.
I, uh, haven't packed up...
anything up for you,
because I wasn't sure what you wanted.
Oh, I don't have much stuff.
Yeah, no, I was meaning
more, like, my stuff
that you might need.
I'm not taking your things, David.
Ah, but why... why do I need
all this stuff for myself?
I mean... Do you have a kettle?
'Cause everybody needs a kettle
for, like... tea.
So take it.
I insist.
Okay.
This is...
this is a lot harder
than I thought it was going to be.
Yeah, it's hard for me too.
Is it?
Mm-hmm.
I don't know if that's possible, Marcy,
because I feel like I'm dying here.
What?
Nothing.
No, you were gonna say something.
Thank you for the kettle.
That's not it.
What were you gonna say? Tell me.
I'm dying.
You mean that you feel the same way?
I do feel the same way,
but...
That's not what I'm saying.
No.
The seizures
that you've been helping me treat,
those are... those are just symptoms.
This is way too freaking much.
Everything that we've been doing
has just been to buy time.
I don't have that long.
And you were just gonna leave?
I don't want you to have
to go through all of that.
What have I been telling you
about doing stuff alone?
I mean, do you have any idea
what that would've done to me,
knowing that I kicked you out?
When?
Not today.
I could just hack in
and remove the charges.
No, that won't do it.
He'll just refile.
I need MacLaren to get involved,
use his FBI influence.
He said he'd touch base once he landed.
Okay. 1:30 for D.C., right?
Uh... flight 329 to Washington.
It just took off.
329...
No.
No, no, no, no, no.
No... no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What?
Marcy?
We have a problem.
Copy.
Copy what?
Trevor, we have a problem.
Copy that.
Um, uh, excuse me.
I, um, gotta take a leak.
Oh.
Sure.
Kat? What are you doing here?
Oh, God. Grant, I'm sorry.
This is so embarrassing.
What?
I thought I was gonna find you
on here with another woman,
and then I saw you talking
to that man up front,
and I realized that I made a...
Ladies and gentlemen,
your Captain from the flight deck.
Uh, we've just entered
an unexpected area of turbulence.
Please return to your seats
and fasten your seatbelts.
For Christ's sake, Kathryn, I'm working.
A police officer
came to our house this morning
and said that you're sleeping
with his wife.
What? That's...
He told me her name
and said that he's seen you
leaving their house.
Sir, we need you to take your seat.
- Just a second.
- No, now, sir.
I'm a federal agent.
Well, I'm a flight attendant!
Go back to your seat!
I'm not asking again.
Grant, it's fine.
We can talk later. Just go.
This is nothing. Don't worry.
Guys, can you hear me?
This is Mac. Can anybody hear me?
Boss, can you hear us?
The plane hasn't descended
far enough yet.
Anybody?
Can anybody hear me?
Yeah. We can hear you.
Is everything okay?
No. No. I think we're descending.
Has the case opened yet?
Uh, not... not yet.
Philip, what can you tell me
about this flight?
I didn't realize
this was your flight
until it was too late.
Flight 329 to Washington
goes down at 2:53 p.m.
on this day.
Are there any survivors?
Boss... all 141 people onboard die.
Bet you wish you had
that free drink, eh?
Ladies and gentlemen,
your Captain again.
One of our gauges
is acting up over here,
probably nothing, but, uh,
we've begun a slow turn.
Oh, Christ. Are we turned around?
I have to be in Washington by four.
Stand by.
Jesus, you smell that?
What is that?
Lithium batteries
catch fire in the cargo hold.
- Something's burning.
- What?
How does it go down?
The plane's already descending
and has made a slow turn back,
but doesn't make it.
Tell me how to stop it.
Tell the pilot you need
to depressurize and climb.
Sir, if you don't sit down right now...
Tell the Captain
we need to depressurize
and start climbing.
Captain, there's smoke in the cabin!
The fire's burned
through the cargo liner.
The flight systems will eventually fail.
Excuse me. Do you know...
It's too late to stop it.
Well, I'm pretty sure it is
my mission to save this plane.
Don't tell me...
Wait. Stand by.
Grant! What's happening?
Grant!
What the hell are you doing?
I have my mission.
Trevor, you need to tell me
how to make a two-person stasis field
hold more than two people.
Who's Trevor?
Those things use a ton of power.
What is that thing?
Who're you talking to?
Shut up for a second!
Find a way.
This is why you were kept
in the dark on this one.
What do you mean?
We keep improvising.
The Director must have known
you'd try
and save everyone on the plane.
You can't do it, boss.
I'm not trying to save everyone,
I'm trying to save my wife,
who decided to surprise me mid-air.
I'm talking about three people.
There has to be a way.
Stand by.
A stasis field means he's
going to need resuscitation.
Yeah, I know,
I'm prepared for that, but...
The wife's not on the manifest,
same with MacLaren.
They've already been scrubbed.
- By who?
- Why does it matter?
Because technically none of us
were given this mission.
And we keep improvising,
and in case you haven't noticed,
the future doesn't seem
to like it when we do that.
Mac's in trouble!
We're not turning back!
Tell me what the hell's going on.
There's a fire in the cargo hold.
What?
We're gonna get through this,
but you have to listen to me
and do exactly as I tell you.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we've had a small fire
in our cargo hold.
The fire suppression system
has activated.
I'm confident we'll be fine,
but as a matter of caution,
we are performing an emergency descent.
Look at me. Look at me.
The Captain's wrong.
This plane is gonna crash,
and nothing can stop that now.
- Oh, my god.
- But I have a device.
What?
This box...
can generate an energy field
that will temporarily
hold our bodies in stasis
during the crash
and throw us clear of the debris field.
Oh, my God, I'm gonna die.
No. We're not going to die.
Go ahead.
Who the hell are you talking to?
I ran the numbers back to front.
There's no way
the stasis field generator
can expand to fit three people.
We have to try.
Don't! It's a question of mass.
Even two people is gonna be a stretch,
considering your angle of impact
and velocity.
I'm sorry. We can't save her.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we need to prepare for a
possible emergency landing.
We have approximately five minutes
to prepare the cabin for landing,
so undivided attention
is very important.
Five minutes.
...require you to open a door,
immediately pull
the red inflation handle
located at the base of door
to ensure proper slide inflation.
Okay. It's time.
The seatbelt sign is on, sir!
Don't try to stop me. Please.
Come on. Now.
I'm not going anywhere with you.
Every other person on this plane
is gonna die today,
but you, for some reason, get to live,
so be humble and grateful
and get your ass out of that seat
before I drag it out.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we will not make the airport.
We'll be making an emergency landing.
When I give the command "brace, brace,"
assume the position
the crew has demonstrated
until the plane comes
to a complete stop.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
Before we brace for landing...
Get back in your seats, now!
Grant? Where are you going?
...Put your head face-down in your lap,
and wrap your arms
underneath your knees.
If you are unable
to assume this position,
cross your wrists
and place them on the seat back
in front of you.
Rest your forehead on the seat back.
Children should lean forward,
feet flat on the floor...
- Sit here.
- ...Place heads face-down in laps,
and wrap their arms
underneath their knees.
Stay calm, and we're gonna be all right.
I don't think I believe you anymore.
It doesn't matter if you do or not.
Just do as I say, when I say it.
Philip?
Go ahead.
Tell me about the crash site.
Uh...
They lose control of flight surfaces
any moment now from fire damage below,
so it comes in steep and hits
in the middle of a field.
There isn't much left, but, uh...
But what?
The tail section.
It's the only part of the plane
left intact
in every picture
in the historical record.
So someone could survive if
they were in the tail section?
No! That's not what he said!
The G-forces would be huge!
Thank you.
No, y-you can't!
You don't have time to save her!
Hello?
- Stay here.
- You're leaving me?
I'll be right back. Don't move.
Sir, sit down!
Sorry I took so long.
Wait. Where are we going?
You were not supposed
to be on this flight.
I know, I'm sorry.
So I'm improvising.
Come on.
Traveler 3468, you are off-mission.
- Oh, my god.
- Come on.
Grant, what did she say?
What was she talking about?
Just stay with me.
Here.
Who the hell is this?
This is my wife. She's gonna
use the device with you
instead of me.
What device?
Just, here, hold this tight
and get close to each other.
Come on. Closer. Closer.
Whatever you do,
don't let go of each other.
- Do you understand? No,
- I don't understand.
Just trust me and listen.
When that light flashes red,
you press it down. You hold it down.
- Okay? That's all you have to do.
- No! Why can't you?
- Where are you going?
- You can do this.
No! Don't go!
You're going to be okay.
45 seconds.
We see you coming in. Good luck.
Heads down! Stay down!
Brace! Brace!
Brace! Brace! Brace! Brace!
We need to separate them!
Get her shirt.
Where is he?
Clear?
Oh, goddamn him!
Clear!
He put himself in the tail.
Hi.
We made it.
We actually made it!
Grant? Where's Grant?
Hi. It's okay.
That son of a bitch
was telling the truth.
Grant!
Where's Grant? Grant?
Oh!
You're not the EMT team I was expecting.
I'm Traveler 3569.
3326.
Welcome to the 21st.
Oh, sh...
Wait. Wait.
How did they get here so fast, though?
No! No!
Wait! Wait!
Carly! No!
We're not supposed to be here!
Let go of me!
Let go! No! Let go!
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com