Previously on Travelers.
This one's a solo assignment.
I'm flying to D.C.
Flight 329 to Washington.
It just took off.
Kat, what are you doing here?
The police officer said that
you're sleeping with his wife.
329 to Washington goes down at 2:53 p.m.
Trevor, you need to tell me
how to make a two-person stasis field
hold more than two people.
Some of them could survive if
they were in the tail section?
No, that's not what he said.
The G-forces would be huge.
No, don't go.
You're gonna be okay.
Let go of me!
Where's my husband?
We can't leave him there!
We have to go back!
Shut her up, Marcy.
Yeah, we'll have to do more than that.
We can't have her remember any of this.
Sooner or later,
I'll need to give her
an HDAC2 inhibitor.
What?
Who the hell are you people?
Let go of me!
Can you hurry up, please?
She's stronger than she looks.
It's coming. Could you
at least slow down a little?
We can't be tied to the crash site
in any of the media reports.
Kathryn! Just relax.
How do you know my name?
Okay. Listen to me.
My husband was on that flight.
He's with the FBI.
He had this device...
that's what saved me, and...
That should buy us some silence
until I can administer the inhibitor.
I don't know how he stands her.
Boss, are you there?
MacLaren can't possibly hear you.
In fact, I doubt the G-forces
of an impact like that
are survivable.
Somebody thinks it is.
That EMTs who took him were our people.
They had to be.
She's right. They had to have known
when and where
the plane was coming down.
The Director would have assigned a team
to resuscitate him and Bishop.
Try his cell phone.
Hello?
Who is this?
Deal with the wife,
then come to OPs A.S.A.P.
Is he alive?
Clean up the mess you've created,
then we'll talk about the next steps.
Should we put her in bed properly?
You don't have to whisper.
You could scream
at the top of your lungs
and she wouldn't hear you.
Especially after I give her this.
You have memory inhibitor in your bag?
Yeah. Every Traveler medic has
to have a few doses on hand
in case of emergencies.
How much will she forget?
Most of yesterday.
I do not envy the hangover
she's about to wake up with.
Okay, grab a pair of shoes for him too,
then go help Philip set the scene.
Oh, the fun they had.
How much alcohol would it take
for somebody to black out
the previous day?
I don't know. I only use heroin.
Let's go with "lots."
You can put the weapon down.
We're not a threat.
Who are you?
Traveler D13.
"D"?
D is for "doctor."
Also, in my case, Derek.
I thought your team was reserved
for heads of state.
That was our first mission, yes,
but now we save
whoever the Director
tells us to save, worldwide.
We've already started the work.
Can he be saved?
If we can stabilize him,
stop his internal hemorrhaging,
replace or rebuild
one or more of his organs,
assuming one of you
is a suitable living donor
and willing to volunteer.
Of course.
Then maybe.
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
Oh...
Ow. Oh, my...
Grant?
_
He looks a lot better
than he did last night.
On the outside.
That's the easy part.
But all the damage is on the inside.
His brain, his major organs.
Took all night just to stabilize him.
They don't really look like
they're working on him at all.
That's because nano technology's
doing most of the work.
Really?
Graphene-based?
As advanced as I've ever seen.
I mean, without them,
with that amount of internal damage,
he wouldn't have stood a chance,
but even a full suite of medical nanites
can only do so much.
Well, I'm in over my head here
and there are more loose
ends I got to clean up, so...
Where are you going?
The airport.
If he wasn't on the plane,
why is his car parked there?
Right. Go.
All right, 0115, you're up.
Ready when you are, Derek.
We've grown it to the first stage,
but we have to grow the organ
the rest of the way
internally.
Yeah. Where are you growing it?
Do you have to cut me open?
Cut you? No.
It will find its own way.
I don't really like the sound of that.
You're not gonna like
how it feels, either.
Lay down, please.
This is gonna hurt a lot.
Oh!
_
I'm scrubbing in.
You're welcome to,
but it's not necessary.
He's the leader of my team.
I wasn't asking for permission.
I... pay here?
You, uh, mind if I look
at your license
and registration, please, sir?
Right, I should have that...
Just, uh, picking it up for a friend.
Uh-huh.
It says here this vehicle is registered
to the Federal Bureau of Investigation.
That's who my friend works for.
Step out of the vehicle please, sir.
Is there a problem? I have his key.
Grant MacLaren's...
Yeah, you read that on the registration.
Now step out of the vehicle.
Turn around.
I'm sorry, I can't do this.
Do you mind opening the gate, please?
Adding stage-3 nanites.
I've never seen that before.
Are you all right?
Absolutely.
Now let's see if this pancreas
needs to be replaced.
Ready suction?
We're getting close.
The bathrooms are done.
The kitchen looks great.
This place is gonna feel
like home in no time.
Oh, what? Is the vacuum cleaner broken?
No, I don't think so.
Just sucked up something
underneath the couch.
Oh. Got it.
Oops.
Don't look at me.
It's your fault they were under there.
I'm just worried I'm gonna find
your bra in here next.
Stop.
Need another unit of blood.
I'll go get it.
You still with me?
What?
You've been quiet.
I was thinking.
About never trying bodysurfing again?
There's that.
Whenever I'm on vacation
for any length of time,
I just start thinking
about how much more
I could be doing with my life.
Like?
I don't know.
My dad was a cop, now I'm FBI.
I mean, Jesus.
Talk about lack of imagination.
But you love the FBI.
Well, "like."
And you're really good at it.
So I keep telling you.
Well, maybe you're just ready
for a new challenge
that doesn't have
to come from your work.
Oh, God, we're about to have the baby
discussion again, aren't we?
- Did I even say the word?
- Oh, it's so...
- Stop! I didn't...
- I can see it all over you.
It's in your eyes. I know that look.
Oh, shoot.
We've got a flat tire. It's okay.
How's he doing?
Sternal fracture,
hemothorax and pulmonary contusion.
Whatever. I mean, how's it looking?
Is he going to be all right?
It's way too soon to say.
We've barely started,
plus... there's a problem
with his heart.
What's wrong?
It's damaged beyond
the nanite repair capability.
The Director wouldn't have sent them
if there wasn't a chance.
The Director's not infallible.
But he is in the best hands
I know of in any century.
Okay.
Did you find it?
Hmm? Oh.
Yeah, that's it. Thanks.
Yeah.
I wish I could be more helpful.
You are helping.
Yeah, clearly you'd be lost without me.
I really would be, Grant.
Hey.
I just got a call from local PD.
Parking attendant
called in a vehicle theft.
License plate matches Mac's SUV.
Seriously? I just texted him.
Maybe he doesn't know yet.
You've reached
Special Agent Grant MacLaren...
Hello?
Hey, Kat. It's Walt. Is Mac with you?
I thought he was with you.
Nope. I guess
we're getting our wires crossed.
Look, sorry to bother you.
Uh, wait. I...
Hello.
Shit.
Hey...
You don't look good.
Thanks.
I'm serious.
I can tell.
You should lie down.
Guys?
What is it, Philip?
We have a situation.
I need an evac.
How fast?
Now?
All right. Hang tight.
I'm on my way.
You need to tell the doctor.
Maybe something isn't right.
Derek?
He's the one who told me
it was gonna hurt.
They can give you something.
Ah... Little pain toward a good cause.
A lot of pain toward a good cause.
Go help Philip.
I'm fine.
The nanites have nearly
repaired the pancreas.
Good. But if they can't
normalize his neural activity,
it won't matter how well
we fix his body.
Okay, good.
Now it's time to take the shot.
All right?
I need you to stand
as still as possible.
All right?
Apply gentle but steady pressure
to the trigger.
The shot should
almost come as a surprise, okay?
Your breathing should stay...
Surprise!
Kat, you need to
take firearms seriously.
I'll show you how serious I am.
And you need to keep
your barrel downrange.
And you need to
keep your barrel downrange.
All right. You said
you wanted to do this,
but if you don't...
No. I do. I do. I like it here.
It feels dangerous.
'Cause it is dangerous. Now, come on.
Okay. Okay. Let me try again.
All right.
Now, take your aim.
Mm-hmm.
And gently...
Ooh.
...Squeeze the trigger.
Oh, my god! I shot a gun.
How about two more shots?
Okay.
Hey! Look at that.
Five shots,
and the target's completely unscathed.
That is a record.
Oh...
I'm not sure I like that I liked that.
Well, you did it.
You don't have to like it.
I like that I like you.
"Like"? Really? That's...
That's the best you got?
Really, really like?
Kinda prefer a different word.
Want?
Oh, I hadn't thought of that word.
Need?
That's even better.
Now?
Yeah, that's my favorite one so far.
I need you to run
a facial recognition check.
This is the guy who
took off with Mac's SUV.
Well, I'll give you this one for free.
That's Philip Pearson.
Your partner had me
run him a few weeks ago.
Are you sure that's him?
Yeah, MacLaren got all aggro about it.
Won't be forgetting
that face any time soon.
That's Philip Pearson.
I've started to worry
that we're gonna regret
not having children.
Are you having actual regret,
or just the fear of having regret?
The fear one, I think.
What about you?
I'm gonna plead the fifth.
Grant, we haven't
talked about it in ages,
and we're getting older.
You can say that again.
But there's new technologies.
It's amazing what they can do now.
And you'd be such a great dad.
I think you're forgetting
how hard it was for us.
You mean for me.
Well, it took us a long time
to climb out of it.
I know.
And I'm pulling
these 60-hour weeks lately.
All right, I-I get it.
I just...
I'm afraid that if it happened again...
I know. I just...
I know.
You're gonna be late.
Yeah.
Beth here.
Walt, Mack's SUV was found
dumped in a back alley parking lot,
suspect not on scene.
They bringing it in?
Not anytime soon.
You're not answering your phone.
Kat, I'm sorry, it's been busy.
Do you know where he is, Walt?
Not yet.
He's not with me, he's not with you,
although apparently we both have
messages saying otherwise.
Right.
You want to walk with me?
If we sounded the alarm
every time an agent's whereabouts
were unknown for a few hours...
What I don't get is the lies.
It could be anything
at this point in time.
Right now, all we know is
that his SUV has been stolen.
Wait. What?
I'm at the pick-up spot. Where are you?
I'm in an alley one block south.
Police are close.
All right, I'm coming.
Police, west entrance.
Oh, God. Aah!
Oh, God, I'm sorry.
I spilled hot coffee on myself.
Oh! Oh, I'm in your way, aren't I?
Uh, I'm sorry. Sorry.
Um, hang on, hang on.
Thanks.
MacLaren.
I got it. All right.
I'll be there.
Oh, good. This takes
forever with one person.
How do corporate clients
always seem to know
which materials aren't in stock?
Now?
"All hands on deck."
But I booked those hands in advance.
I know.
I'm sorry.
"Sorry."
What do you want me to do?
You could not pick up
your phone for once.
Yeah, and they could
not give me a paycheck,
which only pays for everything we have.
You're right.
I should be happy
that I get to spend
any time at all with you
and grateful
that I'm so well provided for.
- That is not what I meant.
- Yeah, it is, Grant.
It's exactly what you meant.
- Kat.
- You know what?
Just please go to work.
What do you ex...
That explains why we lost his GPS.
So, you notice anything out of place?
No.
Well, at least there's
no sign of a struggle.
Jesus. I hadn't even considered that.
Sorry, professional reflex.
You know what the weirdest part is?
It doesn't feel completely unexpected.
What do you mean?
Lately I found myself questioning things
I didn't think
had any mystery left in them,
like my husband.
Oh, God, Walt. Maybe I'm losing my mind.
No, you're not losing your mind.
I've noticed some things myself.
Really?
Little things, like all of a sudden,
a much better shot.
He's suddenly much better
at a lot of things.
Yeah...
definitely not squash.
Last night, we...
What? What happened?
That's the thing. I don't really know.
I woke up to a disaster of a kitchen
full of empty wine bottles, but...
I don't remember attending the party.
I mean, it's not unusual for us
to have a glass of wine or two
if he gets home at a decent hour, but...
he sent me a text this morning,
said that I was in rare form.
Well, Kat, you can be
pretty entertaining
when you've had a few.
But I don't remember having anything!
I mean...
I woke up this morning
feeling hung over,
but never in my life
have I been blackout drunk,
certainly not
on a Tuesday night at home.
It's like my life derailed,
but nothing happened.
Look, maybe you're just stressed.
Let me drive you back to your car.
You sure you don't want
to drive me to the asylum?
That is way outta my way.
They're looking for me.
I'll get eyes on Forbes.
Okay, hold him down.
Okay. Clamps.
Pass me the gauze.
We can't wait. We've gotta do this.
Scalpel.
It's time.
Time?
Come on, old man, you got this.
I'm beginning to see
that time is like a river.
You can throw the biggest rock
that you can find
into the river,
but the water just goes around the rock.
It's not optimal, but we have no choice.
...and it continues downstream
as if the rock...
...was never there.
Aah!
Time to go.
What are you doing?
What does it look like?
No. Just leave it.
I don't know how healthy it is
to leave all this stuff out.
You weren't sure whether
we should set the nursery up
before the baby was born.
You gonna throw that in my face too?
No. Come on!
Just leave it.
I want to deal with it.
You should be resting.
Oh, God, I am sick of resting.
I'm just putting
some stuff away for now.
- If you want to help...
- Why?
Aren't we going to try again?
Was that it?
It's over?
Every time you pass this room,
you stand in the doorway and you stare.
Yeah, I did that before.
Well, I think maybe
it meant something different
before you lost the baby.
No, before we lost the baby.
This isn't just something
that happened to me.
You're absolutely right about that.
Because I almost lost you.
I spent a whole day and night
in a hospital room alone
waiting to see whether or not
you were going to make it.
I was sad we lost the baby,
but just the thought of losing you
was so much worse.
And I'm sorry if that makes me
a selfish asshole, but...
Yeah.
I'm putting a few things away.
It's not like
we haven't heard from him today.
If even you don't know where he is...
We don't keep tabs on each other.
He doesn't know where I am
half the time either.
His vehicle was stolen,
and he's not answering the phone.
We will figure it out, Kat, okay?
I will tell you the minute
that we hear anything.
All right?
- Thanks, Walt.
- No problem.
Forbes.
Yeah, hi. It's Beth.
- Go ahead.
- I, uh, I found something on Mac.
You're gonna want to see this.
Okay, I'm on my way up.
Kathryn?
Yes.
And no.
Do you understand?
These aren't my memories.
No.
I'm not Grant MacLaren.
And yes.
These were his memories.
Only the brightest shards...
fragmented and incoherent.
Orphaned neurons
of your host's mind cut off from you.
Normally, you never
would have had access to them.
Why now?
You're very near death.
I can feel it.
We're trying to save you.
Tens of thousands of nanites
working in concert
to repair damage
to your prefrontal cortex
and throughout the rest of your body.
Your consciousness
was given access to these memories
as a refuge.
Show me more.
There are no more.
Those were the last remnants of him.
I loved you so much.
He did.
They're his memories, not yours.
So why can't I tell the difference?
Cross-clamping the aorta.
Okay. Here we go. Scalpel.
Tissue is presenting normally,
but it's fibrillating.
Let's get it in and get it charged.
Hey. Check your email.
What'd you find?
Mac's GPS data.
Uploaded to the cloud.
Everywhere MacLaren's SUV
has been in the past month and a half.
I marked a few places of interest.
This is great.
I pulled Philip Pearson's file.
Saw his lawyer is Ray Green.
Why am I not surprised?
Guess who bought an old garage
up near the tracks
the day after his client
won the lottery?
MacLaren's been there a bunch of times.
There you go.
Oh, shit.
- I'll get started on a warrant.
- Shit!
We have to move!
What?
MacLaren's partner is coming.
Do you know what
they're doing to him in there?
The mission comes first.
Stop him.
I can hack into the system,
slow him down with the warrant,
stall him for a couple hours, maybe,
but eventually, he will be coming!
Why these memories?
They could be random...
or these memories were so strong
they survived your arrival.
What's happening?
It's time to go.
Go where?
We'll see.
Are you coming?
No.
And yes.
- He's not responding!
- Charge again.
Clear!
- Again!
- Charge!
Clear!
You've reached
Special Agent Grant MacLaren.
Please leave a message.
Jesus, Mac.
Hello?
Can I help you?
I'm looking for Philip Pearson.
Uh... Who?
Pearson. I know he's here.
And you are?
Special Agent Forbes.
FBI.
Well, in that case,
I'm gonna need to see a warrant.
Tell me again
why I shouldn't take you in.
You know why. I'm a hacker.
How am I gonna do that from jail?
Mac?
Now look what you've done.
W-What's going on?
Someone needs to be reminded
of the dynamics of
our working relationship.
W... You're working with this kid?
No, no, no. He's working for me.
A distinction that seems
to have slipped his mind.
I was just trying to show you
how vulnerable you are.
You shut up.
Mr. Pearson is one
of my confidential informants
on the hacking case I was working.
I promised to keep him out of the system
if he promised to stop breaking the law.
Did I or did I not prove to you
that I could steal your car?
You don't even have a license.
I can make one of those too.
He claims that if he could hack my life,
bad guys could too.
I'm telling you, man,
you guys are not secure.
Yeah, all right, that's enough.
Hey, thanks for the tip on my car, Walt.
Wasn't hard to figure out who did it.
Why didn't you call me back?
You didn't get my texts?
No, I didn't get them.
I texted you, like, three times.
Uh, sorry, guys.
He didn't get them.
They were redirected.
I was proving a point.
I'm gonna need to call off the cavalry.
Everyone's out there looking for you.
What?
You went offline
and your car was stolen.
Aw, Jesus. Are you listening to this?
I did you a favor.
How do you people not see that?
Your security is shit!
You're probably vulnerable too.
My fee is extremely reasonable.
If you weren't his C.I...
- Aah!
- Shh, shh.
I'm sorry.
I had no idea he was doing this.
Look, it's not like I don't
have anything better to do
than chase your ass all over town.
I'll make it up to you.
It's not me
that you have to worry about.
Call your wife.
Uh... Walt!
Your fee is extremely reasonable?
I was improvising!
But I think we pulled it off.
I thought I was gonna pass out.
We've had enough of that for one day.
The nanites still have
a few hours' work.
You have no business being on your feet.
So I should take a sick day,
is that what you're saying?
I'm saying
if you want to avoid external scarring,
you have rest for
at least two more hours,
and no sexual activity
for the next 36 hours,
until the nanites have left your system.
Well, I'll try to restrain myself.
Thank you.
It was our pleasure.
How about hooking me up
with some of that sweet nano tech?
Nanites are by directive only.
Sorry.
I've got school tomorrow, Derek!
Lucky you.
We have to fly across the world
to save the life of
a genocidal dictator.
Why would you do that?
Presumably he's better
than the alternative.
It was a pleasure
working with you, 3569.
Same here.
Get some rest.
And I wanted you to know
if there was anything
we could do for you...
It's... It's all right.
I understand.
Take care of yourselves.
Kat?
Hello?
You home?
There you are.
I tried your cell phone.
I turned it off.
Now you know how it feels.
I know, I'm sorry.
I couldn't stop myself from checking it
to see if you were alive or dead,
and it was making me
crazy, so I shut it off,
and then I found myself
enjoying the feeling,
so I kept it off.
Well, it's actually a funny story.
My C.I. stole my car.
- He hacked into my phone...
- You know what?
You can tell me tomorrow.
I am sure it's an interesting story,
but right now I'm tired,
and I want to have a bath.
If you need me to wash your back, or...
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com