Previously on Travelers...
We're off mission. Stand down!
No plan survives contact with the past.
You must be new.
We just got this security-camera footage
from outside the library.
Has Marcy been acting
differently lately?
No.
How are you supposed to throw
a football with a broken hand?
Please stop.
What is wrong with him?
Whoa, Philip.
And all these people are going to die?
Yeah.
I know this person.
I'm starting to think
whoever they're buying from
ain't gonna show.
It's all about patience.
That's what you said
with the Jonas Walker case,
and he fell off the face of the Earth.
You're going to have to
let that one go, partner.
Yeah, I know, I know.
I'm like a dog with a bone, I guess.
Hello.
What are they selling, car parts?
Looks good.
That's a hell of a lot of money
for car parts.
Multiple shots fired! 65 Heward Drive.
We need back-up right away!
- What about the back-up?
- Can't wait!
FBI!
Drop your weapons!
No! Drop your weapons!
All responding units, be advised,
there's a damaged Mercedes
leaving this location
with three armed men,
two of them badly injured.
Intercept and detain if possible!
Traveler...
34... 68.
Support required.
Coordinates 47 degrees, 14 minutes,
35.045 seconds.
Make and model confirmed.
Units are en route.
...07 seconds.
End of message.
You wait for the back-up.
I'm going after them!
It's a damn mess.
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
Philip, you there?
Hey, boss.
What are you doing right now?
Oh, you know...
healing from a gunshot wound,
watching old news with Marcy.
I need you to direct me
to 47 degrees, 14 minutes,
35.045 seconds
by 122 degrees,
22 minutes, 13.407 seconds.
- You got it?
- On it.
Why? What... What's happening?
I just got the most bizarre messenger.
They're all bizarre to me.
Yeah, well, this message
came from the mouth
of a dying man...
a traveler team in need
of assistance at those coordinates.
It's on its way to you now.
We'll meet you there.
Uh, nope, Philip's not
going anywhere in his shape,
but I will be there in 10.
Pick up Carly on the way. Come armed.
Bring your full medical kit.
You're at the coordinates.
Should be an old warehouse on your left.
How far out are Carly and Marcy?
Uh, five minutes.
Make sure they wait for my all-clear.
Understood.
Drop your weapon.
- I'm here to help.
- Shut up.
He's one of the FBI agents.
Yeah. Who you shot at.
Thanks very much.
Whatever happened to Protocol 3?
I'm Traveler 3468.
I received a message
to come to these coordinates
and give support.
Who delivered the message?
One of the Russians.
Well, that's bullshit,
'cause that would...
that would kill an adult.
It did.
The Director must've figured
he was dying anyway.
You want my help or not?
I'm Rick Hall.
This is Carter. That's my boy,
Luca, on the table.
Grant MacLaren. My medic's on the way.
Well, that's good, 'cause ours is dead.
What is this? What happened?
Well, our mission
was to acquire a component
from Russian travelers
and deliver it
to another team for testing.
The Russians' historian was dead,
so they were out of cash.
We were then instructed to finance them
in exchange for the hand-off,
but they got greedy.
A traveler team turned on you?
He must be new.
Yeah. They went rogue.
Tried to take our money
and the component,
probably sell it somewhere else,
and busted it in the process.
You saw the rest. Now where's the medic?
Carly, Marcy... you have the all-clear
to enter the building upon arrival.
One minute out.
They're moments away.
So how badly damaged is it?
I don't know. It's not my expertise.
It was a good plan, if the Russians
hadn't gone rogue.
Yeah, then the FBI would've busted you.
Doesn't sound like a great plan to me.
Oh, shit.
We're coming in.
It's all right.
What can you tell me?
Gunshot wound to the abdomen.
There's no exit wound.
This is Luca. That's Carter. I'm Hall.
Mr. Hall is their team leader.
You can put your weapon away now.
He's lost a lot of blood
and still hemorrhaging.
I think the only thing I can do
is get him stable before
we get him to a hospital.
No. No hospitals.
He's wanted by the police.
They both are.
Well, I don't have anywhere
near the proper resources.
Well, obviously,
the Director thinks you do,
or you wouldn't be here, would you?
All right. Go ahead and put him out.
Can you get me light, please?
All right, all right.
Okay, warm up the laser
and get him on plasma.
What happened?
He got shot in the gut.
No. I'm talking about you.
Let me see.
Ah! Goddammit!
I don't think that you understand
how serious your injuries are.
Stop worrying about me and help Luca.
It's Forbes.
Do your thing.
MacLaren.
We've got three dead bodies.
All of them ghosts in the system.
Really? Any word on the whereabouts
of that car that I was pursuing?
That's what I'm calling to ask you.
No, no. They had too big a lead.
I was just about to get back
to local enforcement.
All right, let me know what you hear.
Will do.
I can't locate the bullet.
I think the only thing that I can do
is cauterize the torn vessels...
Just get the bullet out of him.
I am telling you
that if I operate now, I will kill him.
Your friend, Carter,
is coughing up blood
because his internal bleeding
includes his lungs.
I'm telling you that he's dying,
he can't be saved.
The man is an ox! He just carried...
Shut up and listen to me! Okay?
This is time-sensitive.
Luca has lost close to 40% of his blood.
He won't survive any sort
of surgery without a donor.
So if we act now,
we can use Carter's blood
to save Luca's life.
I have a blood-type converter,
I'm telling you I can't save them both.
So we either watch the two of them die,
or Carter saves Luca's life...
those are your options.
You need to decide
before Carter goes septic
and his blood's not good to anyone.
- Mr. Hall...
- I Hear you! Relax.
Just give me a second, please.
I have to make sure
the FBI doesn't show up here.
Now, look, if I don't do
something to throw Forbes off...
Do what you need to do.
I'll be operating into the early hours.
Carly can assist.
Mr. Hall can handle
anything that comes up.
All right.
Looking good, Trev. How's that feel?
Oh, it feels great.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Let's see what you got in the tank!
Wow.
Man, you're flying!
You'll be back on the team in no time.
Trevor?
Can I talk to you?
Ms. Day? How can I help you?
Actually, I would like to help you.
I've been looking over your transcripts
and there are some things
we need to talk about.
What is it?
Well, it's kind of a bigger conversation
that I'd like to have
with you and your parents.
You know, the whole team.
I like to think
that I can have these
conversations on my own.
Well, you're 17, so.
I've set a meeting with them
for fourth period today.
I'll expect to see you there.
I'll be there.
All right.
Hey! A little help?
Let's see if you've still got it!
What are you doing here?
No "Hey, Jeff." No "Good morning."
I get "What are you doing here?"
Looks like my son spent
another night at the babysitter's
while you were out
with your new man, hmm?
You think I haven't seen
that white dude around?
Is that how you got these new wheels?
You got a sugar daddy?
That's none of your business.
Carly.
We gotta talk about this family.
We're not a family.
Mother, father, and son.
Mother, son, abusive biological father.
- That's cold.
- It's accurate.
So you're gonna throw away
everything that's good between us
because one night
I had a bit too much to drink?
I'm leaving now.
Oh, Carly, come on.
Come on. You know
we got a connection, right?
You gonna tell me you don't miss this?
- Don't, Jeff.
- I do.
Ho, ho, ho... ow!
Oh...
This...
is where any idea you have of "us"
ends.
Right now.
You do not touch me.
Are we clear?
I still got a right to see my kid.
And your kid has
a right to child support.
Don't come near us again without it.
You've changed, Carly. You're like...
You're like a completely
different person.
That's something that should've happened
a long time ago.
Bitch.
Bitch!
Hey, kid?
Hey.
Got your drugs.
Why don't you knock next time?
Why don't you lock the door?
You're welcome, by the way.
If you're smart,
there's about three weeks' worth
of Percocet there.
Although, you know, uh,
trading one addiction
for another never works.
Uh, you look, uh... not so good.
Like somebody beat you up.
Did somebody beat you up?
I'm fine.
You don't look fine.
You look like a piece of...
Holy shit.
What is this?
It's nothing.
It's insanity.
Hey. It's the gambling matrix, right?
This is how you do it, isn't it?
It's really nothing.
There are dates up here
that are months from now.
How much research do y...?
No! Don't...! Don't.
Why don't you give me a tip?
Gimme a little tip. Come on.
Can you just leave?
Please?
Either you give me a tip,
or you tell me what this is all about
on the wall over here,
all right?
'Cause you got all of that,
and you're giving me, like, crumbs.
Come on, man.
You'd be in jail right now
if it wasn't for me.
You know that.
Hey, Luca, it's okay!
Hey, I'm right here.
I'm right here.
I need you to wake up
and listen to me, Luca.
I need you to wake up,
all right? Wake up, Luca.
- Luca?
- No.
Luca, wake up.
Agh!
Get it out!
No! No!
Get it off me! Get it out of me!
Wake up! Luca! Wake up!
Ms. Warton.
I'm Officer Conniker.
I tried to contact you earlier.
I'd just like to speak with you
about the incident outside the library.
What incident?
The boys that assaulted
you and another employee?
Listen, I understand
that you didn't report it,
and that's not unusual
with assault cases,
but I... I saw the closed circuit
television footage.
Caught both assaults
and you kicking their asses.
Not that you'd be in
any trouble for retaliating.
What I saw was actually damn impressive.
Well, I'd like to move on.
Uh-huh. Listen.
Have you sought counseling of any kind?
Everything's fine.
I don't need counseling.
So then why are you living
with this social worker?
Excuse me?
Not that you're to blame in any way,
but I should inform you
that should a state mental health worker
be found guilty
of inappropriate fraternization
with a client,
especially one with
developmental issues...
Do I look like I have
developmental issues, officer?
That's not for me to judge.
I'm just saying that'd be
grounds for termination,
if not worse... litigation.
Just so you understand the consequences.
You gonna take that, or...?
Uh, yeah. If you'll excuse me.
This is Marcy.
What happened?
He was fine when I left.
Night terrors.
Sometimes they're too real.
Yeah, one minute he's sleeping,
and the next, he's screaming.
He almost killed me once.
All right, well,
let's get you closed up again.
Mac. We got 'em.
Got who?
Our friends from last night.
Located 'em right here in town.
We had leads
that had them leaving the city.
Yeah, I did some digging anyway.
Ran the plates
on the car that left the scene.
It belongs to a Sergeant Rick Hall.
Served in Iraq,
lives in Portland.
Had some agents go check out
his place this morning.
Hall hasn't been there in weeks.
Pulled him up on the database.
He owns three other properties.
Place in Austin, condo in Vancouver,
and a warehouse right here in town.
Checked out the freeway CCTV footage...
And...
Nice work.
Let's file for a warrant
and get down there, huh?
Already got it.
Suit up.
Right! I'll meet you downstairs
in a minute.
All right.
Marcy, it's MacLaren.
I don't know.
I just got word from MacLaren.
The FBI are on their way.
We have maybe 20 minutes.
Isn't MacLaren with the FBI?
Yeah, and he obfuscated
the best he could,
but his partner found your name
on the deed to this building
and tracked your vehicle here.
Okay, well, you... you tell him
he's got to stop them.
There's only so much he can do
without blowing his cover.
We're wasting time!
Are you being serious right now?
Are you kidding me?
What about us?
Luca shouldn't even be moved!
I will be there!
I'm okay. We should go.
They're on their way.
We need to move.
What I'd like to do
is change the conversation
from Trevor's football career
and focus on his grades.
If he has a football career,
he doesn't need grades.
Tabling that a moment,
I think it's important
for you to understand
that Trevor needs
to start doing much better...
- ...if he hopes to graduate.
- Trevor, we need you...
...outside the school and ready to go
in three minutes. We've got a mission.
...Are you prepared to do the work?
I can do that.
Good.
Carly will be outside to pick you up.
...Time on his homework
and less watching Internet porn.
Understood, no more porn.
What?
Don't embarrass the kid.
The apple doesn't fall
far from the tree, Gary.
Ms. Day? I know you probably have
a lot you want to talk about
without me in the room,
so I should give you
a chance to do that.
All I have to say
is that I fully intend
to raise my grades
and focus on the sciences,
and I have no intention
of playing football again.
- What?
- Sorry, Gary.
"Gary"?
Thank you for your time and concern.
But Trevor, we're not finished here.
- Trevor!
- You're playing football!
I'm sorry.
He's just been so different
since the concussion.
Can I have one of those?
Do you think you can sit up for me?
All right. There you go.
Okay.
I need you to hold
this bag above your heart, okay?
Is that Carter?
He saved your life.
Above your heart, okay?
Nice and easy!
The wound is fragile.
All right. It's time. We gotta go.
Okay.
Reminder... these men are dangerous.
Approach with extreme caution.
Breathe, man.
You used to love this shit
in the old days.
I wasn't very bright in the old days.
Fall back! Fall back!
You okay?
You should warn us.
Hey, come on. You would've told him.
MacLaren had to be as surprised
as the rest of them.
Don't worry about it. They're fine.
They could've been hurt.
It had to be done!
We would've left too much back there
that might've incriminated...
Jesus, what is that? Is that a baby?
- Whose baby is that?
- Mine.
- You take him on missions?
- Oh, not if I can help it,
but somebody needed
to come save your ass.
He has your eyes, Carly.
He really does.
I just hope we can fix it.
It's a key component.
Tell me this kid knows what he's doing.
This kid is older
than all of us put together.
What the hell was that?
You nearly killed my men!
They're not your men.
Do you even give a damn
about Protocol 3?
Was anybody killed?
You nearly killed me!
Yet here you are, MacLaren!
Look, if you'd done your job properly,
the FBI wouldn't have
found us in the first place.
I can only throw them off
the scent for so long!
Forbes is a good cop.
Well, maybe I should've waited
for your friend, Forbes,
to open the door
before I set it off.
What?
It was our base of operations!
I had to get rid of the evidence!
You almost got...
Okay! Okay, okay.
It's done.
You're alive.
Yeah.
Have you slept? You look exhausted.
I am, but I'll live, so will my patient.
- It's not an easy fix.
- But we can do it.
Well, you damn well better.
Don't talk to my team like that!
Or what? What're you gonna do?
Okay! All right!
All right! Hey!
They just need some time to work.
Let's give them some space.
What is it?
I'm grounded.
You know,
I was tempted to break his nose
on your behalf,
but I held it together.
You and me both.
I don't know.
The Director obviously thinks
he and his team are worth saving, but...
I gotta get back to work.
This bomb isn't exactly gonna
De-escalate the investigation.
I gotta call my babysitter.
Hey. Can I get on our computer?
Uh...
Is there something you need?
I'll do it, just get me on.
I need to set the drop-off coordinates
with the other team,
if that's okay with you.
I guess.
Well, thank you so much.
How are you feeling, Luca?
Better.
Thanks.
Hey, uh, how long
have you had night terrors?
Since I was a kid.
I know it's hard for
some people to understand.
No. I do.
My brother used to get them
all the time, growing up.
Your brother?
Mm-hmm.
Uh, get some rest, okay?
Yeah.
Hey.
Can I talk to you for a second?
About what?
When I was really young,
there was an emergency evacuation
in my shelter block.
I was separated from my brother...
So?
So... one of the things
that I remember about him
is he used to suffer from night terrors.
I just thought,
there's only so many of us...
Leave the future in the past, Doctor.
Protocol 2.
I understand that,
but if it's at all possible...
I don't think you understand.
I don't think you
understand a goddamn thing.
I don't think any of you do!
Look.
We came here with a team of five,
just like you.
You know, we all made it,
which is rarer than you think,
believe it or not,
but we're down to two now.
What does that mean to you?
Uh... two more to go?
When you have been doing this
as long as we have,
doing whatever the Director
tells you, without question...
building devices for missions,
rigging elections,
saving people...
and by the way, killing people, too...
don't think the future
doesn't get its hands dirty.
To do this job, to stay alive,
you need to be focused.
We're very focused, Mr. Hall.
Focused?
You're a bunch of tourists!
He's a junkie!
Don't think I haven't seen
fresh track marks before.
You're worried about
your parents grounding you,
for Christ's sake!
Your tactician brings an infant
to the missions, and MacLaren...
Hah! MacLaren doesn't even know
what side he's on!
Well, I thought we were all
supposed to be on the same side.
I need you to be
committed to the mission,
whatever the mission!
Protocol 1 is the only one that matters,
and that's what you guys aren't getting!
And the reason you're not getting that
because your priorities
are all outta whack!
Now I need this team,
right here, right now,
to get on side,
or I cannot trust you.
Is there a problem?
- No!
- Yes!
Mr. Hall here doesn't seem to think
that we know what we're doing.
I am just trying
to help your people understand
how things are around here.
Oh, we understand how it is, Mr. Hall.
We really do.
I hope so.
Knock-knock?
Kat.
You really are here.
Yeah, I-I texted you.
Yes, you did.
How romantic.
Since this is usually date night,
I thought I'd bring you some Chinese
and make you take a break.
Don't worry, it's vegetarian.
Well, that is romantic.
Mm.
I'm sorry about tonight.
I-I know it's been crazy busy.
I just... we don't have enough manpower.
Oh, come on, I am happy to
share you with your work, babe.
I always have been.
As long as that's all
I'm competing with.
What does that mean?
Well, it has been an awfully long time.
Yeah, I know.
Hey.
You still look like shit.
Thanks.
Who's that you're with?
A friend.
Kinda looks like a cop car.
Yeah, it does a little, doesn't it?
So which one is it?
Right here.
That's great. Thanks for doing this.
Yeah.
Keys?
Oh...
Where's my money?
I transferred your money.
Yeah, you transferred me the rent,
now you owe me 8% commission.
8% what?
And, uh, bets for tomorrow.
I gave you bets yesterday.
Yeah, but I got a little ambitious.
I can't keep doing this, Ray.
You know what?
I can't keep being your errand boy.
Come on, bud. Show me a little respect.
Look at everything I do for you
on a daily basis.
I bring you drugs.
I show you houses.
You don't even tell me your system.
Okay, 10%.
10%. What's that work out to?
Give me the keys.
Who's this house for, anyway?
It's a safe house for time travelers.
Them again, huh?
All right. It's better I don't know.
Here you go.
Did your host have a family?
Sort of. Not really.
She had, um... David.
His name is David.
He took care of my host
before I arrived.
What? Like a butler?
Your host rich?
No, she just needed
assistance with some things.
What about you?
Wife? Kids?
That should do it.
Looks different.
It'll work.
Hall, we found you a safe house.
It's time to go.
Don't let the door
hit your ass on the way out?
What happened
to "we're all on the same side"?
I don't wanna be in the same room.
Listen, we're all gonna get along.
You'll see.
Where's Luca and Marcy?
They went for a walk.
Marcy said that he had to keep moving
to prevent clotting.
Okay. Soon as they get back.
Are you sure that's
the Director's intention?
'Cause I'm just...
I'm just asking a question.
Have you received instructions
from the Director
to relocate my team?
No, I haven't.
Okay, well, the Director
put us together for a reason.
You're splitting us up, why?
Protocol 6.
Oh, listen
to the boy scout quoting his protocols.
I know the rules, MacLaren.
"Traveler teams should stay apart
unless instructed otherwise."
Well, guess what?
You were instructed otherwise.
I think you know
that I have seniority here.
I should be leading this team.
MacLaren.
We I.D.'d all the bodies now.
Counting the Russians
and the guy we found scorched
in the warehouse,
that's four.
That leaves two still out there.
Well, one of them's
this "Rick Hall" character.
Who's the other one?
Ah, the system just pulled him up
on an ABM camera in the East End.
I'll send a picture to your phone.
Guy's name is Luca Shun.
We got him working 15 years
as a sous chef in Portland,
then all of a sudden,
he's wanted upstate
for petty theft and assault charges.
I'm following a lead on Hall.
I'll let you know what I find.
All right.
Agent Forbes?
I told you he was a good cop.
Marcy, I need you and Luca inside now.
Marcy?
She may have turned off her com.
- I'll try and find them.
- Yeah, I'll look around...
- ...The neighborhood.
- You stay put.
- You're just as wanted as Luca.
- Hey. We're right here.
Hey.
What's wrong?
The FBI caught you on CCTV,
knows who you are,
and are searching the area.
Yeah, if only we had
somebody on the inside.
There is no way I'm risking
my team getting discovered.
I want you out of here.
The mission comes first.
You said it was a simple hand-off
of a component,
so hand it off,
and get out of state.
You know, there's a simple
answer to this problem.
He needs to go.
- Who needs to go?
- Go where?
Forbes! He knows too much.
He's too close.
We remove him,
we don't got to go anywhere.
We are not killing Forbes.
Well, if you can't to do it,
I know people who can,
but it's obvious to me
the Director's
put us together for a reason...
so I can teach you a lesson.
Now, if it's too much for you to handle,
I can help you, but I think
it would be better for all of us
to see if you have it in you.
So...
Do we... Do we have a problem?
No.
Do you deny my seniority?
I don't deny it.
Of course not.
You're the kind of man
who follows the rules.
This is great, right?
Luca and I can handle
our drop-off tonight
while you deal with Forbes.
I'm gonna take your vehicle.
- I'll rent you a car.
- Whatever.
As long as you remember
to bring it back
with a full tank of gas.
Cracks me up. I love this guy.
Here's the thing.
When we're both done,
we are gonna have a conversation
about how this new team
will work together.
Forbes.
Hey, it's Mac.
You got something?
Yeah, maybe.
We should meet.
I'll text you the location
and the broad strokes,
but we should go over
the details in person.
Say an hour?
Yeah, I can do that. You all right?
Never better.
See you in an hour.
We're all set.
Nobody said this was gonna be easy.
I know,
but I never thought we'd have to
do something like this.
Just think of how MacLaren feels.
He's the one who has to do it.
He doesn't have to do anything.
The Director didn't order it.
How confident are you in the Intel?
This is the place.
Your new doctor
thinks she's your sister.
Yeah. She told me.
I hope she's right.
Well you should get that thought
out of your head right now.
Your loyalty needs to be with me.
You know you have it.
I'm not so sure of MacLaren.
Oh, don't worry about MacLaren.
I know what kind of guy he is.
He'll fall in line.
And if he doesn't?
Then he'll have to go.
FBI!
Hands! Show me your hands!
Son of a bitch.
Get out.
Sergeant Richard Hall,
you have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say
can and will be used against you
in the court of law.
You have the right to an attorney.
If you cannot afford one...
Search the car.
The aisles are clear.
Sorry for the change in location.
What happened to the other team?
They apparently had complications.
We were instructed to take over.
Here it is.
It was damaged,
but we did our best to repair it.
As long as it works.
Helios isn't far away.
Wasn't anything in the car.
No?
That's cool.
We got plenty on 'em to put them away.
Just makes me wonder...
What were they doing out here?
How about I ask them in the morning?
That works for me. Great work, partner.
You too.
Hey, guys.
I know it's late,
I just wanted to touch base
about what we did tonight.
The last thing I ever thought I'd do
is turn on a fellow traveler...
but I really don't think
we had any other choice.
I guess we'll find out soon enough
if the Director agrees.
Anyway...
I just wanted to say
thanks for sticking by me.
Get some rest.
Can you stay?
I shouldn't.
Okay.
Tell me we did the right thing.
I believe we did.
But I guess we'll see.
Yeah.
We'll see.
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com