Previously on Travelers...
That new doctor thinks
she's your sister.
Yeah, she told me.
Have you been sent a messenger?
Are you authorized
by The Director to talk to me?
Then step away.
Protocol 6, Agent MacLaren.
There's a reason
we're so compartmentalized,
but there's teams of us
all over the world on missions,
and that's why...
Which is why there's a Protocol 6,
yeah, I get the rules,
but help me out here.
You think I haven't seen
that white dude around?
Is that how you got these new wheels?
You got a sugar daddy?
This is where any idea
you have of us ends.
I'll be right down!
Hey.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
That's all right.
It's the same price
whether I'm waiting or playing.
At least you're cute.
How do you know? You can't even see me.
Well... You sound cute.
All I'm saying is that trying to achieve
any true level of intimacy
over the Internet
is like trying to
save the environment using oil.
Mm. I love scented oils.
Are you hard?
So... if you don't want to do that...
what do you want to do?
I want you tell me about
when you were happiest.
I thought I was never
gonna see her again.
And it made me so happy to...
to know that she was gonna be okay.
You know?
That's beautiful.
What?
You really do sound hot.
Like, "dad hot."
Yeah. Thanks. Uh...
Look, Candy, you seem
like a lovely girl,
and I'm sorry for
what's about to happen,
but this conversation is over.
But we just...
Traveler 4019...
welcome to the 21st.
Thank you.
Status report! Everyone all right?
All set.
Let's get to work.
Someone should check on Donner.
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
We've got multiple bodies
and remnants of the bomb out back.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, it looks like
some kind of adult industry
web cam operation.
Anything on these cameras?
Nah, they're all fried.
Even the servers.
Survivors?
None.
Bomb was placed right
next to the gas line.
Where's the bomber's body?
No idea.
Local PD are canvassing the neighborhood
to see if anyone saw
them leaving the scene.
He's alive?
Well, assuming it's a "he."
Forensics should be here
any minute to do a sweep.
Why don't I go back to the office,
see what I can dig up about
the victims and this company?
Make me do the dirty work?
I called it.
Philip, you there?
What happened?
None of the girls survived,
and Donner's missing.
Missing?
He should be dead.
If the Traveler arrived,
he would've defused the bomb
like he was supposed to.
If he misfired...
Donner would have died. I know.
It doesn't make any sense.
What do you want to do?
Search the deep web for an S.O.S.
If the Traveler made it,
hopefully he'll reach out.
In the meantime,
send me the host's address.
Copy.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- You wanted to see me?
- Trevor, yes.
Uh, please have a seat.
How're you doing?
Everything okay?
Transcendent.
Uh, I wanted to talk to you
about your physics midterm last week.
Uh... Not bad, right?
Well... also not good.
I had a meeting with
Mr. Morrissy yesterday,
and he believes you've been cheating.
What?
That's ridiculous.
Well, he wants to give you a zero.
No, I-I mean, I put in the work.
I got 90%. I told you I would.
You believe him?
You got every question right
except the last three.
Yeah, they were...
Which were also correct,
but you scratched out
to not seem suspicious.
Now, Mr. Morrissy thinks
you had the answer key,
and to be honest, Trevor,
it's hard to dispute that.
I'm sorry.
What are the repercussions?
Well, I found a compromise.
I have convinced him
to allow you one more
crack at the midterm
under both of our supervision tomorrow.
Oh, uh...
Okay.
Why don't you come by
for third period today
and I'll help you study?
I'll be there.
Oh no!
Hi!
Gonna be extra good
for Mommy today, okay?
Hey.
Hey. I just got your message.
Jeffrey will be fine.
The rash is just
a common reaction to a vaccine,
but I can come over and check
on him later, if you'd like.
Uh, thank you, but no, that's okay.
I-I have a meeting.
A meeting?
I have a hearing today.
Jeffrey's father wants custody.
Oh. Why don't you just let him have it?
I'm the boy's mother.
No, actually, you're not.
And it would make it
a lot easier to go on missions.
I'm not leaving my son
in the custody of that man,
and that's all there is to it.
Well, then you're gonna
have to fight for him.
I know.
Oh, my god.
Oh, my god!
Oh, my god! No!
No!
Oh!
This is all my fault!
This is all my fault.
- Hey, boss?
- Yeah?
I sent you Donner's address.
Thanks.
If you were injured in the field
and needed to patch yourself up,
where would you go?
Pharmacy, veterinary clinic...
- Commercial kitchen...
- Hold on.
I'll get back to you.
FBI.
_
Aaron Donner.
He was a regular.
I'd do private shows for him,
twice a day sometimes,
until things got weird.
He started sending packages,
and our policy is not
to encourage that sort of thing,
so I didn't respond.
Aaron blamed the company
for coming between us,
and then the threats started.
Threats?
He'd send religious hate mail,
saying that God would make
everyone pay for their sins,
that a day of reckoning would come.
He was crazy!
And then this morning...
You're doing good.
He left me a voice mail
telling me not to come in,
that today was the day
he'd make them all pay.
I tried to warn the girls, but...
It's okay. You're being very helpful.
Excuse me.
Beth?
Can you do a search
on an Aaron Donner for me?
Aaron Donner?
Aaron Donner!
Do you know who I am?
I'm 3468.
If you were hurt in the blast,
I can take you to our medic.
I'm here to assist you.
Okay?
You can trust me.
These allegations are
fundamentally disgusting, David.
Marcy Warton is a client of yours!
She is not who you think she is.
Are you in a relationship with her?
It's purely platonic.
So you don't deny living with her?
Because I have a thorough report
from an Officer Jeff Conniker
that clearly implicates you
as her romantic partner.
Ken... you know I would never do that.
You're suspended until further notice.
- What?
- And don't think...
...that there won't be a full
investigation, David, because...
You know, just meet with her. Please.
Come see who we're talking about.
That's all I'm asking.
You won't change my mind.
Please, be seated.
Ms. Shannon, just so we're clear,
nobody's on trial today.
Okay?
This is just an opportunity
for both sides to state their case
so we can work to find a resolution
that's best for your son.
Have you no representation?
Actually, ma'am,
I was hoping you would
consider a postponement.
Sorry I'm late.
I trust anything my client
has said up until this point
will be struck from the record.
We weren't notified
you'd be joining us, Mister...?
Really? Pearson. We've met twice.
Right.
S-Sorry.
If I may be frank, your honor,
I believe my client feared
the prospect
of Mr. Conniker's retribution
in response to her
simply defending herself.
I'm here to remind her
that she's not alone.
Philip, do...
_
Hey. Welcome home.
Don't do that.
Do what?
That's what couples say,
when someone comes home,
the other one says, "Hey, welcome home,"
but we're not a couple, it's platonic.
Okay, what should I say, then?
Just say "hello" like a normal person.
Hello.
Hi.
What's going on?
Uh, Ken knows you're staying here.
Ken?
My boss, and I should've known
it was going to come out.
It's completely inappropriate.
Okay, then I'll leave.
I don't want you getting
in trouble for my actions.
No. No, no, no, no. I need you to stay.
We have to prove that you're not
who they think you are. That you're...
Batgirl?
That you're not the same person
that he met.
Oh, I've met Ken?
Ke... Yeah, like a dozen times. Ken.
Man, that hit on your head
really had an effect on you.
Just tell me about him.
I'll make it work.
Well, I'm glad you're so confident,
because I could lose my job, Marcy.
Hell, I could go to jail.
Okay, well, what's the plan?
Right, so, it's not so much a plan
as it is that he's coming
for dinner tonight.
Okay.
I just want what's best for my son.
Then start by paying child support.
Every time I come by to talk
to you about it, you assault me.
I assault you?
Is this true, Ms. Shannon?
Have you assaulted Mr. Conniker?
Are we really getting into abuse here?
You pay for everything in cash,
you're out crazy hours of the night.
I'm working.
And I think we all know
what your new job is.
Ms. Shannon is providing
for her child as best she can.
We're more concerned
about household environment
as a result of manner of income.
You know, I'm just
gonna come out and ask.
- Are you a ho now, or what?
- Mr. Conniker!
There's at least one old white
guy coming around all the time.
The money is coming from somewhere.
You watch your mouth!
- Carly, not helping.
- Shut up!
You have no idea who I am
or what I'm capable of.
Here's the rage we've talked about.
You haven't seen rage yet.
Freeze!
Whoa! Easy, partner!
Looks like we were just in time.
He was about to make a run for it.
Packed bag, money, passport.
You don't say.
Want to tell us where you were going?
Well... that went well.
Forget Protocol 3!
I want to kill that man!
As your lawyer, I advise against that.
Philip?
What's up?
Philip, can you arrange funds for me?
I've had some unforeseen expenses.
Sure. It'll be tomorrow.
Bets take a day.
How much do you need?
Really?
"Field of Reference" states
that the speed of an object in motion
is dictated in relation
from where you're viewing it.
Good. And how do you prove...
V ax = V ay - V XY.
When " y" is common in both vectors,
" y " is eliminated,
and leaves for " ax,"
the final answer.
Trevor, how have you learned all this?
Were you just not
applying yourself before?
Now that football's over,
I can be myself.
I don't have to conform
to anyone's expectations.
Right, but your parents,
your teachers, me...
we all want you to succeed,
with or without football.
You see that, right?
I feel that with you, yes.
Good.
But I'm tired of being told
who I should be,
what I should do...
I want to define my own future.
I have a book I think you'd like.
Here.
Now, uh, let's get back to it,
get you ready for the test.
The cameras are off. Talk to me.
I have nothing to say.
I can help you.
Just tell me what
happened with the bomb.
It blew up.
Did you make any attempt to defuse it?
Why would I do that?
A higher power wanted
that bomb to go off.
Cut the bullshit.
I know you're 4022, you know I'm 3468.
There's no other way this makes sense.
It was my mission to greet
your team upon arrival,
so you need to talk to me.
The longer you stay silent,
the less we can do.
There's nothing you can do.
You're in a tough spot, I get it.
I messed up my first mission too.
But you're not alone.
There are other Travelers.
If we have some information,
we can help you out of this.
What the hell is a Traveler?
Aaron Donner, I have a witness
that claims that you were
a longstanding client of hers.
That is, until the company
slapped a court order on you.
I follow the rule of God.
I'm pretty sure "thou shalt not kill"
is in your rulebook.
You were obsessed.
You terrorized the poor girl.
I was saving Mindy.
She'll see that in time.
You blew up her workplace
in order to save her?
It was God's will.
You're looking at three counts
of first-degree murder.
They were sinful.
They were?
Well, it's gonna take
some kind of divine intervention
to save you from lethal injection.
Capital punishment?
The state of Washington carries
the death sentence
for first-degree murder charges
with aggravated reasons.
I want a lawyer.
Now he wants a lawyer.
Yeah, we still got you
for an hour and seven minutes
before the presence of a lawyer
is mandatory.
Then I'll wait.
But I'm done talking.
Marce, I g...
Hi, David.
Leave a message. I'll call you back.
I'll let you know
when the forensics come in.
Thanks, partner.
Hi. I'm so glad you could join us.
Marcy?
Ken.
Uh, we got your text
that you were running late.
David is just opening the wine,
and I think dinner is almost ready.
How goes the battle?
Uh... Yeah.
David said your dog was sick.
My d...?
No, he's fine, it was indigestion.
Oh.
This is Marcy?
This is Marcy.
And, uh, now you know
why I wanted you to see her.
I don't want to rush dinner,
but everything's ready, so...
Do you want to just get started?
I hope you're hungry.
David made his famous pasta dish.
Huh.
Well, it's always that or chicken.
Yeah.
I'm sorry, Marcy,
you're gonna have to help me here.
I'm confused.
I understand you have some concerns
about David's conduct regarding me,
but I can assure you
that not only am I
no longer in his care,
but that our relationship
is purely platonic.
Platonic?
Marcy?
Excuse me. Work.
Hey, sorry,
I know I'm breaking protocol,
but my com...
I'm interrupting.
Agent MacLaren!
Don't be ridiculous, uh,
why don't you come and join us?
You know what, David?
This'll just take a second.
It's a little late for a home visit.
I don't mind. Nice summer evening.
Given what transpired
at the meeting today,
I wanted to follow up.
And... I have a warrant this time.
Come on in.
It's all pretty much the same
as last time you were here,
'cept for the John
in my closet, of course.
Ms. Shannon.
Carly.
Carly. I didn't agree
with how some aspects
of the meeting were handled,
but your behavior was concerning.
Yeah, I can tell by how
you're inside my house again.
I'm not on anyone's side
but Jeffrey Junior.
My job is to make sure
that whatever happens
is for his best welfare.
I get that's your job,
but I'm tired of being grilled.
I'm tired in general.
It is so hard doing this with no help.
Jeff is not a good man.
And he's a cop, so I can't say anything.
I can't go to anyone.
He's doing this
because I won't be with him.
He's punishing me.
Seriously, he's FBI,
and she works with him.
Though he can neither
confirm nor deny it.
It's a lot cooler when he says it.
I tried to call.
Is everything all right?
It-It will be, but what do you need?
I need you to replace my com.
It got busted.
How?
An altercation. I don't know how,
but apparently the new
Traveler's a misfire.
I've been dealing with
a psychopath all day.
All right, well,
I'll replace it first thing, okay?
Excuse me.
Could you please
show me some identification?
"Special Agent Grant MacLaren."
And you are?
Ken Palfy.
She works for you?
Marcy is my associate, yes.
In what capacity?
Well, that's...
...none of your goddamn business, Ken.
Sorry for interrupting.
Nice to see you again, David.
Uh... Aaron Donner?
Did you say anything to them?
No, but they have everything.
I'm familiar with your case.
Right. Um, let's see here.
Okay, so they found
your fingerprints on the bomb,
and DNA came through
with trace evidence that
places you at the scene.
If I have information.
Can I make a deal?
What? Like a plea bargain?
No, I want the charges dropped.
I want to go into witness protection,
new identity, everything.
That's not likely.
I've gained knowledge
of a secret organization
that's infiltrated our society.
What?
There's a huge network of them.
They operate outside the law,
and they're dangerous.
They've even infiltrated the FBI.
And how do you know all of this?
One of their operatives
gave himself away.
I think the Defense Department
would be very interested
to hear what I have to say.
Okay.
What is this organization?
They call themselves Travelers.
Agent MacLaren is one of them.
You must've been born with
a horseshoe up your ass.
Where's the rest of it?
You got three races
out of five with those stupid odds.
Consider yourself a lucky man.
7-3-2-5.
What?
Guys, we need to assemble
back at Ops A.S.A.P.
On my way.
Copy.
I just need to
finish up something at school.
Trevor? Your test isn't until 3:00.
Actually, Ms. Day,
I wanted to thank you
for lending me that book.
I really enjoyed it.
You finished it?
Uh-huh.
And I wanted to return the favor.
It was something that gave me comfort
during a very... lonely time.
Well, thank you.
Enjoy.
Hey. You know he's just
gonna hang himself in there.
My client wants an audience
with the D.A.'s office,
and they granted him that request.
- It's his right.
- He's insane.
Well, it's not for you to decide.
Really? 'Cause I've pretty much
already decided.
Hey. You wanted to see me?
Your letter of resignation
on my desk in an hour.
Turn in your I.D. and keys.
What?
And I think you'll understand
that I can't give you a reference.
This can't still be about Marcy.
What do you think?
I think that you met her,
you saw her, you know what she does.
Steal from people
with actual disabilities
for over a year?
Do you know how much
she's drained from the system?
Because I do. Dollar for dollar.
Do you know how many grants
we've been turned down for?
How many programs have been canceled
because I can't rely on the government
to even keep the lights on?
They won't support us,
but they don't give a shit
if they take from us.
She didn't do any of that.
And what does this have to do with me?
You helped that woman
commit social assistance fraud.
I had no idea!
But when you found out,
did you come to me?
Did you? Did you say, "Hey, Ken,
friend, boss...
Why don't you take a look at this?"
No. And now we're out her
base benefits for two years,
not to mention half the cost
of her apartment,
outings, time.
I know you did things for her
out of your own pocket.
How can you not be furious at that?
It's important work she's doing.
David...
Wake up, man.
She was playing you.
She was playing you then,
she's playing you now.
You're right.
When I thought Marcy was somebody who...
needed my help,
I did do things out of my own pocket.
On my own time,
because I care about my clients.
So who are you gonna get to
do my case load now? Malcolm?
'Cause he never does home visits.
He never takes his clients
to their appointments
or teaches them how to socialize.
Will he know that
when Jason refuses to eat,
you got to pretend that
you're at his grandma's house?
I have put in more overtime than anyone,
and we don't get paid overtime!
But good luck!
'Cause you're worried about
a few dollars!
Try several thousand!
Okay! Well, that's a lot!
Yes, it is!
Mr. Donner...
The Department of Justice
doesn't take kindly
to having its time wasted.
In fact, that's why I'm here
and not the District Attorney herself.
Assistant D.A. Peckham,
my client stands behind his testimony.
Know that we are taking
this very seriously.
State your name
for the camera, then proceed.
Is that feed being broadcast in any way?
Internal use only.
My name is Aaron Donner,
and I have information
on a secret organization
that operates worldwide.
They call themselves Travelers.
A terrorist organization?
Similar, yes,
and they operate outside the law,
infiltrate government agencies.
Yes, I was informed
you even implicated a federal agent.
That's a very serious
allegation, Mr. Donner.
I was approached by him.
He revealed himself as a double agent.
Said that he was part
of a large network,
and that if I joined them,
he could help me with my charges.
Help you how?
He just said that he could
help me if I was one of them.
And how is it
that no governmental department
is even aware of these Travelers?
Because they operate in secret.
Mr. Donner, I'm gonna need
something more concrete
than your conspiracy theories.
We're done here.
He's right there.
Why don't you ask him?
Why don't you ask? Ask him yourself.
Ask him about Travelers. He knows.
Aaron, you're confused.
Special Agent MacLaren,
if you could please escort Mr. Donner
back into federal custody,
where we can process him accordingly?
No, look. Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
Wait! Wait! I can prove it.
I am one of them.
What are you talking about?
I'm Traveler 4022.
I will tell you everything.
How we communicate,
how we receive our orders,
our-our missions, our protocols,
just, please.
To finally live in the world
above ground,
I will not give that up.
I'll tell you everything.
Continue.
We communicate on secure servers
in the deep web.
I can show you.
You'll see messages that correspond
with all the missions that we've done...
heists, assassinations.
The Van Huizen explosion? That was us.
And how can you determine if someone
is one of these Travelers?
We use a com device that's injected
just beneath the ear.
That's how we communicate
within our team.
And you have one of these devices?
No. I was supposed to get one,
but my team was killed shortly
after their arrival, so...
Arrival from where?
The future!
Please, I am telling the truth here.
I swear. Just check... Check his com.
Just look for yourself.
Look for yourself.
Don't.
Agent MacLaren was sent here
to brief me on my first mission.
If I go down, you go down too.
I wish you hadn't said that.
Is this true, Special Agent MacLaren?
Are you one of these Travelers?
Yes.
I'm Traveler 3468.
And I'm not alone.
Traveler 4022,
you are accused of treason.
Your trial begins now.
Give him five more minutes.
He's already had 30.
I'm not missing dinner with my kids
because the ex-football star
had better things to do.
Goodnight, Grace.
Dammit, Trevor.
Traveler 4022
failed to defuse the bomb
that led to the death of his team.
I'm sure it was
a very difficult situation
to face alone.
But he wasn't alone.
No.
You offered 4022 your assistance.
Many times, but he was afraid.
And do you think
this excuses his actions?
No, I don't.
I practiced defusing that bomb
a thousand times...
But when I got here, it didn't work.
I swear, I tried it.
The Director didn't give me enough time.
And what was I supposed to do? Die?
Instead, you betrayed all of us.
It is now time to vote.
3569.
0115.
3326.
What's going to happen to me?
Traveler 4022,
you have been found guilty of treason,
for which the punishment
is death by immediate overwrite.
No. No! No! No!
No! No!
No!
No. No!
Traveler 4024...
welcome to the 21st century.
Thank you.
Yes?
Carly, I was, uh...
passing through the area
and wanted to drop by.
Just for a moment.
I have another appointment.
What's going on? Is something wrong?
I just wanted you to know
you're not alone.
I'm going to help you.
I've seen this system
fail women like you
too many times before,
and I'd like to see this story
have a better ending.
Okay. Um... Thank you.
The father does have a lot of leverage,
so in between now
and the next proceeding,
we need to strengthen your case.
Red flag number one...
your liquid income.
I swear to you,
I didn't make that money by...
It doesn't matter.
As far as I care,
you did what you had to
in order to feed your child.
But... the allegation was made,
and so we have to combat it.
How?
You need to get a job.
I'll help you get set up.
Let's meet later this week.
What's wrong?
Donner got off.
Of the death penalty.
He's still gonna get life in prison.
With a chance of parole.
Not for a long time.
He's just lucky
he killed the right people.
What does that mean?
Nobody cares about the deaths
of a few sex workers.
Just sweep it underneath the rug.
It's not right.
For Chrissake.
We need to talk.
Didn't bring your FBI friend with you?
No. Wasn't necessary.
This should cover
all the benefits that I received
under David's care,
with interest.
Is this legal?
Do you care?
David needs to maintain
his position here.
He's doing a bit of work for us.
That's blackmail.
I could take the money back,
if you prefer,
give it to your replacement.
But David seems to like you.
Tell him he can
come back to work on Monday.
Bye, Ken.
Hell of a first assignment.
Well, honestly, I think
even going to prison's better
than where I just came from.
It's that bad?
I was kind of hoping
the work we've been doing
would have some effect,
especially Helios.
If anything, it's going the other way.
Have we at least found
more fuel for the reactor?
I shouldn't have said anything.
Protocol 2.
You know we're not supposed to...
Yeah, no, I get it. I get it.
Be strong.
Rough jump into the 21st?
I'm Traveler 2587.
So, you're one of The Director's
abandoned orphans too?
I'm on mission,
and you're breaking Protocol 2.
Some mission.
I trust in the grand plan.
Give it some time.
Then we'll talk.
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com