Previously on Travelers.
FBI!
Our mission was to acquire a
component from Russian Travelers
and deliver it
to another team for testing,
but they got greedy.
A Traveler team turned on you?
He must be new.
We gotta talk about this family.
We're not a family.
Mother, father, and son.
Did your host have a family?
David. His name is David.
Your priorities
are all outta whack!
We came here with a team of five.
Well, we're down to two now.
Don't think the future
doesn't get its hands dirty.
Dad?
Dad!
Please, stop!
Daddy! Stop!
Dad! Stop the car!
You're scaring me!
Dad! Stop! Please!
Dad!
Daddy, stop! Stop!
Dad, stop!
Dad, stop, please!
Welcome to the 21st.
I'm Traveler 3468.
3117.
3890.
3892.
What's happening?
Misfire.
Shit.
Uh...
Hi. I'm Grant.
What's your name?
Charlotte.
Charlotte, it's okay.
I'm a policeman.
No, really. I... I am.
See?
It says "FBI".
Well, it's like a policeman.
It's better, even!
Look, my friends and I
need to have a... a talk with your...
your mom and your dad and your brother
about what just happened.
Why was he doing that?
Why did you do that?
Look, I know
you're upset. I would be, too.
Just... just let us... let us talk
with your family, and everything
will be all right.
I promise.
Sweetie, do you have any other
family that live around here?
10 clicks back down the road.
Grandmother, mother's side.
Your side.
How about if I take you there?
I want to go with my mom.
You go with the nice man, Charlotte.
We'll be back in a few days
and we'll be a family again.
Okay, that's my car over there.
The black one.
Can you wait there for me?
Car was going pretty fast.
Maybe she was moving inside of it?
It's a tough T.E.L.L.
for the Director to calculate.
Well, it doesn't matter, it happened.
I'll deal with her now.
Who is your historian?
She was going to be.
This isn't nearly enough to set you up,
so put it on
"Non-Event Horizon" in the fourth.
It's a horse race.
Tomorrow. Look it up.
This is the device.
Keep it upright.
What are you gonna do with her?
I guess I'll just take her to Grandma's
and explain that Mom and Dad
will be back after the mission...
obviously without
mentioning the mission,
which is in just over 48 hours,
and you're down a team member.
- Can you make the adjustment?
- We'll be ready.
Go. We can brief them.
Good.
Protocol 5 till then.
Okay, boss. It's done.
Tip went out as of this morning.
I wonder how many
misfires there have been
since we started this.
First wave was upwards of 30%.
Wow! Nobody told me that.
Yeah. Me neither.
Would you have still volunteered?
Probably.
I mean, if you think about it,
what other choice did we...
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
Carly...
Carly?
Trevor?
I'm over here.
You all right?
My head.
Concussion.
Can you tell if Marcy's breathing?
I can't see her face.
Slow and shallow.
Philip?
Philip!
What do we know?
Not where we are,
not for how long,
or who abducted us,
but it's been a couple
of hours, at least.
My mouth is dry.
No eyes or ears on us that I can see.
We shouldn't count on it.
Ah! They cut out my com.
I can't feel it.
Yeah, same.
I gotta stop getting
whacked on the head.
I'm a blank here.
Where's the boss?
MacLaren was on his way
to Grandma's house.
So he wasn't with us when we were taken.
That's good. There's a chance
he'll find us before the mission.
Well, he'd better hurry up.
Wheelchairs?
Whoever they are,
they plan on moving us.
Don't know about that.
They're giving us fluids intravenously.
I think we're gonna be
in these chairs a while.
And it's been a Lotta years
since I felt this sensation,
but... it's pretty unmistakable.
Catheter.
Oh, God.
- Is that what that is?
- Yes, ma'am.
Do me a favor.
Don't say anything remotely suggestive.
It could get very painful over here.
Don't make me laugh.
I'm serious!
It's like a 17-year-old
male's default setting.
Look who showed up to work.
Hey.
Thought you were driving to Olympia?
I was delayed.
Where were you this morning?
Oh, Kathryn, uh,
she needed me to pick up
an antique chair for a client
because it wouldn't fit in her car.
Why? What'd I miss?
You know, the funny thing
about court dates is,
when you miss one,
you don't get another one next week.
You get it next month or next year.
That was this morning.
It's cool, I covered for you again,
but you're the lead on this one, Mac.
- I'm sorry, man.
- Don't apologize to me.
You got one angry prosecutor
on your hands.
Well, hello, sir.
Didn't catch your name on the way in.
I was unconscious.
I'm Trevor.
So here's a thing...
I got this geography test tomorrow
that I really gotta study for.
Capital cities, countries...
Am I gonna be able to do that?
'Cause it's pretty likely
that my parents are gonna
ground me again if I fail.
Know what that means?
Having to watch hours of golf
on television with Gary!
Don't do it to me, man.
Where are you taking him?
Hey, asshole!
I said, where are you taking him?
Bye!
I know it goes against your instincts...
but don't waste any more energy
trying to get free from your restraints.
It's not gonna happen.
Hello?
Marce?
Hey. It's me.
Um, I thought you said you were
gonna be coming home early
for... for dinner tonight,
and, uh, I couldn't decide
what we were gonna have,
so I brought the ingredients
for basically two different...
...dinners,
and I was just curious to see
what you'd... you'd like
to have tonight, so...
Yeah, one of them would be, like, uh,
roast chicken with vegetables,
and the other one,
it's more of a...
it's like a pasta thing I do,
and, um...
well, now... now I'm talking to you
as if you're actually on the phone.
I don't know why I do that.
That's, uh...
Well, that's weird. So
anyway, give me a call,
or I will see you
when you get back here.
Hopefully soon.
Okay. I'm gonna
start on the roast chicken...
unless you really want the pasta,
in which case call me back.
It's David.
And I'm doing it again. Bye.
Ow...
We're here, Marcy.
How bad is it?
My head and my neck.
Probably...
just whiplash from the impact.
This is the worst hospital
in the world or...
We've been abducted.
I obviously vomited on myself.
Anybody clock when?
Probably before we got here.
The stink's not as bad as it was.
Sorry.
Smells around here
aren't going to improve much.
We've only met one of our captors.
He came and wheeled Philip
out of here a while ago.
Never said a word. That's all we know.
We know they intend to keep us
alive for a while at least.
They've got us on I.V.s.
How long have I been out?
A few hours longer than us.
Now don't
be like that, Mr. Giant!
Pick me.
Take me instead of her!
I'm asking nice here!
Come on!
_
What? Am I supposed to answer?
Who have I told what?
I don't understand.
_
No. I've never seen him before.
No.
He's the father of my child,
and he's a police officer,
so if I were you people, I'd...
_
I don't understand the question.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Who am I talking to?
Why don't you show yourself?
_ Look.
I just take care of my son all day.
My specialty is mac and cheese.
He's with his father today.
Don't you hurt him!
Don't you dare hurt him!
If that child
is harmed
in any way...
I will hunt you down...
whoever you are,
whenever you are...
And I will kill you.
_
Hey.
Sorry to interrupt.
There's someone here
who'd like to see you.
A David Mailer?
Who?
"A mutual friend of Marcy," he said.
Sorry. I can send him away.
He gave me the impression
that you knew each other.
No, no, that's... uh, send him in.
David Mailer, sir.
- Thanks, Beth.
- Hi.
David Mailer.
She just... said that.
So FBI headquarters, huh?
It's a field office.
Uh, h-h-ow did you...?
Uh, the address
was on the...
the card that you gave me.
I gave you?
Yeah, well, you slipped it under my door
when I was out a while back.
We spoke on the phone later that night.
You don't remember.
- No.
- How do I know this Marcy person?
Well, I kinda know
that she works with you, so, um...
Well, obviously, I can neither
confirm nor deny that.
Which is cool, and I totally get that,
and I know that what
you're doing is very important,
and... she really hasn't mentioned me?
The point of this visit is?
Marcy didn't come home last night.
Not "home" home.
She's just... she's staying
with me platonically,
but I was expecting her for dinner.
W-When did you last see her?
Yesterday morning, when she left.
I'm sure she's on
some sort of secret FBI medical thing,
but I was worried
and I just wanted
to hear from you that...
Okay.
Um, I'm gonna look into this.
Why don't you leave
your number with Beth,
and I'll give you
a call if I find anything.
Wait. You don't know
where she is either?
Beth? Beth,
can you please take Mr. Mailer's
contact information? Thank you.
Uh...
Marcy, it's MacLaren.
Carly?
Trevor? Philip?
Shit.
Now exhale.
Feel the silence between your breaths.
Your heart beating in your chest.
Constant as the reactor beneath.
Giving light.
Heat.
Time.
Philip!
Oh, thank God!
I thought I was alone.
I'm really gonna take it personally
if you don't pick me next time.
Hey. Did you see Carly?
They just left with her.
I woke up in an empty room
and they brought me here.
I don't even know how long I was there.
Hours?
Wait. Are you hurt?
Thanks to John Hentrick, no.
Inventor of airbags, 1952.
But I am hurting in other ways.
Withdrawal.
I haven't been able to go
more than 18 hours between doses
since we got here,
and I can pretty much tell you,
without looking at a clock,
we're coming up on that number.
Not the rehab facility
I thought that I'd end up in.
Marcy and I were meditating.
You should, too.
There's no way...
Trust me, Philip.
It'll help.
I promise.
Now exhale.
You're the one who told me
to take the red flag off
these same four people.
Well, now there's
no sign of any sign of them.
One of them might be missing.
Just do it, please.
I'll put in the request,
but even a priority
facial recognition search
isn't likely to turn up anything.
Let's try to be a little more
positive, shall we?
Okay, sure, I'm positive
that I'm the one they're gonna
complain to for using up
NSA mainframe time
on something you called a false alarm.
Jesus! David.
What are you doing out here?
Just waiting to hear
if you've got anything yet.
Well, in the 11 minutes
since you left my office?
No. I have employed resources.
Like?
If Marcy's face shows up
practically anywhere there's
a closed-circuit TV camera,
we'll know her location.
Great. Tell me how I can help.
You can go home.
Oh, my God. You're just like her.
Would you stop? You know what?
I'm gonna help you out,
whether you like it or not.
How about that?
What're you gonna do,
follow me on your bike?
Ah-hah!
She did tell you about me.
You just gave it all away.
You know I have a bike.
Your right pant leg
is tucked into your sock.
I was giving you
the benefit of the doubt.
Okay, I get it.
I'm not qualified, but just know this...
Marcy's welfare is very important to me.
When I find her, I'll call you.
Or better still...
she'll just come home.
Okay, so if I don't hear
from you by what, like, 5:00...
I'm getting the feeling
we're not gonna make our next mission.
That is the least
of my problems right now.
Come on, Philip.
You're stronger than that.
You have no idea what this feels like,
so why don't you...
I can't see.
I can't see!
Really?
You're gonna pass over me again?
How many of them are there?
What did they do?
Just the one you've already met.
There was an old-style television
in an open space, like a warehouse.
In this building?
Must be.
Then they asked questions.
Just words on the television.
"When are you from?"
Shit.
They know.
No. There's nothing to know.
Well, they obviously know something.
They have Jeffrey.
- What?
- My son.
They showed him to me on the television.
They have him.
I saw.
Uh, wha...
Whoa, whoa. Guys?
What's he doing?
He's injecting something
into your I.V. line.
Whoa-whoa-whoa!
Uh, what, uh...
I...
Never mind.
No. No-no-no!
Stop, stop. That's too much.
No! Stop! He'll overdose! Stop!
That's okay.
It's what I needed.
That amount of heroin
will slow your respiration rate
and your heart rate
down to dangerous levels. Philip?
You need to stay with us, okay?
- I'm here.
- Philip, stay awake.
Philip! Listen to Marcy!
I can hear you, I'm...
Philip. No. No, no!
No! No! No! Philip!
Carly! Make sure he stays awake!
Philip, you stay awake, okay?
Hello?
My name is Marcy Warton.
I work at a library.
I don't know why you've taken me here.
I haven't done anything wrong.
Hello? Marcy! Yes.
Oh, thank God. I was so worried.
I've been freaking out.
No. No, I get it. Yeah. Mum's the word.
Yeah, no, of course,
you're... you're busy.
Okay. Well, when you do, I'll be here.
Yeah, all right, yeah.
We'll have the chicken.
Yeah, chicken sounds good.
I can't wait. Okay.
Yeah. Bye-bye.
Philip!
Philip, you do not
have permission to sleep!
We asked you a question!
I'm still here.
Good. That's good.
Talk to us.
Tell us about your parents.
Where do they live?
Yeah. You never talk about them.
What's your mother's name?
2144.
Stay in the here and now, Philip...
Do you remember
the taste of the water?
Recycled so many times
it could never be made pure again?
Shut up!
This can't be heroin.
No, no, no, it is.
Or at least the first one was,
and I am more grateful for it
than I care to admit,
but the second one was something else.
Something I think would only work
on someone who's been modified
to be an historian.
What is it?
Memory...
pouring in like a flood.
Like the Helios tidal wave.
I can't stop it.
I'm drowning in it!
I want you to breathe deeply
- and listen to my voice...
- You can't compete with this.
Do you remember
the taste of metal in the air?
The stink of 20,000 souls
crammed into a shelter
designed for half that number?
Don't talk about the past!
You mean the future.
I mean stop talking.
Do you guys remember
when the reveille bell rang
at the exact moment
the dome in shelter 41 collapsed?
It was exactly at 0600...
almost like cause and effect.
The bell rang
and woke everyone up
a split second before they died.
As a boy, I remember thinking,
"That's so unfair."
Philip, keep your mouth shut.
I'm not sure that I can.
Philip...
Philip!
I'll try.
Philip. Philip?
I'll try. I'll try. I'll try, I'll try.
Philip!
I'll try, I'll try...
Philip?
Philip!
Where are you guys?
"No battle
plan survives contact... "
"Plans are useless."
"...You are planning to fail."
- "...Planning is indispensable."
- ...Franklin. Franklin...
"If you fail to plan,
you are planning to fail."
Benjamin Franklin.
"No battle plan..."
Battle plan...
"...survives contact with the enemy."
Helmuth Von Moltke.
"My mission..."
"...in life
is not merely to survive,
but to thrive..."
To thrive.
"And to do so with some passion...
"passion, some compassion,
some humor, and some style!"
Maya Angelou!
"This is the way the world ends..."
This is the way the world ends.
"This is the way the world ends."
"This is the way
the world ends."
"This is the way the world ends."
"This is the way the world ends..."
_
"...Not with a bang..."
"...but a whimper."
T.S.
...Eliot!
_
***
Well, it's a start.
What about 911 records?
E.M.T. calls?
Nothing. I've also tried
virtually every emergency room
in the Pacific Northwest.
You sure you don't want me
to call Agent Forbes?
No, he's got enough
on his plate.
Well, it's just that he asked me
to keep him updated on everything.
I said that I was sure, Beth.
How many freaking times
do you need me to say it?
Sorry. I'm having a bad day.
Well, now we all are.
Just let me know if you find anything.
Okay.
Oh, ho, ho! Come on!
Finally!
I've really been looking forward
to this, Mr. Giant.
Thank you so-o-o much.
Ha-hah!
I just hate being the last guy
picked, you know?
Drives me crazy.
I'm sure a guy like you understands.
Back soon!
All right, all right!
Hey-hey.
Freight elevator. Sweet ride.
Hey, are we going up or down?
I'm gonna guess down.
Up! You son of a bitch! You got me!
Can I help you?
Special Agent Grant MacLaren.
I'm with the FBI.
I'm looking for a silver van
that was brought here yesterday,
about 3:30 in the afternoon.
Oh, the one that got T-boned
by the Peterbilt?
T-boned by the Pe...?
Yeah. Sure. Show me.
Uh...
Hey, FBI doing traffic accidents now?
No.
Well, what's this about?
It's about you showing me the van,
and not asking me
anymore goddamn questions.
Oh. 'Kay.
There she is.
Total write-off.
Do you know if any of
the occupants were badly hurt?
Oh, we don't get reports
on the incidents.
Uh, the airbags went off,
I can tell you that.
Okay. Thanks for your time.
Uh, you wanna dust it for prints
or hit it with a little
blue light or nothin'?
Knock yourself out.
Wow!
This is great up here.
Nice big space, daylight.
That's a big old CRT.
I'm guessing...
late '90s.
Those flat-screen
sons of guns are heavy, huh?
Probably not so much for you.
I bet you didn't even need
help from your friends.
You do have friends, right?
Are they government,
or is this a private contractor gig?
Whoa, a question on the TV! I love it.
It's like that show my mom
watches after supper.
You know, most people would ask
"Where are you from?"
But hey, I don't want to offend anybody,
if English is a second language.
Maybe it's a typo, huh?
_
What a coincidence! I was gonna
ask you the same thing,
since you're the ones
who brought me here, but hey,
like my humanities teacher,
Mr. Warchowski, says...
"Why are we all here?" Right?
_
Guess.
'Kay, technically,
I'll be 18 in October,
but I'm kind of an old soul.
What about you, Mr. Giant?
When's your birthday?
Back when I was starting quarterback,
our mission was to win the division,
obviously.
You look like you played a little ball
in your day, Mr. Giant.
Then again...
a deaf-mute like yourself
wouldn't be able to hear
the quarterback call plays,
would he?
Ho-ho!
I'll catch you later, man!
What did you say to them?
I got 'em right where I want 'em.
Excuse me.
Officer Boyd?
You got a second?
Sure. Excuse me.
What about the, uh...
The CCTV is down.
What the hell are you doing here?
I thought I made it very clear last time
that you were not
to communicate with me.
Yeah, well, screw Protocol 6.
My team is missing.
For how long?
Since yesterday morning.
Apparently. I just found out
about it a while ago.
All of them! Their coms
and locators are offline.
They don't show up on GPS.
What about the deep web backchannel?
That's the first place I looked!
There's no sign of them.
It's like they've disappeared.
The FBI has far more
resources than I do.
I'm running a facial recognition search
through the NSA.
Which could take forever,
if it works at all.
I know! But what else can I do?
They've all been
previously red-flagged...
by the previous me.
I found their vehicle
in... in a salvage yard.
It had been T-boned by a Vanderbilt...
or some damn thing.
Trail ends there, I'm guessing?
Okay, you need to
consider the possibility
that they've been taken
out of the equation.
What equation?
The Director's.
I've seen entire teams
I was supposed to work
on a mission with just disappear
into thin air.
Probably taken out
by another traveler team
under orders.
You know as well as I do,
the future has
the ultimate power over us.
If the Director doesn't
like the way we perform,
a decision we make...
W-W-Why them?
I'm responsible for my team's actions.
Well, how badly
have you messed up lately?
Maybe you're next.
I don't buy that.
What do you want from me?
My team has been tasked
to participate in a mission
that requires six people,
minimum, to pull it off.
- When?
- Tonight.
And that's what you're here about?
You want my team's help?
The mission comes first.
The mission's canceled, MacLaren!
You just don't get it yet.
Thanks for your help.
Hold on.
If you get a real lead,
I will help you go after them.
Okay? I'll help you.
But if I'm right,
and it's the Director...
I know.
I hope I'm wrong.
Torture doesn't work, people.
It's been proven!
You know, whoever you are,
whatever information
you think you're getting
is of almost no value.
_
Philip.
His name is Philip.
He was in the van with me
when we were...
_
I don't understand the question.
I mean, if you're asking how old...
No! No!
Where's the rest of your team?
M.I.A.!
We have to cancel the mission.
What about all those people?
I was hoping the Director
would send you
a replacement team, but...
Maybe there's still a way.
No, no. Forget it,
the mission's canceled.
The Director will have an alternative.
We have to trust that.
I'm sorry about your team.
I haven't given up just yet.
There's no way they can do the mission
with so few personnel.
All those people are gonna die.
They already did.
We just weren't there
to prevent it from happening.
Just hope the boss
isn't in the same situation
as we are somewhere.
I have an idea that could end this,
if the opportunity
presents itself again.
But I want everyone to decide.
We may not be better off.
I say go for it.
How?
You're gonna try to talk me out of it.
Why?
It's insane.
Marcy!
Philip? You're alive?
I saw... I saw you die, they showed me.
- No, I'm right here.
- No, on the television. They...
They shot you in the chest.
No, no, no, no, Marcy, Marcy,
he's right in front of you.
Marcy, look at me.
You were in those clothes,
you were slumped over...
Oh, this is good.
What? How?
Think about it!
They probably don't even
have Carly's kid!
They're just pushing buttons
and seeing what happens.
I don't know who,
but this still gives us power
we don't have much of.
We don't have any power.
Please?
Please...
Before you take him away, would you...?
Hang on!
Jesus Christ!
He's alive.
He's cold. Dead for hours.
I've gotta get 'em out of here.
Look for a key! Check his pockets!
- I got it! I got it!
- Got it?
Carly!
Carly.
She's unconscious,
but strong pulse, though.
It's me. I'm here.
You're late.
Won't happen again.
Gonna get you outta here, okay?
How many days?
Three.
I had to end it.
What... What was this about?
Why did he do it?
It wasn't him. He was a hired gun.
We never found out who it was.
I'm gonna get you out of this.
Wait. What about the mission?
No, it's canceled.
Couldn't do it without you.
There was no way.
What? What is it?
What if that's what this was about?
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com