TRAVELER D-13 COUGHS
Where's the quantum frame?
CARLY:
He asked you a question.
SHE SCOFFS
Do it. It's what I want anyway.
JENNY: You've been doing
what we want for months, why stop now?
How many members
of the Faction are here?
It could be anybody we meet.
And there could be thousands more
in the quantum frame.
That's why the Director wanted
us to destroy it.
JENNY: The Director ordered
you to build the thing.
I mean, how can you people
not see the irony of that?
You just follow it blindly, no matter what.
That's the difference between us.
No. The Faction abducts innocent people
and overwrites them.
That's the difference between us.
What you do is murder.
What you do is opportunism,
like taking hosts just before they die
is so fucking ethical?
- Yeah. That's exactly what it is.
Hey, guess what?
Everybody is going to die.
Some sooner than others.
When we're from,
everybody in the 21st is long gone
and for what they did to this planet,
good riddance.
Here's what's gonna happen, Jenny.
We're gonna stop this pandemic,
and then we are gonna hunt down
every member of the Faction in the 21st.
The Director's shut down in the future
and most of your team will be dead
in less than two weeks
so good luck.
If you're done questioning her
I'd like to take a few tissue samples,
run some tests.
Please. Whatever you need to do.
TREVOR COUGHS
We should send out an SOS
onto the deep web
and let other Travelers know
what's going on.
CARLY:
They'll be monitoring our backchannels.
If the Faction's overwritten
every single federal agent
that was in that room
with the quantum frame
I don't have those assets to use either.
GRACE:
OK, this is not that complicated.
TREVOR SCOFFS
I'm saying
the Director can fix this.
We need to fix the Director.
The Director exists in the future.
And its reactor's already shut down.
Those are big problems, Grace.
The plan's already in place.
When it became apparent
that the Grand Plan
would take longer than our initial
projections, the Director sent a team
to refine uranium as fuel to extend its
operational life.
A few kilos would be enough.
All we have to do
is take the fuel to the location
where the Director will eventually be built
and it'll be there when the time comes.
Without the Faction knowing.
How the hell are we gonna do that?
Whoa! They outsmarted us!
Whoop-dee-doo! Get over it!
They can't outsmart the Director.
Even if we can just get it back online
for a few seconds
that's all the time it'll need
to take back control.
And you know where this uranium is?
Pull up a map.
GEIGER COUNTER CLICKS
HE SIGHS It's hot in there.
Ever think you'd hear yourself
complain about the heat?
HE CHUCKLES
- No.
Radiation, maybe.
You really want to lose another game?
DOOR KNOCKS
Who the hell is that?
LOCK BUZZES
Who are you?
I'm 4112.
What're you doing here?
- FORBES: I just received orders
to provide backup at this location.
You can lower your gun.
Backup for what?
Damn, I was kind of hoping
you could tell me.
I'm sorry, guys.
Squeaky little kid took me by surprise
when she first started talking.
I missed the whole first part.
Yeah, messengers are weird.
Yeah, she said something about
uranium, maybe?
Yeah, you heard right.
We're refining it.
Fuel for the Director.
FORBE: So how the hell
do you guys get it to the future?
We don't.
- MARK: Yeah, we make it here in the 21st
then we put it away for the Director
to find it in a few hundred years.
Yeah, we're right on schedule,
so I don't know what we need backup for.
Yeah?
GUNSHOT
How much have you produced?
HE STAMMERS:
2.4 kilos.
Why... Why did you do that?
Show me where.
Thank you.
- GUNSHOTS
We're clear.
LOCK BUZZES
It's in there.
Take it all.
JEFFREY CRIES
- It's OK, it's OK, it's OK.
Shh...
- PHONE RINGS
It's OK.
CHILD CRIES
Hello?
Hey, Sarge.
- CHILD CRIES
Yeah, no, I'm sorry, my son's sick
and I had to, uh-
Yeah, no, no, I understand.
Yeah, I'll come down
as soon as his mum gets home.
OK. Thanks, Sarge.
HE COUGHS
Yeah. That's it.
TV REPORTER:
.,.yet to be named virus.
It has infected thousands
of people around the world
with the highest infection rates
among the most vulnerable -
pregnant women, children, the elderly,
and those with lowered immune systems.
Many are turning to emergency rooms
in hopes of treatment
{but infection rates are on the rise'
with nearly every hospital bed in the city
now occupied.
The mayor is expected
to make a statement shortly
however, the epidemic has...
- SHE COUGHS
city and state authorities suggesting that
everyone stay in their homes.
What did he do to me?
We just took some blood and tissue samples.
You're still intact.
You understand, don't you?
No.
You used me.
CUFFS CLICK
- Philip...
Come on.
I was on a mission, just like you.
We want the same thing.
We just go about it a different way.
We forget about...
the protocols and the Director, and all
those limitations, and we just...
do what needs to be done,
what's right.
Like Galloway and Aleksander.
That's very different than murdering
almost a third of the population.
To save everyone else.
Not a bargain I can make.
Well, it's done.
There's no going back now.
We're not giving up just yet.
You should.
Your people won't be able to stop this
and there's nothing an historian can do.
Just think about the time you've got left.
Let's get out of here.
When I found you,
you had swallowed a bottle of pills.
Why?
Guilt?
I feel no guilt at all.
This is for the greater good,
and I can't believe you don't see that!
Then why the pills?
Because I was trying to end it
before the virus ran its course.
You feel sick now?
It's only gonna get worse.
This virus is designed
to keep the infected alive
as long as possible, to help the spread
and make the authorities think
that it's not as serious as it really is.
So when people start to really die,
it's too late.
And the last days of it
are not something I want to go through.
Well, now you're gonna suffer...
along with everyone else...
for every last minute.
SHE SIGHS
They're keeping a pretty low profile.
MACLAREN:
I think that's the idea.
OK.
Watch our six and listen in on com.
Copy that.
HE KNOCKS
Who is it?
3468, on a Protocol Alpha mission.
LOCK BUZZES
3224. What's going on?
CARLY:
We need to pull up the delivery.
Kit's urgent..
'TRAVELER 3224: Is this a joke?'?
No.
The reactor won't need more fuel
for hundreds of years.
It's the here and now we're worried about.
This “flu” that's going around
is about to become a pandemic.
And what's that got to do with us?
- Let's talk inside, shall we?
All we have is in the lab down the hall.
But I still don't see what refined uranium
has to do with a pandemic.
TREVOR: 5053, this guy picked
the wrong
random Traveler number.
3224 died six months ago.
These guys are all Faction.
Well, I wish I could tell you the whole
plan, but, you know... Protocol Two.
No. I don't know.
I'm gonna need more.
Like what? Something in writing?
The Director isn't good enough for you?
You could be pretending
to be somebody else.
I am pretending to be somebody else.
It's in the job description.
Are you new here?
No.
I just don't want to see uranium
fall into the wrong hands.
Well, neither do we.
Hands on your head.
GUN HITS FLOOR
- Door.
LOCK BUZZES
Show him where it is.
Long gone. Have a look for yourself.
Trev.
Any of your team showing any symptoms yet?
You look like you're in the early stages.
Where did you take it?
- Even if I told you, the others would know
and they'd just move it to a safe place.
Some of them are on their way here now.
You're more than welcome to wait.
No sign of uranium in the lab.
Shit!
Feel better?
- No.
I do.
- Come on.
COUGHING
- INDISTINCT CHATTER
This been tested?
DAVID:
Soup's safe, Bob.
I promise.
- How'd you know my name?
Why does no-one ever recognise me
with this thing on?
It's me.
- David?
You shouldn't be here.
- Well, where else would I be?
All my friends are here.
BOB COUGHS
Soup's delicious. I tested it myself.
It'll make you strong and fight that bug
going around.
BOB COUGHS
TRAVELER D-13 COUGHS
TRAVELER D-13: I've got to get back
to my team.
I've done about all I can for Boyd
at this point.
I wanted to give you these.
They're not programmed
to affect the viral load
but if she starts to go into organ failure,
they might buy you some time.
Thank you.
- Aren't nanites by directive only?
Well, with the Director down,
I figure the discretion falls on me.
Boyd's a good medic.
We could use her.
We'll do what we can.
TRAVELER D-13: Good luck.
I'd be willing to trade information
in exchange for those nanites.
I thought you wanted to die.
Not if the cure's right in front of me.
I'm not stupid.
You're the control. You get nothing.
DOOR OPENS
Well?
- There was no uranium.
Just the Faction...
waiting for us.
Why are you looking at me like that?
You're the one that sent us there.
- Aw, that is so insulting.
Yes, I did!
Because we absolutely need it
and time is short.
You need to find out where it is
and go get it.
They're a step ahead of us, at least.
We need another option.
There aren't any other options!
We need to get the Director back online.
The Faction has been planning
this for along time.
So we gotta think outside the box.
There's a military base just north of here.
NS Wallace.
You're thinking nuclear weapons?
That's nowhere near the box, Philip.
But that's ideal, from a fuel perspective.
A few hundred years is nothing
compared to the half-life of plutonium.
It would be difficult.
- Closer to impossible!
And if we've thought about it,
then the Faction probably has too.
Well...
Doesn't sound like we
have much of a choice.
I got you some groceries so you won't have
to go out for the next few days.
The store was a madhouse.
I heard there's looting going on.
Yeah, a few assholes.
How're you feeling?
I'm OK.
Hot. Headache.
Temperature's up near 100.
Let's cool you down.
TV BLARES
The news said this was an epidemic.
Is it really that bad?
Hopefully that's a...
bit of an overreaction.
TV: Doctor, What can you tell me...
- What is it?
About the virus?
They're not sure yet.
They're working on it. But you...
are sick, and you need to rest.
MAN ON TV: So much so'
that while many of the symptoms
match the common flu
kit technically can't be...
What do you know?
How sick am I?
- HE SIGHS
Grant?
I don't know.
OK, what do we do?
The safest place for you is right here.
“Safest”? OK, now you're starting
to scare me.
Maybe we should go to the hospital.
- Not where you want to be right now.
Look...
The next couple days,
it's gonna be hard for me to get home.
Couple of days?
- I will try to-
What about you? You're gonna be exposed.
I've got to support the people
who are trying to solve this.
And you've got to take your meds and rest
and give your body...
and that baby
the fuel that they need.
OK? That means fresh
fruit, not salted meat.
Do you have to go so soon?
The sooner I go,
the sooner I come back.
I love you.
So?
Took all night, but they're done.
Good work.
How's everybody holding up?
We can nap in the car.
When I left, you were afraid
the device wouldn't have enough range.
Yeah, we fixed that.
How does it know when to activate?
Well, the Director is programmed
to broadcast an emergency signal
if it's ever powered down.
Which should trigger the device
and activate it.
“Should”?
Do you want me to go over a list of things
that could go wrong with this plan?
No, thank you.
It'll work, boss.
- CARLY: We're good to go.
Alright, then let's gear up.
TREVOR:
Road trip!
How is she?
Uh...
SHE SIGHS
Her viral load's holding steady
but she's not getting any better.
The nanites will help, right?
Could help.
Could make things worse.
The Faction planned this well.
It's hard to know what contingencies
they've thought of.
Use Grace as you see fit,
but keep your eye on her.
And... Take care.
You too.
COUGHING
SIRENS WAIL IN DISTANCE
Hey, Bob?
I brought you some soup.
Bob?
Bob!
Oh, no!
JEFFREY CRIES
- VOICEMAIL BEEPS
Hey, Carly, it's me. I'm getting worried
about you.
About Jeffrey...
HE COUGHS
Listen, I'm sick as shit. Please...
Call me, let me know where you are,
that you're OK.
CHILD CRIES
Your son says “hi” too.
PHONE BEEPS
CHILD CRIES
DEVICE WHIRS
JENNY COUGHS
SHE EXHALES
You're a hypocrite.
You're all high and mighty
about sacrificing lives to save the future
and then treat me like a lab rat.
You did this to yourself.
JENNY COUGHS
This is a waste of resources.
I should be programming the nanites.
Not yet.
- Why not?
Because I want to see
if the anti-serum will work first.
I'm close.
Boyd will be dead before you're done!
Well, she's my patient.
We both know, in the time we come from,
medical nanites more or less replace you.
OK, if you want to be helpful
why don't you use your computer
and hack into the CDC
and find out what kind of progress
they've made?
The who?
Hack into them too, if you'd like.
Like either the Center For Disease Control
or the World Health Organization
is gonna know
how to deal with a virus designed
in the future?
Let's contact the 15th century
and hire an exorcist!
- Would you please stop talking?
You little power-tripper.
I am trying to save your life!
- JENNY COUGHS
Well, you're not doing a very good job.
I feel awful.
Where are you going?
To the bathroom.
SHE COUGHS
Hi. We're, uh-—
- This is a designated exit, sir.
Oh. Sorry. Uh...
What's he doing?
Just his job.
Everybody relax.
All these guys could be Faction.
If it goes down,
I'll take the booth guard.
Easy! We're not gonna get our warhead
if we start shooting people.
We're trapped in here,
and there's cameras everywhere.
Everybody, calm the fuck down.
Base is under quarantine, sir.
- I'm aware of that.
I'm Special Agent
Grant MacLaren from the FBI.
I've got a meeting with Captain Garcia
on urgent business.
All appointments have been cancelled...
- Vice Admiral Donahue
arranged the meeting, so I assure you,
the meeting has not been cancelled.
Check again.
HE WHISPERS:
Carly!
GUARD:
I see it here now, sir.
Great. And the gate?
Just waiting for your passes to print, sir.
Building four.
On your right.
Appreciate it.
SHE COUGHS
SHE KNOCKS
GRACE SHOUTS:
What?
You alright?
- GRACE: No, I'm dying
but I still need to go to the bathroom
periodically.
WATER RUNS
Well, you've been in there for a while.
I was just concerned.
I'm fine!
TOILET FLUSHES
Did you see where she put the nanites?
In there.
JENNY COUGHS
What're you doing?
- Shh.
Shhhh...
Captain Garcia?
Special Agent MacLaven from the FBI.
It's “MacLaren.”
- Your pass says “MacLaven”.
GARCIA: Agent MacLaren
knows his name, Ms. Jackson.
Should I issue a new pass?
He won't be here that long. You can go.
That doesn't sound promising.
It is what it is.
I'm sure the Admiral relayed
the urgency of our request.
And your pass says MacLaven.
People make mistakes.
- MACLAREN: Our request isn't one of them.
How does that particular warhead
possibly help prevent a pandemic?
I'm not authorised to explain.
Shame. I'd pay good money to hear it.
CARLY: While you're deciding
whether to help us or not
a deadly virus is spreading worldwide.
You're being a little melodramatic,
aren't you?
Flu kills people every year.
- It's far worse than what's been reported.
There are millions of
people infected already
even if they haven't
presented symptoms yet.
And it's spreading exponentially.
The admiral's email said
you'd be coming in with CDC personnel.
Is that supposed to be you?
They're specialists.
Uh-huh.
This is making less and less sense
the more I hear.
If you'd like to call the Admiral,
I'm sure... GARCIA: Not necessary.
My orders were clear.
The warhead is being separated
from the torpedo as we speak
for what good that could possibly do.
It's being loaded directly
into your vehicle.
I just don't like ordnance leaving my base
without an explanation.
Trust me when I say
you're helping to save millions of lives.
I hope I'm one of them.
I feel like shit and so do half the people
on my base.
I will personally make sure
that the people of this base
are among the first to receive
the antidote once it's ready.
COUGHING
David.
You should go home.
Yeah, I'm just gonna sit for a bit.
You've done your fair share.
Government's getting serious.
There's looting going on.
Looting?
HE SCOFFS
I saw a movie a few months back
where something like this happened.
It was very believable.
But I never bought the looting.
“Hey everyone's getting sick,
so let's...
"Let's break that window
and steal that TV."
I... I don't get that.
Me neither.
I mean, you get a pretty decent TV
for next to nothing nowadays
compared to what I got mine for? God.
David.
- The expensive part is the cable.
David...
Go home.
Yeah.
No, I, I'm waiting for Marcy to come by.
Maybe I should go home.
It's a good idea.
I should've swung that fucking axe.
Forbes would've shot you.
Thirty percent of the human population...
Including all of you.
TREVOR:
Boss, you can't blame yourself
for not being able to foresee
the unthinkable.
That's why they call it “unthinkable...
Can't think it.
- Still, I know how you feel.
I'm the one that provided
the Faction with the virus.
You were drugged.
Again.
Stop. It's done.
You know, I've been
wondering about that.
Maybe the Director can undo this.
How?
The future can only send
a consciousness back
as far as the most recent
Traveler, right?
And Travelers are arriving all the time
all over the world
as part of the Grand Plan...
but the last one had to have
been months ago...
before the Director went down.
Before all this happened.
The Faction might not be able to send
consciousness back
or establish a TELL,
but messengers count.
It's still a transfer of information
from the future.
TREVOR COUGHS He's right.
Messengers cause the same ripples in
space-time as Travelers.
PHILIP: And we know the Faction has
sent messengers recently.
They thought of everything.
Well, guys, on the bright side...
We're almost home.
COUGHING
Hard to believe where we're walking
right now
is under a kilometre of ice
in a few hundred years.
The domes get built right over there.
We've only ever seen the shelters
from the inside.
CARLY COUGHS
SHE PANTS AND GASPS
What's wrong?
SHE GASPS
Aw, shit. Marcy!
JENNY GASPS
- MONITOR BEEPS RAPIDLY
What happened?
She shouldn't be having
respiratory issues at this stage.
You didn't trust me. I had no choice.
What'd you do?
I instructed the nanites
to pull the virus into red blood cells
where it can't survive.
She should be getting better.
The Faction predicted that countermeasure.
The virus blocks red blood cells' ability
to carry oxygen.
She's suffocating.
MARCY: Turn them off!
- Deactivating the nanites
will be like flushing them down the drain!
- Turn them off or she's gonna die.
Either way, they're useless now.
MONITOR BEEPS RAPIDLY
GRACE:
There, she's better.
No, she's not better!
She's right back to where she started.
They've been ahead of us this whole time.
Did you not think the Faction was gonna
factor in nanites?
This is all because you didn't trust me!
Why should I?
You're alive because of me.
And perfectly healthy.
Am I?
When you reset me
you left out some things.
What'd you leave out, Grace?
This is what you want to talk about
when we're all dying?
- I'm not dying! You are.
KATHRYN COUGHS
- TV BLARES
KATHRYN GROANS Oh...
TOILET FLUSHES
Oh...
SHE SIGHS
PHONE BUTTONS CLICK
VOICEMAIL: You've reached Special Agent
Grant MacLaren. Please leave a-
TV: and looting continue to run rampant'
among fears of the virus that is plaguing
nearly every nation on Earth.
Local authorities are struggling
to maintain order...
TV: and while the death toll
continues to rise
fewer and fewer people are finding
themselves
table to recover from the deadly disease..
Health officials continue to search
for answers...
PHILIP COUGHS
Want to take a break?
- PHILIP COUGHS
No, I'm good.
OK. Come on.
Almost there.
Guns on the ground!
Secure the warhead.
Where are you taking it?
FORBES:
Somewhere it can't power the Director.
Oh, come on.
Of course we knew you'd try
something like this
when you didn't get the uranium.
Don't beat yourself up!
You're a good team,
and we need numbers.
We should be working together.
I don't think so.
The Director had its chance.
Didn't change a goddamn
thing in the future!
Other than create the Faction.
The future we came from,
you all died in the collapse of shelter 41.
HE LAUGHS
Why can't I wrap my head around that shit?
- Why am I not surprised?
Alright.
Thanks for the plutonium.
We'll make sure to put it to good use.
Let's go!
- MACLEAN: Plutonium?
What... You think we brought a nuclear
warhead in here?
I thought you said that they were
watching all of our communications.
There was a typo
in my Admiral Donahue email that...
It may have thrown them off.
When I wrote “Mark 45 warhead”
instead of, uh...
What was it? Mark 46?
- Oh! Oh, right.
The 45 was nuclear.
That makes total sense.
PHILIP: Except the Mark 45 torpedo
was decommissioned in 1976.
On a Wednesday.
Never in a million years
could we get a nuclear warhead
from a US naval station.
Your friends just walked away
with a conventional
Mark 46 antisubmarine warhead.
DEVICE HUMS
Carly, I think they're far enough away now.
DEVICE BEEPS
HEAVY GUNFIRE
SOLDIERS GRUNT
Device is in place and activated.
Turn around.
HE CHUCKLES Come on, Mac.
I'm unarmed.
You really think you can kill me
in cold blood?
I really do.
HIGH-PITCH RINGING
- JENNY SCREAMS
RINGING IN FORBES' EARS
JENNY SCREAMS
FORBES SCREAMS
I'm Traveler 4991.
It worked.
The Director's
back up and running.
The cure has been sent to the 21st.
FORBES: The encrypted beacon
on the device was activated
almost the moment power
to the Director was cut off.
It took some time for us
to find and recover it
but we got to it without them knowing...
Even when we broke through,
the energy source was only capable
of powering the Director for three seconds.
Enough time for the Director to reroute the
power to itself through the network.
Cut off the Faction's
access to the reactor.
Design the cure...
to win the war.
How many Faction are still here?
It's impossible to know how many were sent
into the quantum frame.
The Director won't have a TELL
for all of them.
HE CHUCKLES
PHONE BUZZES
MACLAREN: Kat?
Grant.
I have been so worried.
I've been trying to call you.
- I know, sorry.
But all the work we've been doing,
it 's paid off.
You're gonna be OK.
I'm so sick.
Don't say that if it's not real.
No, I promise, we've had a breakthrough.
Watch the news.
I... I'll be... I'll be back with you
as fast as I can.
I'm worried about the baby.
I'll be back tomorrow at the latest.
HELICOPTERS APPROACH
Maybe sooner.
He didn't answer.
We did it.
That means we should be able
to wake you up soon.
GRACE:
One, she can't hear you.
Two... I can't believe
you're giving her the cure first.
I'm standing right here!
- Boyd is far more sick.
Am I at least next?
No. The newly arrived Traveler
in her very sick host body, then you.
Oh, just admit you hate me.
TV BLARES
Kat?
Sweetheart, hey. Hey, wake up.
Oh... You're home?
And I've got something for you.
TURNS TV OFF
Come on.
What is it?
No, I can't take any medicine,
in case it affects the baby.
I got this directly from the CDC.
I made sure to ask.
It's perfectly safe.
It works really fast.
I'm going to let you sleep.
No. Can you just lie with me
for a bit?
Just for a minute.
I would like nothing more.
Jeff?
Jeffrey?
Jeffrey!
Carly?
CHILD CRIES
I know you were trying to call.
I had to get this first.
It's a treatment for the virus.
What? Where did you get it?
CHILD CRIES
- It doesn't matter.
It'll cure you both.
I was so scared.
I didn't know what to do.
You didn't come home.
I didn't know what to do but hold him.
CHILD CRIES
- Oh...
HE COUGHS
Give him to me. I know.
I'm supposed to go to work
soon as you got home, but...
It's OK.
Just rest a while first.
CARLY: I know. I know, I know.
- Yeah, I think I will.
CARLY:
I know.
CHILD CRIES
TV: The cure was developed by scientists
at the Centre For Disease Control
and is now being mass produced
and sent to health officials...
DOOR OPENS
around the world. It's estimated
that Within a few months...
Marcel
- the disease will be all but eradicated.
You hear they cured this thing?
- The death rate is expected to drop...
Ah, you're probably the one
that came up with it.
Not this time.
Did you stay inside?
No.
No, I was helping out at one
of the shelters. David...
You could have been exposed.
Yeah, I was.
The people I work with
are the first ones to be forgotten
when something like this happens.
You're not gonna give me that, are you?
Only if you're sick.
Speaking of sick...
This man I know just collapsed...
while I was trying to get him soup.
Your pulse is good.
And while they were wheeling him out...
I felt like one of those minor characters
in a movie that does not end well.
And I thought to myself...
“Marcy's gonna give me shit
if I end up dying from this.”
Because I can't help myself.
You mean from helping others?
Yeah, but isn't that what you do too?
Open your mouth.
- Your way of doing things...
GARBLED: is more impressive.
Right. Well, you're not sick.
Well, maybe you should give me
the shot anyway.
No symptoms.
If you were exposed,
it means you're immune.
So, find your friend who collapsed
and give this to him.
OK?
- Yeah.
What, you're leaving again?
I have other patients.
I just wanted to make sure
that you were OK.
Wow. House call.
I'll be back later, if that's alright.
Don't wait up.
DOOR CLOSES
Yeah, I probably will.
I thought you were going home.
Just came back to check on my patients.
How are you guys feeling?
TREVOR GROANS Oh...
Much better, thank you.
Good.
You'll be happy to know that
the CDC has set up treatment centres
to disseminate the antiviral en masse.
And Jenny...
That is, Jenny 3.0...
is coordinating deliveries.
BOYD: Marcy?
Oh, yeah.
She woke up a while ago.
Hey.
- BOYD: Hey.
How're you feeling?
Mm. Like shit.
But I'll live.
I'll also live, thanks for asking.
I still haven't heard
from the other two members of my team
but I'm hoping-
DOOR KNOCKS