VINCENT: And the dream begins
the same every time...
INDISTINCT CHATTER
Where's Greg?
Oh, he called in sick.
I'm covering for him.
Just fix it, please.
Mr Corrigan has
a conference call at 8:45.
Not a problem.
Greg, hey, thanks for coming.
- I'm Vincent.
Screen's locked up again.
I'm gonna need it
for a call in five minutes.
Can you get me back up?
- Oh, yeah, for sure.
I just need to get back there.
Hal? Listen, I gotta let the IT guy
work on the computer for a bit here.
Let me just duck
into another office.
Yeah, let me put you
on hold, hang on.
Just take two minutes,
two minutes...
Sorry.
Just turn it on and off again,
I guess, huh?
VINCENT LAUGHS No, no, no, sir.
OFFICE DOOR CLOSES
COMPUTER POWERING DOWN
COMPUTER START-UP CHIMES
HIS EARS RING INTENSELY
HE GASPS IN PAIN
HE MOANS IN AGONY
HE SCREAMS
STEADY BEEP OF COMPUTER
VINCENT: From the moment
/ arrive in the 21st Century
'something's wrong..
'According to the historical record'
'Anthony Corrigan, stockbroker'
was at his desk
on a conference call
'but instead, it's someone else..
'We were wrong..
I try to send the message,
but the computer freezes.
I practised a hundred times,
but everything '3 wrong.
I try to reboot the system,
but there's no time now.
COMPUTER START-UP CHIMES
COMPUTER BEEPS
The mission's a failure..
'So why should I sacrifice myself?'?
INDISTINCT OFFICE CHATTER
I decide I should at least
try to warn them.
Everyone listen!
I can't explain why, but if you don't all
follow me right now, you're going to die.
You have to leave now.
Greg...
What the fuck are you doing?
VINCENT (VO):
/ run.
I don 't even know what floor I'm on,
only that I have to hurry.
'First, I hear the plane...
PLANE SOARING ABOVE
and then the explosion.
RUMBLING EXPLOSION
And I don 't remember anything else
until I'm outside, looking up.
Alright, everybody, clear out. Let's go.
- INDISTINCT CHATTER
SIRENS WAILING
FIRE TRUCK HONKS HORN
POLICEMAN: We're going to need
that building evacuated.
DISTANT SIRENS FADE AND ECHO
SIRENS WAIL
Everyone around me is looking
at the destruction above
'while I discard the last vestiges'
of the man who was
supposed to die that day.
'And then I hear the second plane..
INCOMING JET WHOOSHING ABOVE
CROWD SCREAMING IN PANIC
And then I wake up.
DR PERROW: Dreams of 9/11
aren't uncommon, Vincent
even for those who were
nowhere near ground zero.
I have the dream
because it happened.
My mission
was a proof of concept
to send a confirmation that I
arrived safely in the 21st Century
then die, so no one could trace me.
But...
I survived.
They won't forgive that.
So you're afraid whomever you were
to send this message to
intends to punish you?
They're already here.
I've seen the changes in history.
At least, the histories that I remember.
And they'll be coming for me.
SIRENS BLARE OUTSIDE
HE SIGHS NERVOUSLY
[DOOR LOCK BEEPS]
[DOOR CLICKS OPEN]
Walt!
Jesus, what took you so long?
You're lucky they gave me
permission to talk to you at all.
I'm gonna say one thing
and I need you to listen.
Destroy that device
by whatever means possible.
I've never asked you to do
anything more important.
What, that thing in the barn?
You need to do it now.
- What is it?
What is your association
with those people in the barn?
They all raised a red flag
a few months back.
You said that they were
just a bunch of kids.
I ask because two of those people
are in the hospital, and a farmer is dead.
Alright... I'll talk.
A few weeks ago I received a top secret
inter-departmental communication
asking if I'd noticed
any changes in you.
I told a pair of special agents
with very expensive sunglasses
that, yeah-—
WAKEFIELD: You know your friends
are giving you up as we speak?
- Sir...
can you please
be quiet so I can think?
FORBES (VO) CONTINUES:
and your Wife noticed, too.
Nothing that either one of us
could point to
but enough to say
that something is up.
These people, whoever they are,
if they have something on you
if they're using you,
if they're making you do things
we can protect you!
Destroy the device.
That's all I got.
PHILIP WHISPERS:
They're never gonna do that, boss.
Philip, stay off the coms.
I'm not talking to you anymore.
Before I go...
they wanted me
to ask you about this.
HE CLEARS HIS THROAT
Well, Walt...
that's a handkerchief.
They tell me
it's a communication device.
Really?
It's made from something
called graphine.
A technology we're working on
but we're not quite there yet.
They suspect that it's powered by
the natural electricity of the human body
capable of broadcasting
an encrypted signal for miles.
This one came from the high-school
senior that's in surgery right now.
TRAVELER D-13:
How is she doing?
DOCTOR: Rifle was shot from
point-blank range.
There's severe damage
to the spleen and...
Who are you?
TRAVELER D-13: Seriously, no one told you?
I'm a specialist, hereto assist
from Grace hospital.
Call me Derek.
HEART MONITOR BEEPS
- INDISTINCT CHATTER FROM STAFF
DR MORI:
And suction?
DOCTOR 2:
Take care of that blood.
DR MORI:
The bullet's causing a lot of inflammation
between the T-12 and L-1.
I'm worried about the lumbar nerves.
DOCTOR 2: We can't
get ahead of this blood loss anyway, so...
DR MORI:
OK.
Let's get it outta there.
OFFICER: I need to state
for the record that you gave me permission
to look at your phone and listen
to your messages without a lawyer present.
Well, I have nothing to hide, so...
Wait, what are you doing?
I'm playing back
a saved message.
Yeah, that one, that has nothing to do
with... with anything.
Sir, the message came
from a phone registered to you
that called this number two seconds
before a man with no identification
who was allegedly holding
a gun to your head-
was fatally shot from
the apartment next door.
And you saved
this message because...
It's kind of a keeper.
MARCY (RECORDING):
Hey, David, it's me.
I guess it 's my turn
to leave you a goofy message.
[just know how stressed out you get
when you don 't hear from me
so I wanted you to know that
I might be away for a while
maybe even relocated.
I just don 't want you
wondering or worrying
if you don't hear from me.
You know, if it happens.
I don't even know for sure if it will,
but if it does...
thank you for being there for me
when I really needed someone.
In another time
or another life, right?
'Goodbye, David..
See?
MAN SHOUTING OUTSIDE:
This is bullshit!
Jesus, he's having a bad day.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Hey, Jeff, keep your voice down.
I told you what happened.
The optics suck, and you know it.
It's on the news,
you shot a 13-year-old kid.
That was about to shoot Carly.
Who also murdered her mother
and brother last night.
That kid?
Number 2 pencil to the head, both of them.
Girl was certifiable.
Now, get Carly's ass down here
to make a statement
and you're just the poor bastard
who had to stop her.
OK, Carly's
not answering her cell.
We've been having trouble at home.
In the meantime, buddy, I'm sorry,
but I gotta take your badge.
Forensics already got your gun.
Oh, come on, this is bullshit, man.
Let me just go down the hall
and talk to him.
- Hey, no.
Not with booze on your breath, OK?
Hey, if I was forced to shoot a kid,
I might have a few drinks, too.
This is gonna work itself out.
Just go home.
I can see there's a fight
going on inside of you.
If you're worried about Kat-...
She is completely in the dark
about this.
She called me earlier
to tell me that you sent her away.
That your life was in danger
and so was hers.
Is that true?
It's what made me put a team
together to come after you.
We were tracking your car,
and then it disappeared like it went into
a dead zone...
- HE STAMMERS: Yes, but...
she's alright?
If you don't talk, you won't walk
which means Kat may never, ever find out
whether you are dead or alive-
Destroy the device, Walt.
Please.
I'm begging you.
Look, I probably
shouldn't tell you this
but I have also been told
that that device is far beyond-
DOOR LOCK BEEPS
Thank you, Agent Forbes.
I'll take it from here.
- Look, I need more time.
Seriously?
You're telling him
more than he's telling you.
But, hey, thanks for trying.
Walt...
remember what I said.
AGENT WAKEFIELD:
Yeah, yeah, yeah, destroy the device.
He heard you the first time.
We all did.
DOOR SLAMS
Yeah, it's not gonna happen.
DR PERROW:
Are you feeling threatened, Vincent?
VINCENT:
No, I have defences in place.
Deuterium oxide
in the radiant heating system
acts as a fair
space-time attenuator.
It slows neutrons.
Don't worry,
it's not radioactive.
Uh... Why wouldn't they just
assume that you died on 9/11?
Why do you think that
they're still after you?
Because they've already
found me twice.
VINCENT:
/ found my way out of New York
and took a train
to the Pacific Northwest.
I had the money and the stock certificates
I'd taken from the safe
but if I was going to stay hidden,
I needed more.
'Historically, there was'
a man named Oliver Norton,
became a tech millionaire on his own
and all I did was insert myself
into the process
as invisibly as possible,
and take my fair share.
VINCENT: lhad convinced
Oliver that I had debilitating phobias
difficulties dealing with people,
privacy.”.
I needed a front man
for my company
that uses proprietary computer software
to predict market trends.
Of course, I wouldn't let
anyone see it
{not even him..
As long as the predictions
were correct, he didn't care.
'In fact, he was so grateful'
he constantly
wanted to reward me.
And that's when Oliver
introduced me
to the woman
who became Taylor's mother.
Buddy!
Meet your new assistant.
Assistant?
Hi, Vincent, it's a pleasure
to meet you-
No, no, I don't
need an assistant.
Oh, yeah. You do.
I got a company
I gotta pretend to run.
No, sorry, I can't-—
- Trust me, alright?
I already told Irene
all about how you like to do things.
No cell phones,
portable radios, webcams.
No life, no fun...
And I completely understand.
Me, I don't like crowds.
I... I'm not sure I'll have
anything for you to do.
High-maintenance people always think
that they're low maintenance.
You need this, partner.
VINCENT: It wasn't
an assistant I needed
{it was human contact...
and Oliver must have known that..
You said in our initial session
that your wife died of an aneurysm.
Yes. That was the first time
I was discovered.
TAYLOR:
Dad?
You know I'm not to be disturbed
when I'm in this room.
Sorry, but Pepper wants out,
and Mr Morraca isn't around.
Well... alright, take her out then.
I'll watch you from here.
TAYLOR:
OK.
Hi.
Hello.
TAYLOR:
Come on, Pepper.
He looks like you.
Fortunately for him, he looks like the host
who provided the chromosomes.
Not me.
David Mailer?
Yeah.
I'm your lawyer.
- I don't have a lawyer.
Philip Pearson said
you might want my help.
I don't know Philip Pearson.
- Friend of Marcy?
Marcy? Oh, my God, yes.
Is she OK?
Are you...
what are you, like a...
FBI lawyer?
Wow. No. No.
Jeez, uh, he said
she said you were special
but I didn't realise
you were "special".
HE SIGHS:
Well, this...
Sorry, this is...
I... I'm not good at this.
This is so not my thing.
Well, David, fortunately
this is my thing
and I am very good at this.
So... we're probably
looking at 10 years tops
nine with good behaviour.
What?
Nah, just fuckin' with you.
Why would you... Oh, my God.
This isn't how actual law-enforcement
officers behave, MacLaren.
There's giant chunks of time
missing from your logs.
It's a miracle we didn't catch on
to you people sooner.
"You people",
what does that mean?
Agent Forbes says, compared
to just a few months ago
you are like a different person-
- Jesus!
Take my blood,
take my fingerprints
take whatever you need-
- Who now spends
half his time
with a high-school senior
his counsellor, a single mum
a heroin addict, a farmer, and...
this one kills me...
a mentally-challenged woman
in the care of the state.
Philip Pearson is my CI
on a hacking case.
We suspected the device had
something to do with hijacking internet-
Let's skip over the part
where you pretend
there's a legit scenario
where those people,
in a fucking barn
with whatever that device is
makes any sense whatsoever.
Whoever you are
and whoever you work for
we're on to you now.
I'm a single mum.
There's a lot of folks like me.
This is gonna sound weird,
and possibly insane
but I'm just gonna
go ahead and say it.
I have a turtle at home,
and I had to leave in a hurry
and there was
a lot of broken glass-
You think this is funny?
No.
MARCY:
I'm just a librarian
that's all I am.
You're more than that.
TRAVELER D-13:
Clamps...
DOCTOR 1:
OK...
ALERT BEEPS
She's fibrillating.
Charging, one, two, three.
Clear... shock.
[DEFIBRILLATOR PADDLES FIRE]
[ALARM WAILS]
DOCTOR: BP's stabilising.
- There we go.
That's not me.
It's clearly you.
I have no memory of this.
Don't I get a phone call
or something?
Who do you want to call?
My babysitter for one.
Jeffrey Jr is in the hands
of Washington Family Services.
What?
Why?
No, he needs to be
with his mother!
God, how long are you
going to keep me here?
Sit back down, please-
WHISPERS: Permission to break
the fuck out of here.
SHOUTING: I want to see my baby!
- Sit down!
I want to see him now!
-  MUTTERING: Alright, you call it.
I call what?
PHILIP OVER COM LINK:
Uh... guys?
What are we doing?
Let me see it one more time.
On three.
CARLY:
Two...
One...
GRUNTING
On the move.
Right behind you.
LOCK BEEPS OPEN
Do we know what we're doing?
MACLAREN:
Getting out of here.
GUN CLICKS
- SHE SIGHS
Don't forget Protocol 3.
Don't forget I was
ordered to kill you.
Right.
This isn't a good time.
MARCY:
Guys?
I think Philip's this way.
DOOR LOCK BEEPS
I took his legs out.
He went down pretty hard.
- Marcy?
It's probably just a concussion.
He'll live. OK, let's go,
let's go, let's go.
Come on.
Hey!
That looked like it hurt.
Well, they didn't try to kill anyone,
so you owe me a buck.
What's their progress?
Almost to the gym.
Alright.
Let's see what they do.
Boss?
Jesus Christ...
That isn't the way out.
No. It isn't.
Mac, we gotta go.
Go ahead.
GUN CLICKS
Didn't think so.
MACLEAN:
OK.
We're here. Now what?
LIGHTS CLUNK
We were wondering if you'd really try
to destroy the device
given the opportunity.
DOOR OPENS
It seemed odd, considering
you built the thing.
Hey, but now that you're here,
maybe you can show us what it does.
Under supervision
obviously.
Sorry.
Not gonna happen.
ANNOUNCEMENT: Dr Kravitz,
you have a visitor in the main lobby.
Dr Kravitz, you have a visitor
in the main lobby.
Mr and Mrs Holden?
Is Trevor OK?
He's out of surgery,
and we've stopped the bleeding.
What the hell happened?
All I can tell you is that your son was
involved in a shooting
and that the bullet we removed
in order to save his life
was lodged dangerously close
to his spinal cord.
There's still
a great deal of inflammation.
Can we see him?
DR MORI SIGHS
Tomorrow at the earliest.
So he's gonna be OK?
I'm confident
Trevor will survive this.
He's very strong.
But you should know
there's a possibility
he may not regain
the use of his legs.
DR PERROW: How old
was Taylor when his mother died?
A baby.
I'd spent the latter half
of my life before this one
being eaten away by a disease
that doesn't exist yet.
I never imagined
the possibility of family.
A loving wife.
A child.
Irene was convinced that I'd be angry
when she told me about the baby
afraid I'd think
she'd trapped me.
But how could she know that
that in the future I'd left behind,
life was so precious...
And new life, so rare
most precious of all.
CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS
Just as she couldn't have known
that a stolen moment while I slept
a small token of a perfect memory...
would be the instrument
of her death.
HER EARS RING INTENSELY
An image of me, taken on a cell phone
time and place recorded
and posted to a friend
discovered and acted upon.
Vincent, I think...
- You see, we knew
it was possible to send messages
directly to the 21st through a host
but we projected a 40% chance
that an adult mind might not be able
to withstand the shock of transfer.
That's the whole reason
I volunteered to go first!
No one would have to die
that wasn't going to die-
OK, let's just stop-
Artificial Intelligence
isn't supposed to be capable
of taking a life
that isn't about to end.
The Director shouldn't have risked it,
don't you understand?
No!
Not one part of what you just said.
I apologise.
Vincent, I can't help you
if I don't understand
what you're saying.
Of course.
COM LINK BEEPS
Hey, guys...
I just want to say
whatever happens
from this point...
be proud of what you accomplished.
I still think,
in the grand scheme of things
we did good.
I know we did.
And I still have faith
the Director will find a way.
I believe that with all my heart.
Just...
maybe not with us.
You all know
what you have to do.
Boss, could you be
a little more specific?
Self-destruct.
Obviously.
What?
In three...
Two...
One.
MIMICS EXPLOSION
SHE LAUGHS
HE LAUGHS
LAUGHTER ECHOES
MACLAREN GIGGLES
Sorry, Wakefield
you had that coming.
Com 3468... disable.
Com 3465, disable.
Com 3569, disable.
3326... disable.
COM BEEPS
So long, you guys.
HEADPHONES CRASH ON DESK
Well, that's my work day.
Text me if anything happens.
INDISTINCT CHATTER
We've gone long past the time
I allotted for this visit.
I was wondering if we could start fresh-
- No, I...
No, I'd rather you stay
a little longer.
Vincent, these delusions...
- Memories.
Are a very complex product
of severe paranoia.
I can't...
- I told you they've found me twice.
They?
- The Director.
Alright.
SHE CLEARS HER THROAT
Tell me about the second time.
It was a year later.
The company had become
quite successful...
You're not gonna believe
how well that meeting went.
Meeting?
Yeah, with the venture capital
company, I told you.
I told you it was a bad idea.
They made an offer.
Now, I didn't commit because...
- No...
because they want your software, too
but-
- No.
Eighty-seven million dollars!
Say "no" again, I dare you.
Oliver, I told you from the beginning.
OLIVER: I thought we were
supposed to be partners!
This is my software.
I've told you, if we affect the market
in any tangible way it just doesn't work.
Yeah, OK, one, why is that?
And... And two, who cares?
If we can sell the company
for 87 million?
I'm not taking "no" for an answer.
You're gonna hear them out.
- Oliver, wait. Wait!
HE SIGHS
There is no predictive software.
It doesn't exist, it never has.
All the computers out there,
the software
it's just for show, it's a front.
Then... how have you...
- I'm doing it.
No one could have guessed
large market trends
that accurately and that often.
That's true, I'm not guessing.
I'm remembering.
What the hell
is that supposed to mean?
It means you can't sell
the company, Oliver, I'm sorry.
You can't use that in here-
- Yeah, I'm breaking the rules
because you're out
of your fucking mind!
If I had stayed silent,
he might have lived
but the FCC was investigating
the company
and they had tapped his phone.
Voice recognition and GPS
allowed them to find me
the moment I spoke...
Oliver, please, I told you.
Stop, please, I told you,
it's dangerous.
I said, stop!
ROBOTIC VOICE:
Traveler 001
you are outside
mission parameters.
Self-termination
required immediately.
INTENSE RING SOUND
VOICEMAIL:
First new message.
KATHRYN:
Walter, it's Kathryn again.
'I'm at my mother's..
{Please call me back..
MESSAGE ALERT CHIMES
INDISTINCT CHATTER
Callahan.
- Any idea what's up?
Wakefield just sent me
a message to come here.
Yeah, most of us
all got the same message.
He does this.
OK, here I am.
What's so important?
I was going to ask you the same thing.
You just texted me.
I what?
Yeah, me too.
POWER SURGING
[INTENSE HIGH FREQUENCY SOUND]
[ALL SHOUT IN PAIN]
ALL SCREAM
DISTANT SCREAMS ECHOING
So your business partner
also died of an aneurysm?
Yes.
And you became sole owner
of the company.
Yes.
You think I killed them.
I told you, it was the Director.
You have nothing
to be afraid of, Dr Perrow.
I feel so much better
having unpacked myself
of all that baggage.
HE CHUCKLES
HE SIGHS
I feel nothing but gratitude.
Great.
Well, if you don't mind,
I'll be, uh, heading home.
My daughter will be wondering-
- Of course, I've kept you too long.
And your cell phone
and payment, in cash
is ready outside.
And I'd like to schedule
another appointment, please.
SHE SIGHS
Vincent...
you need medication.
I'm not helping.
Of course you are.
It doesn't even matter
that you don't believe me.
I get to talk to someone
who affords me the privacy
of doctor-client privilege
and you get paid
a great deal of money.
It really is the ultimate
21st-Century arrangement.
DISTANT SIRENS
- INDISTINCT HOSPITAL ANNOUNCEMENT
Grace?
Shh!
I had to sneak in here.
What are you doing?
I'm sharing the medical nanites
I was given by D-13
so that you'll be able to walk again.
I overheard them talking.
Oh.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
It's going to quadruple
my recovery time
but I suppose you're worth it.
So there's no sweet
nanotech for me again?
The Director left me out?
You've lived longer than any human
in history, and you're complaining?
I'm starting to take it personally.
HE GROANS GROGGILY
SHE TYPES RAPIDLY
Wait, don't medical nanites need to be
programmed to do specific tasks?
Yes, and I am a...?
Programmer.
Oh, yeah.
I'm sorry, I'm all drugged up.
I got shot.
I stepped in front of you,
remember?
Oh, wow, you did.
Thank you for saving me, Grace-
OK, now shut up and heal.
I need to concentrate.
LOCK CLICKS OPEN
Walt, I... I thought-—
- I'm Traveler 4112.
I'm sorry.
I know he was a friend.
How?
0014 built the Quantum Frame
with a fail-safe
one that would level this entire building
the moment Wakefield
and his team opened it up.
Which made all of you host candidates.
I heard it happening.
How many?
Twenty-five of us in the gym,
including Wakefield.
What about the-
- The Quantum Frame.
It's being dismantled
and scrapped.
HE SIGHS
So, that's it?
That's it. It's over, Grant.
Mac. You call me Mac.
They shorten everything
for some reason.
Mac...
I'm gonna need your help
with a lotta things.
Welcome to the 21st.
SHE SIGHS HEAVILY
LOUD KNOCKING
- SHE GASPS
Thank you.
MOBILE PHONE VIBRATES
- SHE GASPS IN FRIGHT
Do you really think it's ethical
to plant a bomb
and then take over the people
who would have died
when that bomb went off?
How is that not
circular reasoning?
No way the Director would
allow that level of technology in the 21st.
The Director was the one
who had it ordered built
in the first place-
- Hey...
a wise man once told me,
take the win.
Hey.
They wouldn't tell me much
but I got a quick look
at the monitors
at the nursing station, and...
they're both gonna recover.
Well, I'll take that win, too.
Come on, everybody,
I'll drop you home.
I think I'm gonna stay.
He would.
I've decided
I'm not gonna kill you.
Oh.
HE CLEARS THROAT
Good.
I was gonna ask.
I mean, there must have been
some kind of power struggle
back and forth when all that
was going down.
Who knows where the order
came from, right?
Well, at least it's settled now.
Still...
it must have been hard for you.
Thanks for the lift.
David...
It's the middle of the night.
It won't come out.
I mean, you'd think...
they'd properly clean up
something like this, you know?
All those people here, every one
of them capable of holding a mop.
But nah, they're just
gonna leave a...
a giant blood stain and a...
a business card with the number
of a cleaning service.
I'm surprised they
took away the dead body.
I'm sorry that
you had to go through that.
He was a John Doe by the way
which I found fascinating.
Yeah, not just no ID
no record at all.
But you probably already knew that.
Ray's a heck of a nice guy.
Here, let me help-
- Nah, I got it. I'm trying, uh...
I'm trying baking soda.
You know, the good news is
apparently, the Indian lady
that lives next door
whose name I never knew
told an Officer Boyd
whose name I do remember
for some reason
that the person
that came into her apartment
was a stocky bald man
with a thick Canadian accent.
Those Canadians, man...
you gotta watch out.
But I'm sure you knew
all about that, too.
David, here...
Stop, stop-
- Now all I have to do
is make myself available
for future questioning
whatever that means.
That's good.
- Oh, it's wonderful.
Can I do anything?
Can I make you some tea?
Um...
You know, I've had about 57 cups
so I'm... I'm a little wired.
What can I do?
This is nice.
Why don't you take the bed tonight,
I'll take the couch, OK?
You know,
I think I will tonight.
I'm really tired.
OK.
So, how was work?
CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYS
COMPUTER ALERT BEEPS
THUNDER RUMBLES