First time?
PHILIP:
Yeah. You?
Second.
Third for him.
JERVIS:
Good evening, Historians.
Welcome to Regional Update 4.
I'm Traveler A-26
of the archivist program.
If this is your first time,
please take a moment
to look inside the bag
you were provided on the way in.
The two green pills are to be taken
immediately following the update.
It's important that we restore
any chemical imbalances in the brain.
The yellow pills, you will need
going forward.
From time to time you may
perceive what we call
"projections" -
visual manifestations
of one or more alternate timelines -
an unavoidable side-effect
of memory not acquired
by conventional means.
The yellow pills will help to focus your
sensory perception
on one timeline at a time.
When you run out, call this number
to arrange for more.
Get that?
Yeah.
JERVIS:
Next, Protocol 2H.
The update is not to be discussed
with anyone. Ever.
Do not break this protocol.
This update will include historical
information relevant to your team's role
in the Grand Plan, including potential
candidates, investments, etc.
But by its very nature, your update may
also include historical information
about your team members,
loved ones
about you.
This is a burden you will have to
carry with you until the day you die
a date which, for obvious reasons,
will be omitted from your update.
Any questions?
Let's begin.
FEMALE COMPUTER VOICE:
Historians.
Open memory chain 1A.
Hey. I made breakfast.
Uh, I don't wanna be late.
Hey, come on, Carly.
Take five minutes.
KATHRYN:
Grant! They chose me!
Who?
The Pattersons.
Uh...
You know, the restaurant owners.
Jill.
- Jill. Right.
This means what exactly?
That I will be designing their new
restaurant with a brand-new baby.
Well, you'll have my help with the baby.
I can't take a job
that I don't have time to do.
Kat! We'll figure it out.
So I should say yes?
- Do you want to say yes?
Yes.
- Then yes.
OK.
I'll let them know.
Soon.
Nice work.
Hey, guys.
Hey.
What's the mission?
I got a messenger
with lotto numbers yesterday.
Director must've seen we're in a bit of a
financial hole and decided to step up.
Good.
I obviously can't win any more lotteries
without attracting undo attention,
so...
you won 86k on the super draw
last night...
and these numbers on the mega ball for
tonight will get you 62.
Sixty-two dollars
doesn't sound like very much.
$62,000.
Oh, OK.
You both get six numbers out of seven.
Why don't we just win seven out of seven
and we're covered?
Because historically, someone else is
supposed to win the big one
and completely ruin their lives.
- What about me?
You are too young to gamble.
An excellent example of irony.
MARCY SNIGGERS
So will that get us out of the hole?
PHILIP:
Not even close.
This is seed money.
But I can quadruple it
with horse races and use
those earnings to create
something far more substantial.
How does that even work if the historical
record has changed?
The messenger gave me very detailed
instructions.
We're good.
Congratulations, you guys!
Sweet.
- Thanks.
INDISTINCT CHATTER
So?
What did you think?
I liked it. It's like therapy.
Yeah. That's the idea.
We should do it more often.
- I'm in.
Hey, do you know if there's a store
around here anywhere?
So do I go for the $3 water,
the luxurious $5 bottle of water...
or the suspiciously under-priced
99 cent water?
You're buying a lottery ticket?
Mm-hmm.
Thanks.
- You know...
I buy one once in a while when the jackpot
gets insanely big like this one.
I don't know why. I mean, any size jackpot
would change my life.
I always play my same lucky numbers.
Yeah. Do you ever win?
Nope.
Thank you.
CASH REGISTER BEEPS
- MARCY: Thanks.
INDISTINCT CHATTER
What's up?
Why'd you stop playing?
Same reason you did.
You got a concussion, too?
Whatever, Trevor.
- Whoa, Kyle!
Don't try to tell me that you
don't remember what he did to us
because of your concussions.
Nobody forgets shit like that.
Maybe I just don't like to think about it.
VEHICLE APPROACHES
TREVOR:
Hey. Can I help you?
No, I don't need any help.
Do you need any help?
I'm good.
- Yeah, no, we're good.
Who's your friend?
Kyle.
HALL:
Well, hello, Kyle. Nice to meet you.
You know, Trevor and us, we...
we go way, way back.
I'm Hall. This is my associate, Luca.
Hey.
- KYLE: Hey.
Hey, Trevor, I'm gonna go.
I'll catch up with you later.
COM BEEPS
- Boss, it's me.
GRANT ON COM: What's up?
Hall and Luca got out of prison early.
How do you know?
TREVOR: Because I'm standing
right in front of 'em.
'They're parked outside my school..
I guess they don't know
I don't like being watched.
Tough guy. I love it!
Do me a favour, um...
Give my regards to the boy scout.
ENGINE STARTS
They just drove off.
What was that about? What'd he say?
TREVOR:
Nothing,.
Just thought you should know.
Thanks for the heads up.
Hey, Philip.
Got your winnings.
Hopefully, we get more
messengers like that.
Where's the rest of it?
I took some.
I need to invest that.
Well, turns out "baby needs a new pair of
shoes" isn't just a saying.
And my van needs a new transmission.
OK.
I can make it work.
How's all that going, by the way?
You and Jeff and the baby?
Is it working out?
It's fine. Why?
I don't know, just asking.
- Asking what exactly?
Uh... If things were OK at home?
Are you developing a thing for me?
No!
I just haven't...
heard you talk about that in a while.
It's all good.
- Great.
I mean, don't get me wrong,
I think you're very attractive.
This is weird.
- I agree.
I'm going to go.
- OK.
Thanks for the cash.
HE GROANS
KYLE GRUNTS'
TREVOR:
Atta boy!
Come on, Kyle.
KYLE GRUNTING
Come on, Kyle! One, two.
Hey, atta boy.
TREVOR:
Atta boy!
Way to work out some of that aggression!
Come on, let's get some water.
Come on, let's keep going.
Have a drink. Come on.
TREVOR:
Let's talk a bit.
Leave it alone. The old man can't
touch us anymore.
Come on.
One, two, one, two.
KYLE GRUNTS'
Ready? Two.
One, two.
TREVOR:
Why haven't you told anybody?
Why haven't you?
We're not talkin' about me.
He... He said if I let him...
- One, two.
Come on, come on. Two.
He'd take care of me!
Set me up
with scholarships and shit...
One, two.
- KYLE GRUNTS
What did he promise you, huh?
The same.
Eight straight. Come on.
HE ROARS
What if it's still going on
with other players?
Man, you know it is.
Then we gotta do something.
Like what?
You want to go to the police?
Go to the school?
Be his victims the rest of our lives?
- If that ends it.
TREVOR:
He can't stand against both of us.
We did nothing wrong, Kyle.
If...
Would you... would you go in with me?
Absolutely.
Come on. Let's see a two.
Atta boy. One, two.
KATHRYN:
Grant?
KATHRYN SHOUTS:
Grant!
KATHRYN 8088:
DR HIGGINS:
Stay calm for us, Kathryn.
Everything's going to be fine, sweetheart.
This is exactly where you need to be.
KATHRYN: Grant, please don't leave.
- No, no, I'll stay right here. I promise.
We're going to get her an ultrasound
and assess her from there.
She'll be out shortly.
STUDENTS CHATTER
GRACE:
Good morning, Trevor!
How are your grades?
Have you narrowed down
a list of colleges yet?
What can I do
to better help you succeed?
I read my employee manual
and I am ready to guide
the shit out of these pubescent brats.
I need your help with something.
Marcy!
Hey!
I'm sorry. Do I know you?
It's me. Luca.
2587. I was just warned about you watching
members of my team.
I only want to talk.
Do you?
DR HIGGINS:
Hi, Kathryn.
I have the results from the ultrasound
and the baby is fine.
KATHRYN:
Oh, thank God.
You have formed
a small placental abruption
so we want you to stay in for a bit
just so we can monitor you
and the baby,
make sure it doesn't get any worse.
But what if it does?
- It won't.
DR HIGGINS: If the baby forces our hand,
we can talk about our options
but for now we just need to assess
where we're at, OK?
Buzz the nurses if you need anything.
MACLAREN:
Thanks.
LUCA: You don't remember
anything from that time?
MARCY:
Nothing.
I was briefed by members of my team
about the time I lost, but...
It's not the same as actually living it.
LUCA:
Well...
at least now I know why you never
came to visit me in prison.
MARCY:
Sorry.
You said you would have died...
Losing my sister before I ever really
got to know her would be worse than-
Luca, Luca.
We were separated so young.
We can't know for sure that
we're really family.
COM BUZZES
- MACLAREN: Guys, it's Mac.
I'm going to be unavailable for a while.
There's a problem...
MARCY:
What's wrong?
Kathryn's in the hospital.
She's had some medical...
complications, and I need to be here
with her.
Marcy?
- Yeah, I'm on my way.
Is everything all right?
- Sorry, I have to go.
Holy...
Uh...
ANSWER PHONE:
Hey, this is Marcy. Leave a message.
Marcy, I won the lottery!
HE SPLUTTERS
Six numbers out of seven!
That's... That's $31,000!
Isn't that freaking amazing?
It would have been $62,000,
but someone else won the lottery.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God, that's you!
Because I took your numbers! You won
the lottery, too! Congratulations!
Wait...
I mean, that means
I took half your money.
I mean, that's like...
That's like cheating.
Um...
Yeah, you know what, I should just
give it to you. So...
That's what I'm gonna do.
But, I mean, what are the chances that your
numbers would be picked
any more than my mine, right?
Oh, my God, did you hear the greed in my
voice? Because I sure did.
Whoa... I mean, I may as well have just
come out and said, "That money's mine!"
Hmm!
Ahhh...
This is how money ruins people.
I think I'm going to be sick.
PHONE RINGS
Still no answer.
We said we'd meet after second period.
You know, for my first actual case
as a guidance counsellor,
you could have eased me into it.
Holden!
I have been looking all over for you.
Connor needs a QB who can hit him in the
hands if we want to win state.
So...
We'd love to have you out.
And Connor, how are things?
Could use my old quarterback
back on the team.
Talk some sense into him.
Oh, I don't understand
sportsball, so...
Can't keep a spot open
for you forever, Trev.
Why didn't you just deal with him
right then and there?
Not in front of the kid.
It's gonna be hard enough
on him as it is.
HIP HOP MUSIC PLAYS
Seventy-eight...
Seventy-nine...
One-thousand!
HE LAUGHS
I'm really digging us
working out together.
Yeah? That's good.
And this playlist...
Damn.
You like it?
- Oh, yeah.
You gotta... You gotta get that,
that core engaged, right?
You know what I mean?
Get that heart rate up.
SHE LAUGHS
You know what I mean?
- SHE LAUGHS
Unh... Come on, Carly.
You know that body likes to dance.
I don't even know what you're doing.
- Come on, Carly, it'll come to you.
Let it go.
That's right.
OK!
There she is.
BABY CRIES
MARCY:
Hey.
What did you find?
I took a look at her file. There's nothing
out of the ordinary.
She's stable.
Her blood pressure's a little high-—
- Those drugs you gave me
shouldn't they have
protected her from this?
They were designed to help
not to make her invulnerable.
HE SIGHS
How do we get you in there?
I don't think you understand.
There's nothing even I could do.
She's right where she needs to be
and if they need to take the baby
out early, a Caesarean section
is a standard procedure
for these doctors.
Medicine isn't magic, in any time.
Would you like me to inform
the team of what's going on?
No.
No, I'll do it when the time is right.
MIKE:
And, uh, yeah
it just feels good to know
I'm not doing that to my family anymore.
ALL:
Thank you, Mike.
Philip...
COLIN:
Did you want to share?
Uh, yeah, I do.
Hi. My name is Philip
and I'm an addict.
ALL: Hi, Philip.
I have a secret.
I know the future.
I know what's going to happen.
Global events.
Deaths.
Winners of horse races.
It was all recently delivered to me
like a movie.
And mostly, it's the same future
that I remember
but there are differences.
You all think I'm crazy right now...
but it's true.
For example...
I know that somebody in this room has very
recently been diagnosed with cancer
and has decided to ignore it.
As if ignoring the problem is going to
make it go away.
Because there's only a 50/50 chance
that the treatment will work.
And they're afraid of going through
the pain of chemotherapy for nothing.
And the truth is, I don't know...
whether this person is going to live
or die if they decide to get treatment.
I only know for certain that without it...
IN THE DISTANCE:
Philip?
I'm sorry, what... what was I saying?
Not much.
You stopped talking after you said,
"I have a secret."
Oh.
I'm sorry. Um...
Maybe someone else should go.
It's alright.
We've all been there.
HEAVY METAL MUSIC BLARES
CAR HORN BEEPS
MONITOR BEEPS STEADILY
PHONE RINGS
Where have you been?
- I'm on my way now.
Don't worry about it, bro.
We're gonna do this.
Have you been drinking?
Pull over.
Trevor, I'm fine. Chill.
TREVOR:
Where are you?
Where are you? Where are you?
Oh, hey, nurse. How's she doing?
Excuse me. I asked you a question.
No.
It was for your own good.
What did you do?
ALARM SOUNDS
[FEMALE VOICE ON PA]
Code blue. Code blue.
Resus team to room 372...
- Go be with her.
Dr Higgins, what's happening?
- I can't talk right now, Mr MacLaren.
Please stay out of the way.
- FEMALE VOICE: Resus team
'to room 312 immediately
Philip, I need eyes on Hall right now.
He's leaving the hospital.
PHILIP ON COM:
I'm on it.
Don't lose him.
HIGH-PITCHED RINGING
TREVOR:
Kyle! Kyle!
Back up!
Kyle, get outta the car.
There's something wrong with this host.
No.
LUCA:
You're just drunk.
Traveler 5532.
Welcome to the 21st.
This is too much.
Andrew, I have watched you do everything in
your power to change your circumstances.
I mean, you got clean, you got that
part-time job at the grocery store.
This is just a little financial help
to put a roof over your head.
But I'll never be able
to repay you. This-
DAVID:
No, I don't want you to. Just, just-
Just keep doing what you're doing
and I'll count myself lucky to know you.
I don't know what to say.
- You don't have to say anything-
Oh!
Thank you, David.
HE CHUCKLES
OK.
Wendy?
I'd like to make your day.
MACLAREN: Come on.
You must know something by now.
My latest information is that your wife
is still in surgery.
DR HIGGINS:
Mr MacLaren.
Would you come with me, please?
TREVOR SHOUTS:
Philip!
Look, I need your help.
Look, I know that the historical record has
changed since
we got here, but not everything, right?
A lot stays the same.
Yeah, why?
- Carson Perry.
He's a football coach at my high school.
Ring any bells?
Come on, dig deep.
Carson Perry...
Gets arrested on 16 counts
of sexual assault charges, as well as
possession and distribution
of under-age pornography.
When?
- Not soon.
We can't wait.
Trev, I've been through this, you assign
yourself vigilante missions-
- What if it's my protocol five?
TREVOR:
I recently learned that my host
was abused before I got here by him.
I had no idea.
Neither did I.
I promised my friend, Kyle,
that I would help take him down
and just now...
- Kyle was a host candidate.
You knew?
- 3:09, this afternoon.
Driving drunk. I'm sorry.
I understand why you couldn't tell me
but as far as I'm concerned,
that coach killed him.
I need to fix this...
KNOCKS ON DOOR
DR HIGGINS:
Mr. MacLaren, in this case, it was
antiphospholipid antibody
syndrome, or APS.
She developed an arterial thrombus
which then caused a coronary embolism,
which is a clot in the heart.
Kathryn went into cardiac arrest.
Mr MacLaren, in our efforts to save
Kathryn's life...
We lost the baby.
- Yes.
And all I can say is that it's...
extremely fortunate that
that clot passed on its own
or this would be an even more difficult
conversation for both of us to have.
When can I see her?
She's in recovery, she's sedated,
but you can see her in a few hours.
Mr MacLaren, we have counsellors
available if you need them.
COM BEEPS
- Philip, tell me where Hall is.
PHILIP ON COM: Boss, he 's here.
What?
TREVOR: Hey, boss.
- PHILIP: Easy...
Get off of me!
- CARLY: Listen!
PHILIP: We can't do that.
- MACLAREN: You're a fucking
dead man!
- I know, I know...
You killed my child!
- Not what happened.
You'd better hope
the Director overwrites you
before I get... HALL: The
Director was the one who sent me!
I was on a mission.
HALL:
Let him go.
There you go.
What're you talking about?
The child was never going to survive.
It was never supposed to.
- You don't know that.
My mission was to save your wife.
There had to be a way to save them both.
MARCY:
I don't think there was.
HALL:
Listen to your medic, MacLaren.
What did you do?
Kathryn MacLaren was going to die
of an undiagnosed coronary embolism
that stopped her heart during the
delivery of her stillborn child.
HALL: The Director ordered me
to give her a traveler-synthesised drug
to eliminate the clot
so that she would survive
because she wasn't supposed to die
because you broke Protocol Four.
She wanted a child more than anything.
HE SCOFFS
You're gonna stand there and uh...
and blame her for this?
Is that what you're doing?
No.
Right.
Look, I get it.
HALL: I get it. It's tough
to stay focused in the 21st.
That's what I've been trying to tell
you guys ever since I met you.
Trying to teach you guys
to not get caught up in all the bullshit.
HALL:
But you had to stab me in the back, huh?
The Director obviously agreed with me
or you wouldn't have gone to prison.
Yeah...
I can't argue with that.
HALL: I guess we all need a lesson
now and then of what our mission is.
And this was yours.
But, hey.
MacLaren, your wife is still alive.
Go be with her.
Welcome home.
Hey. Yeah. Sorry.
Hi.
- CHILD GURGLES
I know it's later than I said.
Can I hold him?
I was trying to get him to go to sleep.
- I know. I don't care.
CARLY:
Hey.
JEFFREY: You wanna cuddle
with your mama, big man?
So...
How was today for Carly Shannon?
It's over now, let's leave it at that.
You?
I had a pay duty.
I basically just chaperoned some drunk
college kids around for time and a half.
Sounds awful.
- Wasn't so bad.
You OK?
Tell me about the day he was born.
Ah...
Are you sure you wanna
go there right now?
Cos that's not your favourite story.
I want to hear it from your perspective.
JEFFREY SNIGGER
KATHRYN:
Grant?
HE WHISPERS:
I'm here.
They told me she was a girl.
SHE SOBS
Holden.
Change your mind?
You're going to come clean.
Sorry?
You're going to come forward
to the police
and you're going to detail all
that you've done.
Trevor, what are you talking about?
Do it on your own volition
and face the consequences
or it'll be done for you.
Yeah?
- TREVOR: Mm-hmm.
I'm not gonna do that.
Those are your only two options, so...
I don't think you realise what
you're doing, here.
You're really willing to throw everything
away to destroy both of our lives?
TREVOR: There's other lives to consider.
- Oh, come on.
Maybe you don't want
to play football anymore
but you do not want
the shit storm that'll come from this.
You prey on young boys
who look up to you.
You make promises in exchange
for access to their bodies.
Come on, Trev.
I will come forward.
I'll talk about the
hotel rooms on the road.
The showers.
All of it.
Who's gonna believe you?
You're a bad kid
and everybody knows it.
People change.
COACH PERRY:
Not the Trevor Holden I know...
I don't know where this act came from,
but I don't buy it for a second.
I know you.
Intimately.
You're going to keep your mouth shut.
I'm not threatened by you.
- You should be.
Don't push me, kid.
Release the materials.
PHILIP ON COM: On it.
- Release the materials?
What the hell's that supposed to mean?
Thank you, Philip.
TREVOR ON COM: That's What
Trevor and Kyle would've wanted.
PHILIP: All we did was accelerate
what was going to happen anyway.
Freak had whole hard drives
of incriminating shit.
He made his choice.
COMPUTER CHIMES
COACH PERRY:
No...
What?
PHONE CHIMES
COACH PERRY:
Oh, no.
PHONE RINGS
Oh, my God.
COMPUTER CHIMES
Oh...
DOOR OPENS
There she is!
Did you get your winnings?
- I did.
Amazing luck.
- Isn't it!
You're not upset that I cheated?
No, of course not. I'm happy for you.
You must be thrilled.
- Yeah! Yeah.
It's all gone.
What?
Did you ever hear of the story
of St. Francis?
No.
- Yeah. No, me neither.
Somebody called me that today.
I don't understand.
I didn't feel right taking what would
have been yours
if I hadn't peeked at your numbers,
and I know
that you wouldn't let me give it back,
so I gave it all away.
I helped out a lot of good people.
Honestly, Marcy, it was...
It was the best day of my life.
Remember my... my client, Jason
with the bad teeth and the hair?
Yeah. I do.
- Yeah. Great teeth now.
I mean, they will be.
Even getting them cleaned has made
a huge difference.
And on Wednesday, he's got some
much-needed dental work.
Good for Jason.
Yeah! No, he hates dentists.
Who else?
I'm not sure if you remember Marjorie.
I bought her a new walker.
They're pricey for what they are.
Uh... Steve got one of those scooters
to get to his new job.
He can't walk very far without breaking
into a sweat.
Jordan got my bike for his
pizza delivery job.
Your bike?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I thought I'd buy myself a new one.
I should have saved some.
All of it?
I know it sounded like a lot of money, but,
I mean, everything is just so expensive
and I had a whole list of people.
David...
- It doesn't matter.
I'll get my steps in.
So...
What're you gonna do with yours?
Um...
I have some debts to pay off.
Debts!
Wow, that is responsible.
SHE CHUCKLES
I should have some left over.
Even more responsible!
So what're you gonna do with it?
Well, first...
I'm going to buy you a new bike.
I'm so happy you said that.
THEY LAUGH
What's happening right now?
Where the hell is this kid?
Give him a minute.
He's probably hungover.
I'm sorry, he's what?
Sorry, I'm late.
I was having a hard time deciding
what clothing to bring with me.
Yeah, not a problem, kid.
Just don't make it a habit.
So, what's the mission?
REPORTER: the Prime Minister has
called highly threatening.
PHILIP AND REPORTER: This will 59
vere/y impact foreign relations
if the troops continue to invade the region
against U. N. sanctions.
REPORTER: ln local news, a fire ravaged
a downtown apartment complex last night
and authorities are saying that the cause
of it is more than likely...
REPORTER'S VOICE ECHOES
PHILIP REMEMBERS JERVIS' WORDS:
The yellow pills will help
to focus your sensory perception
on one timeline at a time..
An unavoidable side-effect of memory not
acquired by conventional means...