JENNY: 3326 access
memory chain 71985VX...
JENNY'S VOICE ECHOES:
Write it down.
VOICE ECHOES:
That's all of it?
Philip? Is that all of it?
Is it error-free?
Yes.
Is it good?
It's great. Can you move?
CAMERA CLICKS
- DOOR KNOCKS
How did you get in?
Little girl named Chloe.
I said I would send it to you.
Yeah, well, something like this,
I have to see for myself.
TRAVELER D-13: Those stereoisomers
are going to be difficult to reproduce.
VOICE ECHOING:
We're gonna have to do it in batches.
JENNY:
We're leaving.
TRAVELER D13:
Sure. Good work, Philip.
VOICES ECHO
Oh... Oh. God.
What did we do last night?
We were going to your place.
We did.
We did?
HE CHUCKLES
This is disturbing.
You hit the drops pretty hard.
Mm...
It's never felt like this before.
It'll pass.
We need to talk.
This has to end.
What?
This. Us.
I got a new mission.
What mission?
Sorry, Philip.
Lightning struck.
So "goodbye"?
We never see each other again?
I... I thought we had a connection.
Right.
I am your connection.
That's not what I meant.
That should last you a few months
if you use 'em the way
you're supposed to.
Jenny.
Jenny!
JEFFREY CRIES
- OK. It's almost over.
THERMOMETER BEEPS
OK.
- A hundred point six.
It's high, but manageable.
I know, I know, I know, I know.
So, um...
alternate between these two:
acetaminophen and ibuprofen.
It should manage his fever
or whatever pain he might be in.
CARLY: That's it?
- That's it.
He should be fine in a few days.
- JEFFREY CRIES
You hear that, baby?
Auntie Marcy says you're gonna be alright.
Ah.
Stay for coffee?
Sure.
OK.
So I'll put him down.
JEFFREY GRIZZLES
TREVOR:
Philip.
You've been quiet lately.
Yeah, not much to say.
Well, some people find talking about it
to be therapeutic.
It has been two weeks.
You know that doesn't make
a difference for me, right?
I remember every detail
as if it just happened.
OK, good chat. Ahem.
HE KNOCKS
Who is it?
TREVOR:
0115.
PHILIP:
3326.
We were given orders to meet you.
You must be Graham.
Yeah. Come on in.
You boys hungry? I got soup on.
No, thank you.
- TREVOR: Smells delicious.
You have a lovely home.
It's just temporary.
Driving up and down the state,
making hand-offs.
PHILIP:
Along mission.
Well, roll out's been longer than expected
but I ain't complaining.
I got to see three eagles!
Hopefully you're done soon.
Yeah, well, your team's
one of the last on the list.
SUDDEN VIOLENT COUGHING
Excuse me.
Here you go.
TREVOR: What a lovely couple.
Thank you for coming
and checking him out.
I know I probably sounded crazy.
No, you don't sound crazy.
You had a natural maternal instinct.
CARLY LAUGHS
I don't know about natural.
It's not like I'm really his mother.
Yeah, you are.
In every way that means something.
You guys have bonded.
Who would've thought
that would happen to somebody like me?
MARCY:
You mean a soldier?
Maybe you've changed.
Maybe we all have.
I mean, I have to believe that
we are more than
just our consciousness.
At least, the one we came here with.
Maybe that's...
Maybe that's the better part of us.
It's funny, you said something like that
the night that you...
Um...
What?
The night that I was reset?
What did I say?
Mac didn't tell you?
Well, he said that it was the only way to
save my life.
It was.
Well?
I really didn't have any choice then.
You thought you did.
What? What does that mean?
I shouldn't have said anything.
- No, Carly.
We just didn't know
it was gonna happen so fast.
Are you saying that it happened
against my will?
I don't know.
We thought you had more time.
So did you.
You said you wanted to go home
because you wanted to think about it.
What could there possibly
be to think about?
I mean, I'd be dead.
I know, that's what I said at the time.
Now I'm beginning to understand.
This is exactly how it happened last time.
Kat... you've been taking your medication
you've done everything by the book.
It's gonna be alright.
- Oh, stop saying that.
DOOR OPENS
Hi. Apologies.
The, uh, the printer was down.
How are we?
Kathryn, the, uh, latest ultrasound
it looks good.
It looks really good.
The dark Spot's completely gone
which means that it was probably nothing
or maybe just a mistake with the scan.
You and the baby are fine.
I'm sorry...
Thank you.
- DOCTOR: You're welcome.
Now, I want you to stick to the
calcium-rich foods, the folic acid, and...
OK
- I'll see you in a few weeks.
WHISPERING: OK.
- Thanks.
OK.
Thank you.
SHE LAUGHS
HE LAUGHS
SHE SIGHS
DOOR OPENS
What was in the package?
- An antiviral.
Historically, this is the beginning
of a minor flu outbreak
that kills 70,000 people worldwide.
That does not sound "minor" to me.
Percentage-wise. we're not wired
to think in "billions" of people.
Over a few months, an antigenic shift
allows the virus to mutate
infecting more of the population.
Eventually, the CDC and WHO get it
under control.
Must be why they provided
a broad-spectrum antiviral.
This will inhibit
the development of each of its mutations.
Our mission is to save three of the people
who, historically, don't make it.
Are there any more?
Jeffrey's already been through
the worst of it.
You need to protect yourself.
Couldn't we have gotten
the pill version?
These are the host candidates?
Jordan Lam, Annie Kapoor
and Brittney Palmer.
Personal trainer, a flight attendant
and a travel blogger.
Prime hosts that must
have spread the virus.
Well, let's make sure that doesn't happen.
INOCULATOR CLICKS
WOK SIZZLES
- INDISTINCT CHATTER
TRAFFIC NOISE
Are you gonna do the whole class?
Just waiting for the right
opportunity.
Hi, Brittney.
- Hey.
I'll be doing your vaccinations today.
OK.
- So you can take a seat.
MAN SHOUTS
That's it.
Have fun in Europe.
Thanks.
WOMAN WHEEZES
SHE SPEAKS GERMAN:
Main Asthma.
SHE GASPS FOR BREATH
SHE EXHALES DEEPLY
MACLAREN GASPS:
Oh!
God. I was stung by a freakin' bee.
Me too. I think.
Are you allergic?
No. I'm not.
- Good.
CARLY TYPES
NEWS REPORTER, RADIO:
as reports are increasing
of an unknown flu strain'
that seems to be rapidly spreading
throughout the country.
'The World Health Organization'
describes the condition
as ”atypical influenza ”
and confirms five cases
have been reported
in the Pacific Northwest so far.
-  It's starting.
Good. Nice work, everybody.
Protocol five until further notice.
ENGINE STARTS
We need to talk.
Hello, Miss Day.
When's the last time you heard
from the Director?
LAUGHING: The school board director?
- What are you talking about?
Hey, you're worried about them?
Please! There's literally nothing going on
inside their tiny brains.
The girls are thinking about
their insipid friendships
and the boys are imagining them naked.
What do you want?
SPEAKING VERY SLOWLY:
Have you heard
from the Director?
Yeah, we've had missions.
Well, why haven't I heard anything?
I don't know. Maybe because
you jumped here without permission?
Or maybe because you don't have a team?
Maybe I can join your team.
I could be your computer expert.
Nah, we already have a computer expert.
I could be your vastly-more-capable
computer expert.
Doesn't work like that.
- Well, it should! I'm getting bored!
You gonna finish that?
Wow.
Mm! Fake chicken.
TREVOR LAUGHS
Mm!
Hey have you seen my, uh,
my work jacket?
You were supposed to take Jeffrey today.
I know that, but I just got called in.
There's this big bug going around.
So?
So I'm going to work.
What'd I say?
SHE SIGHS
It's what you didn't say.
"Hey, Carly.
"I know I was supposed to take
Jeffrey today, but something came up.
Can you help?"
Well, why do I have to say all of that?
You're his mother.
And you're his father.
We said we were going to do this together.
Equal partners, remember?
Carly Shannon
would you please help me out
by taking our gorgeous son to the
babysitter's house
so that I can go to work
as an underpaid
underappreciated, beat cop
one more day?
Fine.
But you're doing pick-ups
for the rest of the week.
Absolutely.
And your jacket's on the hook by the door.
Thank you.
See you, little man.
I'll see you, uh, see you tonight.
Hey. You want your ducky?
JEFFREY GURGLES
Yeah, you do.
Oh, ho, ho, ho.
Oh? Where are you taking him?
CARLY GIGGLES
PHILIP:
Hello?
BOYD:
3185. Has your team taken the antiviral?
Yeah.
- OK, let us in.
DEVICE BEEPS
DOOR BUZZES OPEN
Oof!
BOYD COUGHS
Where's Marcy?
PHONE KEYS BEEP
PHONE RINGS
DAVID'S RECORDED VOICE: Hi. This is
David Mai/er. Please leave a message.
ANSWERPHONE BEEPS
Hi, David. Um, it's me, Marcy.
Just wondering if you wanted
to maybe get together to talk.
PHILIP ON COM: Marcy, you there?
Uh, so, if you'd like to,
just give me a call back.
OK. Bye.
PHILIP ON COM: Marcy?
-  PHONE BEEPS OFF
SHE SIGHS
Yeah, Philip, go ahead.
PHILIP:
We need you at Ops.
'Boyd showed up with one of her teammates..
What's happening?
I don't know.
She said it's some kind of viral infection.
NEWS REPORTER:
There's growing concern
for an outbreak of a new flu strain'
that has infected a number of people
in recent days.
While much is still unknown
about the virus...
Hey, Sarge.
I never got my assignment.
Connicker, what are you doing here?
- I'm filling in.
Yeah, right. This flu is kicking us around.
You get your shot yet?
No. Not yet.
- Well, you better get on it.
You covering McAllister or Boyd?
- McAllister.
Hospital.
NEWS REPORTER:
The infection rate appears to be higher
'than that of the average seasonal flu..
HE COUGHS AND SNIFFS
- While death tolls are still
much lower than a normal flu'
health authorities are
expressing concern
'over the intensity of the symptoms'
and the speed in which
the virus seems to be spreading.
MARCY:
So it presents like classic flu
fever, sore throat, headache.
BOYD:
Yeah, but it's not the flu.
He received the same broad-spectrum
antiviral we all did.
OK, so a virus that's not the flu...
Um...
Meningitis? West Nile?
I checked those.
I checked them all, actually.
There's no match.
Well...
- BOYD COUGHS
OK, well, if it's a virus, we can
identify which one it is.
I've checked every gene sequence
for every virus
in the 21st and every century after that.
Are you saying that it's a new pathogen?
Yeah. Unknown in this time or in ours.
How is that even possible?
BOYD COUGHS
RAGGED WEAK BREATHING
HE MOANS
"O, my love, my wife!"
"Death..."
"that has sucked the honey of thy breath"
"hath had no power yet
upon thy beauty."
STUDENTS SNIGGER
TEACHER:
Seriously, you guys?
How old are you?
Go ahead, Trevor.
"Upon thy beauty."
"Thou art not conquered."
"Beauty's ensign yet
is crimson in thy lips and in thy cheeks
and death's pale flag..."
MARCY ON COM: Trevor? You there?
Aye.
STUDENTS SNIGGER
TEACHER:
Good. OK, OK.
TEACHER ON COM: Take it from, um-
Are you in class?
Mm-hmm.
- TEACHER: "Dear Juliet"
"Dear Juliet, Why art thou yet so fair?"
MARCY ON COM: OK, you need to leave.
You might be infected
with a dangerous pathogen.
Just keep your distance
from other people and get outside.
What's happening?
- MARCY: Just go now.
We're skipping to the last section.
One final embrace, one last kiss
and then you drink the poison.
MARCY: Go, now. MacLaren's waiting for you
I gotta go.
You don't have to kiss, just read.
- TREVOR STAMMERS
SHOUTING: Don't! Don't touch me!
I'm sorry, I gotta go.
DOOR RATTLES
Hardly even looks like a virus.
No, you kind of expect something
pleomorphic.
Spherical capsid... radial symmetry.
That's what's infected us?
That's what we're trying to determine.
Oh, good! I need blood from both of you.
What do you call it?
- BOYD: Mm. We haven't got that far yet.
Boyd's viral count
is up in the hundreds of thousands
her teammate's up over a million.
Here...
Here. Seems to be tied
to the antiviral mission somehow.
We got it two weeks before you did.
Heath's immune system was already
compromised.
I had to remove one of his lungs
after a mission blew up near the beginning.
His antibodies are showing no
cross-reactivity
his body just keeps amplifying it.
So how do we get it under control?
MONITOR ALARM BEEPS
CARLY:
Heath! Little help? Guys!
BOYD: We need to sedate him!
Keep holding him down!
MONITORS BEEP WILDLY
SYRINGE CLICKS
- MONITOR SOUNDS CONTINUOUSLY
BOYD: I can't get at BP.
- There's no pulse.
One, two... three, four...
five, six, seven
eight, nine, ten.
11,12,13,14,15,16,17,18,19,20-
- Stop CPR.
MONITOR SOUNDS CONTINUOUSLY
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven
eight, nine, ten.
One, two, three, four, five six
- He's gone. Marcy.
Seven, eight...
- Marcy! He's gone.
MONITOR WAILS
- MARCY PANTS
I'm sorry.
Come on.
Let's get you off your feet.
You need some rest.
I think it's a little late for that.
So...
how's it looking?
We're all infected, aren't we?
Not all.
SHE SIGHS
You, Philip, and Carly have it.
You and I somehow rejected the virus.
What?
Each of your blood samples
has a viral load between 500
and 1,000 copies per millilitre.
Ours is zero.
- What about antibodies?
Trace amounts.
- Somehow, we're immune.
How is that possible?
It's hard to say, without
running more tests.
So, if we're immune, can't you create
a blood serum?
We'll try, but we might be
running out of time.
If this started with the mission,
we can't be the only ones.
Check the deep web for any other teams
reporting the same symptoms.
If it's transmitted
through air particles and fomites
that means there's a good chance
you've infected everyone
you've come into contact with.
Are you sure?
Outside of an immunity
we're predicting an infection rate
of over 40%.
PHILIP:
Forty?
Call everyone you've
come into contact with.
Tell them to stay inside.
Boss, you're gonna want to see this.
Traveler teams from around the world
are reporting the same sickness.
MARCY: They've been transmitting it
this whole time.
If I get you more of the antiviral,
can you analyse it?
See what went wrong?
Possibly, but I'm running low
on ethidium bromide.
It's a controlled substance
it's not something you can get
on short notice.
What about your hospital?
Yeah, the lab should have some.
I'll text you a name.
You two, track down the team
that handed off the vials
I'll go to the hospital.
I've got to get my son
from the babysitter's.
Carly! You're infected.
The best thing that you can do
for Jeffrey right now
is stay away.
VOICE OF MARCY RECORDED: Hi, David.
Um, it's me, Marcy.
I was just wondering if you wanted
to maybe get together to talk.
Uh, so, if you'd like to,
just give me a call back.
'OK, bye“.
PHONE BUTTONS BEEP
PHONE RINGS
MOBILE PHONE RINGS
David?
DAVID:
Marcel Hey! Sorry, I just got your message.
I was out riding.
Uh, I'd love to meet up.
MARCY:
Um, where are you right now?
I'm at home.
- MARCY: OK, don't leave.
You coming over?
- No, David. Uh...
A dangerous flu is spreading.
Like SARS?
Worse than that.
What?
Wait. What-what? Where are you?
I'm... I'm safe. Just...
Why do I get more worried
every time you say that?
David, you don't need to worry
about me, OK?
Well, I do, I worry about you.
And I worry about my
clients, most of whom...
don't have a home to stay inside of.
David...
Just stay home.
I've seen how bad this can get.
Marce, I'm sorry. Thank you for
telling me, but I've got to go.
David!
RADIO NEWS PLAYS SOFTLY
REPORTER:
have reported a wide range of symptoms
from common flu ailments'
like headache, fatigue, and fever
'to, in rare cases, more extreme symptoms'
including redness
and bleeding around the eyes.
'At this point'
health authorities are advising the public
'to stay home if they feel sick...
REPORT CONTINUES
INDISTINCTLY
Where are you headed?
Home.
When you get there, stay there.
There seems to be a bad flu going around.
And tell everyone you know, alright?
Sure thing.
REPORTER:
Officials have been able to determine
that despite being referred to
by most as ”the flu”
this is not actually a new strain of
influenza
'but rather a new virus completely..
'The origins of the virus remain'
unknown and concern for the public
surrounding the sickness
continues to grow, as hospitals
doctors offices and walk-in clinics
tare all finding that they're...
Mac, where are you?
It's all-hands over here.
I know, listen. Did you receive
an antiviral in the last two weeks?
Yeah, I had to save some hosts.
Any of your team sick?
Yeah. Three of us. Why?
MACLAREN:
We've seen Traveler reports
this is happening all over the world
and I think we are the
primary transmitters.
Shit!
I have my team tracking down
the antiviral, to run some tests.
FORBES: Alright, well,
let me know how it goes.
In the meantime,
the CDC's setting up shelters.
Wakefield wants us
to meet up with the National Guard.
' I'll text you the address..
Look, I'm on my way to the hospital.
I'll have to meet you in 30.
Alright.
WRACKED, STRAINED COUGHING
COUGHING
GUN COCKS
Graham?
Graham! It's Trevor.
I'll go check the back.
- OK.
SIRENS WAILING
RADIOS CRACKLE
- INDISTINCT CHATTER
Hi. Sorry. Can you tell me
who's in charge here?
What do you need?
He's got a bad fever, a headache.
He needs to see a doctor.
Well, he's not gonna get one here.
The ER's been in overflow for an hour
and people with the flu
are being sent home.
He'll be better off at home.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Nurse, he doesn't have a home.
Well, he's better off anywhere but here.
You his family?
Case worker.
How many people are you
caring for right now?
Uh...
HE CHUCKLES
Officially or unofficially?
Wait here.
INDISTINCT CHATTER
Oh. Here. Um...
It's not much,
but it's better than nothing.
Thank you.
Yeah. Be sure to keep one for yourself.
Thank you, that's very kind.
- Take care!
Agent MacLaren!
David.
Is Marcy here?
No.
Maybe you could pass along
a message for me?
Could you ask her
to come by the shelter a little later?
These guys are in rough shape.
I'll pass it along
but her hands are pretty full right now.
Yeah, I bet.
MAN: Excuse me! Why are you taking her?
We were here first!
I'm not taking anyone, sir, relax.
We've got a kid here!
DAVID:
How bad is it?
OK. I'll let you get to it, then.
Remember to ask Marcy.
I will. Good luck.
Yeah, you too.
Pupils are sluggish.
Intracranial pressure?
I mean, that would explain
the headaches and the seizures.
We could try mannitol
or skip straight to a cerebral shunt.
Great.
Isn't that your specialty?
Funny.
- KNOCKING AT THE DOOR
PHILIP:
We got company.
GRACE:
Let me in!
I can't, we're sick.
So am I! Let me in!
PHILIP SIGHS
- DEVICE BEEPS
DOOR BUZZES OPEN
One of those teenage petri dishes
got me sick.
What's all this?
We got a mission to save people
who were gonna die from the flu
but the Director's antiviral didn't work.
That's impossible.
PHILIP: There's also an outbreak
in Shanghai and Berlin.
CARLY ON COM: Hey, Mac, you there?
Go ahead.
We found the delivery
team, but no antiviral.
The supply was cleared out
and the team had been assassinated.
What?
CARLY ON COM: There was no sign
of struggle or forced entry.
Are you thinking inside job?
It wouldn't be the first time
a team turned on each other.
Right?
None of this makes any sense.
OK. I'll see you back at Ops.
She doesn't look good.
Not helpful.
Hold this above her head.
None of this matters
in the long run.
The Director will fix it!
Didn't fix him.
Traveler incoming.
DOOR BUZZES OPEN
Ah! Told ya!
Here comes the cavalry.
It's good to see you. We need help.
Everyone does.
- Alright, let's have the cure.
We can chat later.
There is no cure.
- What?
Of course there is.
We're from the future.
Several teams are working on a viricide
but so far without success.
I'm here to talk to Philip.
I want to go over the antiviral data
one more time. Maybe we made a mistake.
I don't know what you're talking about.
The formula you wrote on the wall.
It allowed us
to synthesise the antiviral.
It's right here, look.
PHILIP:
I remember this...
but I don't remember writing it down.
How do you not remember? That's impossible.
When did this happen?
TRAVELER D-13:
About two weeks ago.
You were with 4514.
Jenny.
What?
- I had a headache
and she told me it was from the drops.
She must have given you
a memory inhibitor.
Oh, God.
- Please tell me what is going on.
Just go get her!
MACLAREN: Hello?
- KATHRYN: Hey. It's me.
What's happening?
Are you alright?
Grant, have you seen the news?
No. [haven't Are you sure you're OK?
Yeah, just feeling a bit...
shaky, I don't know.
Probably just the news making me crazy.
Can you come home?
Not yet. Look, just lie down, Kat.
And stay inside, OK?
KATHRYN:
OK. What about you?
Are you gonna be alright?
-  JEFFREY: Well, look at this.
Grant?
I gotta go. I just...
uh, I'll call you soon.
Come to get a look at
some real police work?
Carly's worried about your son.
You need to pick him up and go home.
You running errands for her now?
I thought that shit was over between you.
It was never what you thought it was
and, right now, this is about
something bigger than that.
You need to pick up your son,
Jeff, and go home.
POLICE RADIO CHATTERS
COM BEEPS
- Hey, it's Marcy. We need you back at Ops.
We know the source of the antiviral.
A Traveler named Jenny.
Philip knows her.
I'm on my way.
FORBES: Mac, it's been over an hour.
- What are you doing here?
We're late. We gotta meet
with the National Guard.
You'll have to do it without me.
We need you.
My team comes first.
Jenny!
Chloe!
Jenny?
HE COUGHS
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no. Jenny. Hey, hey.
Hey! Hey.
No. No, no. No. No.
LABOURED BREATHING
Are you sure about this?
Do I have any other choice?
SHE COUGHS
- Alright.
Her Vitals are good.
- BOYD GASPING
Oh...
SHE COUGHS
BOYD GASPING
She's stable.
OK.
CHILD CRIES
Carly?
CRYING CONTINUES
Shit.
It's OK HE COUGHS
Shh... It's OK, I've got you.
I got you. It's OK.
JEFFREY COUGHS
- CHILD WAILS
Shh-shh-shh. It's OK.
It's OK. It's OK.
DAVID:
You know, when I was a kid
my mum would make me chicken soup
when I was sick.
Not exactly sure why
it was always chicken soup.
Vera!
Hey, I was trying to reach you.
I said no doctors!
OK. No, no.
- Don't touch me.
No. It's David. See?
SHE LAUGHS
- Hi!
You OK?
- Yeah.
Alright. You got something to eat?
Ok. I'll be around
if you need me. OK?
It's OK, big man.
We're gonna get through this.
CHILD CRIES
- We're gonna be fine.
You're a fighter.
Just like Mama.
Just like Daddy.
CRYING CONTINUES
- It's OK, it's OK.
It's OK. It's OK.
Hey.
I sense that doctor you sent me to
likes you a lot.
Where's... what's-her-name, Jenny?
They should be back any minute.
- Philip knows her how?
Ah, oh... So what's this?
I'm trying to determine
the pathogen's reproduction number
based on hospital databases, social media
updates...
Here. Let me show you something.
An "r-nought" indicates
how infectious a virus is
by determining the rate of secondary
infection.
If it's less than one
the virus will quickly die out.
If it's greater than one...
We have an epidemic.
So what are we dealing with?
Let's put it into perspective...
Influenza has an r-nought of one...
With an incubation period of two days.
Chances are you'd infect
one person in a day
then they'd go on to infect
one more, and so on.
This virus has an r-nought of at least two
with an incubation period...
of 10 days.
Fourteen days ago
ten Traveler teams across the world
transmitted the virus.
So that is...
Potentially, 150
people on day one...
Three hundred and thirty...
on day two.
- I don't like where this is going.
So, based on the data I pulled
from people already reporting symptoms
and factoring in
the exponential growth rate...
Over 4 million people
are currently infected.
Tomorrow, it'll be almost 10.
Most of them aren't showing symptoms yet,
but they will soon.
So how long before the death rate
starts to climb?
A couple of days.
PHILIP:
I need some help out here!
Clear off that table.
Marcy, I don't know if she's breathing.
She took pills.
Get her up here.
TRAVELER D-13:
I got a weak pulse!
What'd she take?
- Oxycodone.
JENNY GASPS
- PHILIP: Hey, hey
Jenny, I'm here. I'm here.
You're at Ops. You're safe.
JENNY COUGHS
- PHILIP: You're safe.
You overdosed. I found you in your room.
Hey! Listen to me.
Listen to me.
The mission is in trouble.
No, Philip.
The mission went exactly as planned.
MACLAREN:
What?
What do you know?
- It won't change anything.
What did you make me do?
JENNY PANTS
My team...
they tried to record messengers...
JENNY GROANS
but any incoming signal
caused static on our devices.
We needed a historian.
And someone to synthesise the catalyst.
No.
I was directed to create an antiviral.
Actually, you were...
directed to expedite genetic
recombination of the historical pathogen.
You created the new virus.
No, no, no. She's delirious.
The Director would never
order that mission.
Who said the mission
came from the Director?
The future I left
was divided
between those loyal to the Director
and the Faction.
Both sides fighting for control
back and forth.
When you reset the Director,
we lost the ability to access the 21st.
We lost the past, we lost everything.
We had no choice
but to shut down the reactor.
We've had missions.
Received messengers.
And that's all. Only messengers.
Without the Director's processing power
consciousness transfer isn't possible.
So...
before power was cut to the Director
in our last moment of control,
we sent everyone we could to the 21st.
All at once.
Into the quantum frame?
How many?
The frame is capable
of receiving and storing thousands.
So Forbes,
all those people with the FBI...
Are all Faction.
Every mission we've done since...
- Has been for them.
JENNY:
The Faction has our own plan.
Overpopulation is the single greatest
threat to the 21st century.
The Director wasn't capable
of seeing the natural solution.
How many people are gonna die?
The virus is genetically engineered
to preserve 70% of the population.
The future will survive.
SHE COUGHS
And those of us who die,
including me
will have made a great sacrifice.
Seventy percent? Jenny,
you're murdering over 2 billion people.
The mission comes first.
FORBES: Take positions
around the device and stand by.
GUARD:
What the hell is that?