I am so sorry.
RANDY: How could he be offering
a Whistler chalet
a Tuscan villa,
and a Caribbean hideaway
all for 20,000 dollars?
I've gotta be honest...
I'm wondering the same thing.
Look, I've been
doing this a while
and I have
never seen a deal like this!
So which property
appeals to you the most?
Maybe the Caribbean hideaway?
Don't we all
wish we were there right now?
But seven to ten days a year?
That's, like,
2,000 dollars a day.
RANDY:
Yeah! If you go once!
It's a lifestyle.
Isn't that what you said
you were interested in, Dale?
Yeah... I said that.
But that was after you said
this would only take ninety minutes
and we'd get a free dinner
at House of Rib.
Ninety minutes...
No, I hear you.
RANDY:
Alright...
I don't know how I'm gonna do it
but let me go talk to my manager
and see if we can do better.
Give me five.
When I come back,
you'll have a whole new perspective.
LOCK BEEPS
PEOPLE SCREAMING
DOOR OPENS
DOOR SHUTS
FOOTSTEPS
SHE GASPS
- HE SIGHS: Kat!
I thought you said
the danger was over.
It is.
Then why are you holding a gun?
You didn't call me back.
I thought you were still
at your mother's.
Why didn't you say something
when you came in the house?
I expected you to be at work!
HE SIGHS
I've been up all night. I'm sorry if-
Doesn't matter, I'm just glad you're home.
- I'm not home.
I'm just here to get a few things.
I know the last couple of days
have been insane.
- You know, I must have left
a dozen messages.
Until I got yours
at four o'clock this morning
I thought for sure you were dead.
That's all over now.
What's over?
Tell me.
- You know I can't talk about my work.
You've never said
my life was in danger!
Because of my work,
I was targeted by a... a group.
And I was afraid, by association,
you might be in danger, too.
It's not the case, they're no longer
a threat. That's all I can say.
How do I even know that's true?
You're obviously capable of lying to me.
Please stay and talk.
I'll make breakfast.
No, I'm not gonna do that.
Kat! Hey.
What? Are you
planning on supervising?
What do you want from me?
I don't want anything
from you, Grant.
Not a single thing.
BEEPING SOUND
SHE SIGHS
David?
DAVID:
Hey! I made pancakes.
You probably don't remember
what pancakes are
but I happen to know
that you like them a lot.
What's wrong?
- Uh, nothing, just, uh...
You used to sleep naked when we met,
and I thought maybe you...
Nope.
False alarm.
How long you been up?
Oh, since, uh...
All night.
I was thinking of maybe
watching some TV
but then you were
all... wrapped up cosy
on the... on the couch
and I didn't want to wake you,
so, um...
then I, uh...
then I... Hey, you know what?
Let's switch things up
and... and you sit here
cos I'm always sitting on this side.
Oh. Yeah. Yeah.
Thanks.
Good.
Are you OK?
- Hmm?
Sure!
I don't know.
No.
I mean, a strange man died
right across from where
I eat my cereal every morning
and I'm just having a...
hard time dealing.
- MARCY: David, he was
gonna kill you.
- That doesn't help.
I was the one that
he was looking for.
Well, that definitely doesn't-
- David, it's over.
You're safe.
Well, you know that...
does make me
feel a little bit better.
RENE: I thought your parents
were never gonna leave.
They're just worried about me.
Yeah, but the doctor said
it's just temporary, right?
Mm-hmm.
- From the swelling?
Does it hurt?
- No.
You really can't feel anything?
Uh-uh.
Nothing?
No.
What about this?
HE GASPS Whoa.
SHE LAUGHS
- Rene...
The nurse could
walk back in any minute.
You can feel that?
- Rene...
Please... Please.
I'm still in recovery.
I should rest.
I shouldn't get too excited.
OK... babe. You rest.
I'll see you tomorrow...
and the next day...
and the next.
Do I seriously have to listen
to that tomorrow
and the next day and the next?
[CURTAI N SWISHES]
I almost pressed the call button
because I thought I was
gonna throw up my lunch.
She's very young.
GRACE:
You're very old.
I can't argue with that.
You really don't feel anything yet?
I mean, the amount of
medical nanites I gave you
was barely above
the minimum threshold
but I thought you'd have
some sensation by now.
With age comes patience.
How are you feeling?
Like I could walk out of here
but I'll have to fake it
for a while
or they'll think
I'm a medical miracle.
Mm!
Besides, I love
the food in here.
It's amazing! Right?
Carly...
Carly!
What do you want?
How about you answer your phone?
I'm not here to creep,
just to say thanks.
You can thank your Sergeant.
He's the one that made me
give the statement.
Oh, I did.
Listen, I'm just as upset
about Jeffrey Jr. as you.
I'm not even allowed
to see him, Jeff!
No contact.
- Me neither.
You didn't know?
INDISTINCT OFFICE CHATTER
Hey, partner.
Everything all right?
I just went into
the wrong bathroom.
Back to basic training for you.
What's this?
- Missing persons report.
Doesn't missing persons fall
under local law enforcement?
We come in if there's
an interstate component.
Right.
- All six failed to check out
out of the same hotel.
Left all their belongings.
"Serenity Inn and Suites".
So... So I guess
we have to go there.
Yeah.
We're FBI agents.
Badges and everything.
All right, but, uh...
can you drive?
You just need practice.
Who'd like to start?
Hi. My name is Philip...
and I'm an addict.
THE GROUP:
Hi, Philip.
You know,
the hardest part about this
is admitting to yourself
that you're not strong enough.
Uh, that you can't just stop...
even when you know
what it's doing to you.
I was doing really well,
I was...
and then I lost
somebody close to me.
Technically, not, uh,
lost... lost
she's still in my life,
but she's just...
This is impossible to explain.
I feel like she's gone.
At least, a part of her is.
Anyway...
I miss her.
COLIN: Thank you, Philip.
- THE GROUP MURMURS
THE GROUP:
Thanks, Philip.
Who'd like to go next?
FOOTSTEPS APPROACH
Hi.
I'm sorry about your friend.
Thanks.
We need all the support
we can get, right?
I'm Traveler 4514.
The Director assigned me
to help you.
DISTANT SHIP'S HORN BELLOWS
You know, you're right.
A little fresh air is nice.
It's important
not to get fixated.
Was I fixated?
Yeah, I was.
It's normal to be
rattled by trauma.
You just want to make sure
it doesn't tip into something more serious.
Like what?
Here, let's sit.
SHIP'S HORN BLASTS NEARBY
- Jesus.
I think you're experiencing
early symptoms of PTSD.
That's ridiculous.
Soldiers in battle get PTSD.
First responders of horrible disasters-
- Heightened anxiety
inability to sleep
exaggerated startle response.
Exaggerated star-
You just made that one up!
I'm fine!
I mean, technically,
it's too early to diagnose
but early treatment won't hurt
and it should help, so...
Here. Come here.
Give me your hands.
I want you to close your eyes.
I want you to think about
what happened to you
while you focus on
my tapping... OK?
Seriously?
Is this a real thing?
Cos it... it feels
a little bullshitty.
Uh, you know what?
I'm sorry. I, uh...
Could we just keep walking?
Yeah. Good idea.
You know what? I'm gonna head back
to the apartment.
I'll meet you back there.
Where are you going?
To get something that'll help.
OK.
PHILIP:
So your mission is to help me?
Specifically to...
give you this.
Eye drops?
Synthetic compound.
To help with
the heroin addiction.
It's invented 20 years
or so from now.
Naloxone, buprenorphine...
and some other things
that are even harder
to pronounce.
But... it will stop the craving
and curb your withdrawal.
And I'm just getting this now?
Hey, I... I know you were trying hard,
but then you had the setback
when you got captured, they gave you...
- How'd you know about that?
The future.
Maybe the Director figured you'd quit
on your own and you couldn't do it.
SHE CHUCKLES
There. See?
It's perfectly...
SHE GAGS AND GASPS
COUGHS AND CHOKES
SHE LAUGHS
That wasn't funny.
- Yes, it was.
One drop per eye, as needed.
Jenny, by the way.
These are amazing.
- Yep.
Now what do I do?
- Whatever you want.
What are you gonna do?
Did you receive any...
training on the simulator?
You had a simulator?
Wow. OK.
Uh, just loosen up on the wheel
and try to get out of your head.
You know,
sing a song or something.
Doesn't have to be a song.
Just recite something
you know by heart.
Uh, list the protocols.
Uh, Protocol 1. Uh...
mission comes first.
Uh, two, leave
the future in the past.
Better. Just turn up here.
Protocol 3...
don't take a life, don't save a life,
unless otherwise directed.
Good.
- Protocol 4
Uh, don't reproduce.
- Don't reproduce.
TIRES SQUEAL'
I don't know how the hell
you got to work today.
Uh, just like that.
Yeah, well, Protocol 2 isn't gonna
get you out of practicing.
Hold on a sec. Kat?
KATHRYN:
You're right. We should talk.
Great. Uh...
Come by the house tonight.
I'll make... / 'm staying at
Nicole 29 While she 's away.
I'll text you the address.
Sure. Want me to bring anyth-?
-  PHONE BEEPS TO END CALL
JEFF:
Carly, they took away our son.
We need to be on the same side.
CARLY: You charged me
with assault
blocked me from getting a job
told the judge
I was an unfit mother.
You have every right
to be pissed at me
but I did those things
because I was pissed at you.
So how about we stop being
pissed at each other
and see what happens?
When I saw the girl
about to shoot you
I just felt...
I can't imagine what I'd do
if I lost you for good.
Yeah, I guess I never did
thank you for that.
Mm, well, you still haven't.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
So walk us through
what happened.
The seminar was going great.
I had two buyers on the hook.
Maybe three!
And then I...
I left the room near the end,
to go get my manager.
We usually offer a slightly better deal
to really drive it home.
Sure.
Except when I came back,
20 minutes later
they were gone.
Twenty minutes?
It's a sales technique...
just let 'em stew on it
a little bit.
Guess it wasn't
such a great deal.
Can you show us
the security footage?
KEY RATTLES IN LOCK
- Mr Conway?
DOOR LOCK BEEPS
Son of a bitch.
That way.
Hey!
OK, fine.
You know, running
from a federal agent
kinda makes it look like
you did something bad.
No, I... uh...
- Freeze!
I think I got it, Ace.
Put it away.
All I did is look the door
to keep them inside.
I know it goes against
fire code, but-
I don't give a shit
about the fire code, Randy.
There are six people missing.
I don't know what
happened to them.
I came back and they were gone.
I swear.
The security tape?
Oh, ah...
KNOCKING AT THE DOOR
DAVID:
Marce?
Hey. My key isn't working.
DOOR LOCK CLICKS
Hi.
MARCY:
Hey.
I stopped by the hardware store
on the way home and uh...
it turns out
they were having a big...
sale on locks.
SNAPS FINGERS
- Yay, safety.
Why don't you have a seat?
RANDY: Now, we only use this
for training purposes.
MACLAREN: We don't care.
- Right.
RANDY TYPES
Can I have one of these?
Sure, yeah,
but they're a day old.
Press play, please.
You didn't tamper
with this, did you?
No. No, I swear.
- You can stop swearing.
Did you have more plans
for the group?
We were gonna shuttle them
to our sister location
to pick up
their free dinner vouchers.
In the shuttle bus outside?
Yeah. Yeah, why?
Might want to get
your brakes checked.
What is this?
This is an eye-movement therapy kit
to treat PTSD.
Alright.
Follow the light with your eyes.
I want you to think
about what you were doing
moments before the man arrived.
I was washing dishes.
Concentrate on how you felt.
MARCY:
What happened next?
Drying the dishes.
I... I don't see how this is supp-
- This is part
of the desensitisation process.
Here, give me your hands.
Close your eyes.
Alright.
HE SIGHS
LOUD KNOCKING AT DOOR
LOCK CLICKS OPEN
DOOR CRASHES OPEN
He forced his way in.
How did you feel
when that happened?
HE INHALES SHARPLY
DAVID CRIES OUT
He kept hitting me.
[MARCY'S VOICE ECHOES]
David..David... David!
GUNSHOT
No!
DAVID GASPING
- MARCY: David.
I'm right here.
Hey. Look at me. Hey!
You're fine.
I am right here.
MARCY: OK?
- DAVID PANTING
You're fine. You're fine.
Why do you figure that
they put a hole in them?
Let's concentrate on
one mystery at a time, shall we?
Um... new arrivals cause
static on video cameras
so it's pretty obvious
that it's six new Travelers.
With a total disregard
for Protocol 5.
Well maybe they're
working on a mission.
Let's be sure. In the meantime,
we bury any connection to this hotel.
Philip, are you there?
'Yeah, go ahead..
I'm leaving what looks like
the scene of a mass arrival.
Six people in a hotel conference room.
Do you remember anything about
a group of Travelers
arriving today in Bel/ingham?
Uh, how were they
supposed to die?
I 'm just guessing, but something
with a shuttle bus.
Brake failure, maybe?
Nothing like that today, but you know
the timeline's been changing.
Yeah, or maybe they went missing
for a different reason.
What, you mean like
how we went missing?
Let's hope not. I'll keep on it.
Sorry about that.
Oh, must be a relief.
- What?
If you're seeing changes
in the timeline
it'll mean you won't have
to carry the burden
of knowing everyone
who's about to die.
Maybe eventually.
It's amazing how
little has changed
considering everything
we've done.
I know what happened
with Aleksander Andreiko.
Maybe we shouldn't
be talking about that.
JENNY: Hey, I agree
with what you did.
You saved that kid's life.
You know the Director
isn't perfect.
We definitely shouldn't
be talking about that.
Don't forget. We created it.
The Director might not
be able to break rules
but we can.
PHILIP CHUCKLES
What?
I feel like I'm waiting
to be struck by lightning.
Not a black cloud in the sky.
Come on.
Where are we going?
It's a surprise.
MARCY:
Here.
Is that any better?
I have no idea.
I have another,
different treatment.
Can it be later?
Sure.
Although, sometimes,
medicine is the best medicine.
Cannabis is known to help
with symptoms of-
Absolutely, it's known to.
- LIGHTER CLICKS
You need to inhale the smoke.
Oh, I'm familiar
with the process.
HE INHALES DEEPLY
HE EXHALES
You know, it's excellent
for memory loss, too.
KNOCKING
DOOR UNLOCKS
Hey.
Hi.
Come in.
Wow. This is nice.
You've been here before.
We helped her move in.
Right. Right.
All I remember is boxes.
What are you doing?
Opening some wine.
HE RUMMAGES IN DRAWERS
So, how long's Nicole away?
All year. She's on sabbatical.
What's that?
Separation papers.
They have to be filed-
- Wait, wait, wait. You...
You're talking divorce?
- You broke your vows, Grant.
And I told you,
it's the worst mistake I ever made...
Shit.
- No, don't touch it.
I'm sorry.
HE GASPS
You're bleeding.
Yeah.
I'll get it.
- Do you have any-?
Yeah, yeah.
In the bathroom.
Everything alright?
I gotta go.
No, not before
you sign these, Grant, I...
Thank you.
Are you OK?
- DOOR SLAMS
SHE SIGHS DEEPLY
Trevor?
Are you asleep?
Uh... I was.
I was dreaming.
- About what?
I was walking in the park.
I don't dream much.
I can tell.
Sorry. I shouldn't
have woken you.
I'm just used to being able to have
intelligent conversations 24/7.
I thought you weren't
much of a people person.
Who said that?
Ellis.
Oh.
He was right, actually
but I was talking
about the Director.
Lamenting those conversations
are over now.
I talked to the Director
a few times.
I talked to it endlessly.
I don't know
what to do with myself.
Protocol 5.
You can counsel children.
Please, I said
intelligent conversation.
So you miss the Director?
SHE CHUCKLES
Huh. I think I do.
Interesting.
You miss her, don't you?
I can tell by the way
you look at me.
What you see is my realisation
that, instead of
saving Grace's life
I made her last few
hours terrifying.
I guess I've cheated
death for so long
I thought that I could do the same
for somebody else.
But I've lived long
enough to know better.
Well, try to understand that
faction had already
corrupted the Director.
The grand plan was in jeopardy.
- I understand.
MAN'S VOICE ON PA:
Ladies and gentlemen...
please give a warm welcome
to our speaker for this evening
'Dr Edwin Calloway..
CROWD APPLAUDS AND CHEERS
You can't be serious.
Edwin Galloway?
Do you know how much hatred
and intolerance this guy inspired?
Immigration...
is the true test of a nation
because the nation needs to be
strong enough to survive it.
Too much accommodation...
This guy is a racist click.
I am not watching this.
Shh. Just wait.
- EDWIN: How many people here
today feel like this country is headed
in the right direction?
And how many feel like
their cultures and traditions
are being respected
by the people they suddenly find
taking their jobs
dating their daughters?
Well, there's a reason
you all feel this way...
Their cultures
don't respect your culture.
CROWD MURMURS
That's a mistake.
AUDIENCE GASPS
EDWIN:
All right. Shut it off.
SHOUTING: Shut it off!
EDWIN SHOUTING:
Shut it off!
CROWD JEERS
JENNY LAUGHS
You did that?
- Still not struck by lightning.
Here.
No, thanks. I feel fine.
Yeah, but do you want
to feel amazing?
JENNY CHUCKLES
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Protocol 4, right?
HE INHALES DEEPLY
HE EXHALES SLOWLY
What was I saying?
Uh... that you should
sell the apartment?
Right.
Although, I think you got
to say if someone died
you know, on the disclosure form.
- Just...
SHE SIGHS Re-stain the floors
and nobody needs to know.
See?
That's why you're an FBI doctor.
Who am I kidding?
I can't sell this place.
All my stuff's here.
Oh, man. I'm really
feeling this.
I don't feel anything, though.
RAPID TYPING
- INDISTINCT OFFICE CHATTER
FORBES:
Hey, Mac?
Whatever it is, try figuring it out
on your own.
I just did.
Come on, check this out.
Two of our missing people were
just flagged in Sacramento.
Local PD got 'em
for running a red light.
Dale Miller and Meredith Gilroy.
Looks like they don't
know how to drive either.
I suggested that these two
were just having an affair.
What about the others?
Technically? No longer under
our jurisdiction.
Local PD took it back.
There's hope for you yet.
Hey.
- Hey.
What is this?
I got a present for you.
Wow.
Looks great. It, uh...
it even covers up the-—
- Yeah, that's kind of the idea.
Yeah, I got you a present, too.
Yay, safety.
I'm not gonna be needing those.
I'm not staying.
What?
You can continue
the therapy on your own
as you feel you need it.
But I can already tell
that you're getting better.
When did you decide this?
I was told my living here
was always temporary.
You can't just buy me
a goodbye rug and then-
David... you went through
a traumatic experience.
Yeah, I'm feeling
another one coming on.
OK, well, just keep up
with the treatments-
Don't talk to me
like I'm a patient.
I'm responsible
for what happened.
You said we were safe.
- You are, but...
you'll be safer without me.
- How is that even possible?
You're the one who saved me.
- And look at the result.
I mean, your anxiety
may never completely go away.
I did that to you.
HE SIGHS
You asked before
if we were intimate, and...
I didn't know what to say
because, I mean...
Well, I don't know,
because I'm an idiot.
What I should have said
was, yes.
We were intimate.
I love you, Marcy.
And you love me.
You just don't remember.
You're right.
I don't.
But I do care about you.
KISSING SOUND
Enough to leave.
JACQUELINE: I understand
this is a difficult time
for both of you.
But the 72-hour
dependency action was filed
and Jeffrey Jr. will be
in the care of the state
until the next assessment.
That's why we're here.
We need to see him.
Not until the next hearing.
I'm sorry.
Trust that he's in a good home.
- I'm his father!
I have a right to see my son.
The action was filed
for Jeffrey's safety.
CARLY:
By who?
It was you, wasn't it?
When we received information
regarding the police incident-
OK. Hold on.
I was cleared of all charges...
I called you, Mr Conniker
and we spoke at length
but I understand why you may
forget the conversation.
We also tried unsuccessfully
to contact you, Ms Shannon.
So what do we do?
Based on your current behaviour
and your history...
I think it might be time to consider
allowing another guardian
to take care of Jeffrey.
Indefinitely.
I'm not gonna give my son
over to some stranger.
Unless things radically change
that is going to remain
Jeffrey Jr.'s best option.
MARCY: Philip?
- PHILIP: Yeah! Just one minute!
DOOR CLOSES
Who are you?
This is Jenny.
- Hi.
Hello.
Philip, can I talk
to you for a second?
Did you bring a 21st-er to Ops?
Well, actually,
she's a Traveler.
And that's better how?
So I'm gonna go.
- Good idea.
Talk to you later?
What's going on?
- I'm clean, Marcy.
That's how we met.
The Director sent her to help me.
POCKET UNZIPS
A synthesised drug
to help me get off heroin.
I need to know
what this is made of.
Naloxone, buprenorphine...
and some other things.
What other things?
- I don't care. It works!
My body doesn't hurt when I'm not high.
I get to have a normal life.
There's nothing normal about this!
- Why?
Because I met someone?
You have somebody.
Not anymore.
I'm gonna stay here for a while
until I find my own place.
Of course.
This place is yours, too.
You OK?
I'm fine.
DOCTOR:
Mr Holden.
TREVOR: Mr Doc.
What's the prognosis?
DOCTOR:
Still a lot of inflammation.
Do you feel anything yet?
Even pins and needles?
I think so.
It's hard to say.
Well... let's, uh,
do the test again.
Ow!
Oh, I felt that.
And movement.
That is excellent.
Excellent!
So does this mean...?
- It means there's hope!
Wow.
Thank you so much.
Would you like me
to contact your folks?
I... I would like that
very much, yes
because they'll want
to thank you, too.
I'll check in again later
before I go today
but how about one
of these, buddy?
Alright.
- BOTH CHUCKLE
Hope?
There are medical nanites
designed in the future
swimming through
your spinal fluid
that I programmed personally,
repairing the damage.
There was never any doubt.
Well, I wanted him to feel good
about the job that they did.
Well, I want them
to bring breakfast.
They're half an hour late
already, and I'm starving.
Thank you for saving me, Grace.
You already said that.
[CALL BUTTON CLICKING REPEATEDLY]
Hi.
- Come on in.
Carly, what're you doing?
What do you think?
JEFF: You're not gonna find anything.
I told you, I stopped drinking.
This is for real.
No, Jeff.
This is for show.
And you better not
screw it up...
because this is our one chance
to get Jeffrey back.
JEFF:
Don't worry. It's gonna work.
The big question is,
where do I put my, uh... my stuff?
By the couch.
Hey, um, you hungry?
I was thinking-
KNOCKING ON DOOR
LOCK BUZZES OPEN
She's not here, is she?
The bitchy little blonde?
Marcy is out
looking for an apartment.
That's why I texted.
You seen this?
His followers went nuts on him
and then, this morning
he woke up,
shot his wife and his kid
before he killed himself.
Philip, I know-—
- His wife and child
are dead and it's our fault.
You mean my fault.
I mean this is fucked up, Jenny!
No. It really isn't.
- None of this would've happened
if you hadn't hacked
his presentation.
He probably would've
gone on spewing hate
that led to the deaths
of hundreds of people.
Thousands!
You tell me,
you're the historian.
It's not up to us.
I didn't tell him
to kill his family.
All I did was tell the truth.
And his wife and child?
The world is a better place
without Edwin Calloway.
And I'm sorry
maybe he took some innocent people
down with him
but I refuse
to feel guilty about it.
Yeah, well,
the Director's gonna know.
If the Director thought
what we were doing was wrong
why didn't I get a messenger?
Orders from another
team to back off?
Can you look me in the eye and tell me
what I did was not a good thing?
Kat.
Grant, what are you doing here?
You can't just show up here, when-—
- Kat...
I know.
- What?
That you're pregnant.
What? Did you show your badge
to my obstetrician?
No.
Can I come in?
I saw your supplements
in the bathroom.
You went through my things?
- Yes, I did
and you can give me
shit for that after we talk.
No, I am not doing that.
- Yes, you are.
Kat!
It happened the night
of your surprise party
the one time we made love
in the past four months.
I just found out.
I haven't even decided
to go through with it yet.
It was hard enough before,
when I knew how you felt about me.
You do know how I feel about-
- And if I decide not to
I won't have you standing there
judging me.
This is something we wanted
more than anything.
It's my decision to make,
and I'm gonna do it on my own.
You should go.
DOOR SLAMS
MEREDITH:
So, the Tuscan villa, the Whistler chalet
and the Caribbean hideaway...
Three stunning properties
all for the price of two
or three normal vacations.
Alright. I can tell you need
a little more motivation.
I'll go see if my manager can knock
a few dollars off the purchase price.
I'll be right back.
LOCK CLICKS
PEOPLE SCREAM