BREE:
He thinks you don't like him.
ANNA: You know what,
who cares if I don't?
Well, he does.
He should get over it.
Anna, I don't think you get it.
Don't think I get what?
Bree?
Anna Hamilton?
I'm Agent Hall with the FBI.
For your safety,
I need you to come with me.
What happened to my friends?
- HALL: Your friends are gonna be fine
but you won't be,
unless you get in the car right now.
Tell me why.
SHE SCREAMS
No! No! No!
BREE: Anna? Anna!
Anna!
MARCY: What... will.. you... be?
What w-will you b-become?
That's so good!
You wanna try the next part?
No.
Come on, girl.
You can do it.
Tomorrow.
It can't always be "tomorrow".
I'm here now, so let's try it.
Marcy! Mercy me.
Time to rock and roll.
This is her reading time.
The man wants to see her now,
which makes it treatment time.
Let's go.
I told her
she didn't have to go today.
Well, you shouldn't
have said that, bud.
I don't...
I don't want t-treatment!
No! No!
Hey. She's a person.
Treat her with respect.
You do your fucking job,
or you won't have one.
I don't want to go...
I don't wanna go!
I'll be here for you
when it's over.
MARCY: No!
James! James!
I don't want treatment!
I don't want it.
Hey. Hey.
Behave
or there'll be
no ice cream after.
I don't want it.
VINCENT: Dear, sweet Marcy.
Don't be afraid, dear.
I have no desire to hurt you
and I mean that sincerely.
No, quite the opposite.
I only want
to make you whole again.
What'd the messenger say?
Another Traveler team
needs tactical support
in less than an hour
at these coordinates.
PHILIP: Got it.
Where's the boss?
Mac, where are you?
TREVOR: Must be off-com.
We can stop by
Kathryn's place on the way.
Where's Marcy?
She just texted me.
She's having some kind
of medical procedure.
We're just gonna have to do
the mission without her.
OK, so nobody get shot today.
TREVOR: That's a good rule in general.
Hello?
I'm so sorry to bother you
at home, Kathryn.
What?
How do you know my name?
He's one of my C.I.'s
who knows better
than to come here.
It's an urgent C.I. thing.
MACLAREN: Alright.
Are you the one
who stole my husband's car?
Well, actually,
that's a funny story.
For another time.
Be back soon.
Look, um...
I need this job.
Just, uh...
Don't let it melt.
Marcy?
Did it work this time?
I told him information transfer
was way, way too slow.
I tried to fix it.
To get you back in...
You're still in there.
You don't know
because you're not here.
He knows.
I'll keep trying
but squid transistors
barely even exist here and now.
You gonna eat that?
Can I have it?
OK.
Well, if they're after me,
then...
how do you know
my parents are safe?
Well, because
they're also under protection.
Right? And that's
question number six.
Oh, fuck me.
What the fuck
are you doing here?
I'm not exactly
thrilled about it either.
We got a messenger.
Tactical support at these coordinates.
Tactical?
I don't know.
I, uh, I think we're good.
The Director doesn't seem to think so.
Where are all the customers?
You ever eat here?
I like it.
Who's she?
That's, uh, 53.
As in "P.O.T.U.S."
Centuries before my time,
but I'm pretty sure
the 53rd President
was another old white guy.
Do you even remember
the other candidate that year?
How close that election was
and how the country
was torn apart after?
Anna, say hello
to Special Agent MacLaren.
It's an honor to meet you,
Ms Hamilton.
Hi.
So, are you assigned
to protect me, too?
Actually...
- Yeah, he is. Until 1600 hours.
Why do I need protection?
- Hey, we had an agreement, right?
Ten questions?
You're already at eight.
Yeah, whatever.
MACLAREN: What happens at 1600?
HALL: How the hell
should I know?
All I gotta do is make sure that,
until then, she's...
Hey, hey! Hey, hey!
Get her to cover now. Now!
FBI! Get down and stay down!
We just lost a camera.
Tracking four targets..
You call this "tactical"?
Carly! Trevor?
- Ready, boss!
In position.
Trevor, your 9:00, moving toward
the west side of the restaurant.
The Director got the last one.
We can't count on the Director
to have eyes everywhere.
We should move.
Stand by.
We're moving somewhere safe.
You know, we were fine
until you showed up.
They must've followed you.
If we hadn't been
ordered here, you'd be dead
and so would 53
who I am taking
to a safe-house right now
with or without you.
MacLaren's right.
We should go.
Yeah, yeah.
MONITOR BEEPS
DRAKE: Come on, girl. Eat up.
I don't have time for this shit.
You know what happens
if you don't.
MARCY: I w-want to go home.
This is your home now.
No, I w-work here.
Get that outta your head.
I remember.
Alright.
Doesn't have to be the hard way.
Don't make me do this.
Hey!
You do it again
and I'll report you!
You'll report me?
I'm not the one who looks at her ass
every time she walks away.
I don't do that.
Don't get me wrong, it's a...
Treat her with respect,
or I'll talk to Dr Carroll.
Carroll?
Ha! That's perfect.
Boom!
Yeah, you go ahead and do that
while I feed
your hot little girlfriend.
DRAKE: You are done.
Don't even bother signing out.
I don't wanna see your face.
I need to use the bathroom.
It's not far now.
You just have to hold it
a little longer...
Madame President.
So in this timeline,
she actually wins the election.
Why would the faction
not want that?
'Cause they're working off
old information.
Where are we going?
That's an excellent question, Anna.
You, uh, you got one left.
MACLAREN: It's an old farmhouse that
I know of. We should be safe there.
That's what Special Agent Hall
said about the restaurant.
"Agent"?
"Special".
Why isn't Marcy with you?
Some sort of
minor medical procedure
I wish she'd told me about.
Is she alright?
I'm sure she's fine.
Simon...
that's beautiful.
SIMON: Thank you.
I like it.
Who is she?
0092.
No, I mean, what's her name?
She's not born
for another two...
no, hundreds of years from now.
Oh! That's
a very long time.
Yes, it is.
Home, sweet home...
The ozone layer is gone by then.
That's just one problem.
In a hundred years,
there are way worse...
we live under the ice.
Oh...
The math's not that complicated
You have two people
that want the same thing...
the two people fight over the one,
and then there's none.
Well...
I have
two pills...
For one person.
OK? There you go.
I'm not supposed to take
anything before treatment.
Marcy, isn't it?
Uh, yeah.
Good, I was hoping to catch you.
Simon is correct
that I prefer he not be medicated
during the treatment.
Oh, well, there's
a daily schedule, Mr Ingram.
SIMON: Maintenance of the yeast vats,
first and foremost
is your responsibility
to the community.
Please, Simon...
allow me to speak
with the orderly.
You go on ahead.
An hour is all I ask.
Dr Carroll approves.
You can check with her.
Dr Carroll's gone home,
and I-I can't...
Perhaps if you understood more
about the therapy I was working on.
You're curious.
Of course, you're curious...
More concerned.
A few of the patients who've
gone through your treatment...
haven't...
returned to the ward?
Because they've been transferred
to another hospital
as promising candidates
for further research.
I can show you the paperwork.
The work we're doing here is truly
for the greater good, Marcy.
We're making progress,
I promise.
In fact...
if you're open to it,
I could use your help.
It's a nice spot.
Glad you approve.
A sign on the road
says it's for sale.
Might be a good investment.
FBI seized the house
from a meth cook
who burned himself to death
in the kitchen, so...
So, big kitchen?
I need you to set
these claymores up
there and there.
We can do that.
Conceal 'em best you can,
then run the wires back to the house.
What, you take orders
from your tactician?
So should you.
Hey, look, I can still tell
you got a problem with me
but you gotta get
over that, alright?
The Director keeps
putting us together.
Must be some good reason.
"Ours is not to reason why."
It's like we're two disciples
but we don't see eye to eye.
I'm not in the mood
for mythology.
But we're both disciples, right
so what're you gonna do?
Hey, look, what
I'm trying to say...
Don't you fucking touch me, Hall!
Take it easy.
Relax.
Let's just get to 1600.
DRONE WHIRS
GUNSHOTS
VINCENT: The technology scans the brain
and records specific patterns
not dissimilar
to something like an MRI.
What exactly am I signing?
Legalese.
The fee for allowing me
to perform the scans
is on the last page.
That's a lot of money.
Is it?
I'm embarrassed to say
that I've lost perspective.
Simon...
what are you doing here?
I helped build the first one
in the future, too.
Good for you.
He likes to "assist."
I consider it
part of his therapy.
Um, Mr Ingram...
uh, I've changed my mind.
You've signed the papers,
you can't.
I just did.
Marcy, it's a harmless scan.
You won't feel it.
Sorry, I don't...
I don't feel comfortable.
Please, be reasonable.
I'm sorry.
You can keep your money.
It's not about
the money, my dear
but now you've seen the device.
This is awkward.
Drake!
Move!
- Uh-uh-uh-uh-uh!
MARCY: Let go of me!
MARCY SCREAMS
You really should read
everything you sign.
MARCY: No!
I'm always in awe
of the potential of youth.
Of what may come.
Even if we didn't know
who she was.
If we succeed in our mission
she'll become one of the great leaders
of a generation.
Mm-hmm.
So I'd very much like
to make it to 4 o'clock.
TREVOR: I wonder if it's a coincidence
that the Director assigned you
a mission to preserve
the life of a child
after what happened
to you and Kathryn.
I think the Director
isn't a licensed therapist
and neither are you.
I do understand
what you're going through.
You couldn't possibly.
Yeah, I do.
Even you forget.
I've lived long enough to see
two of my own sons die of old age.
Uh, no. This isn't
the same thing.
You're right, it isn't.
You're grieving a life lost
that hadn't even begun yet.
A loss of potential.
Anna has that.
All I'm saying.
We got vehicles.
MACLAREN: Yeah. I see 'em. Anna!
Get inside.
The Director will, too,
as soon as they get closer.
Smile for the camera,
Mr Faction.
ROBOTIC VOICE:
Protocol Three is suspended.
Protect Anna Hamilton at all costs
and hold until reinforcements arrive.
NORMAL VOICE:
What just happened?
Nothing happened.
Just go inside.
You're fine.
Here I thought we were gonna make it
to 1600 without any trouble.
DRAKE: She doesn't even recognize me.
There was a malfunction.
Some information
was lost during the scan.
Simon is working
to restore it soon.
Simon?
Until then, Marcy is now to be
considered a patient of this facility
under the care of Dr Carroll.
Dr Carroll agreed to that?
And so will you.
I can make you very wealthy,
very easily.
We can move patients
to different wings
but there'll still be staff
who know Marcy as an employee.
Bribe those you can
and get rid of the rest.
I leave it to you.
CARLY: The Director should turn
every one of them into hosts
or kill them by messenger
as soon as they're on camera.
Maybe Anna should hide
upstairs and wait...
Don't. If they
don't find her
they'll burn this
place to the ground.
It's what I'd do.
Really?
And you...
keep your head down.
Why do they want to hurt me?
Because they're afraid of you.
More than you?
Even more than me, yes.
Why don't we just talk to them?
Wow.
Even now...
Anna, this won't happen
but if they manage
to get through this door
and they try to take you
fight them
and you keep fighting
because help is on the way. OK?
OK.
PHILIP: No, I can do this.
MARCY: We have a mission today.
You're no good to anyone like this.
Oh god, that's better.
Just enough for you to function. Here.
Back to human. Thanks.
Well, that's what I'm here for.
But when I'm gone...
Don't say that.
It's going to happen,
and probably soon.
The seizures are just getting worse
and I can't stop them.
MONITOR BEEPS RAPIDLY
HALL: Seriously?
That's all we got.
No, this'll help.
Didn't think the Director
would let them get this close.
We can't wait for the Director.
Aim centre mass.
Shoot when I shoot.
Oh! Crash!
Sorry. I didn't see that...
that move comin'.
Are you OK?
I... I'm fine.
I'm fine.
Uh... I was... I was watching you
there a little bit
and I was thinking
you looked lost.
Maybe I can help.
Is there some family that I can...?
- Mm. Mm.
Turns out we're going
the same way anyway.
Um, what's your name?
Uh, M... Marcy.
Marcy?
Yeah.
- Seriously?
That is easily in my top ten
favourite names in the whole world.
You're the first one
I've met in person.
My name's David.
MONITOR BEEPS RAPIDLY
Four of them are coming around
the south side of the house.
Hall, that's you!
I know! I know!
It's like the fucking Alamo!
Where's the Director?
They've gotta have an S.T.A.!
What?
"Space-Time Attenuation" device.
It creates a field around 'em in which
the Director can't see 'em.
I see the S.T.A.!
It's in the green truck under the tarp!
Trevor...
we need an end-run.
Go.
TREVOR: Son of a bitch!
HALL: Cover him!
Cover him!
Like I said, it isn't much...
But it's not the street
and it's subsidised.
Do... Do you live... here?
No.
This is your place now, remember?
See, there's a...
there's a bed in here with...
clean sheets, like I promised
and...
good, there's a towel, too.
And a dresser
for all your things.
So first thing tomorrow,
we'll... we'll go...
get you some things.
And here,
there's a little fridge
to keep your milk
for your cereal or your tea.
Do you like tea?
Oh, looks like the previous tenant
left a big chunk of chocolate!
No, that's hash.
Take that away.
And...
Good!
That works, too.
You have a light
to read your book by.
MARCY GIGGLES
So, I will let you
get settled in.
N-No... d-don't go.
Oh, I have to go.
I have other clients.
I-I did look up the hospital
you said you were a patient at.
I w-work there.
You work there?
- Mm-hmm.
Huh.
Well, that's different.
Either way, they said
they have no record of you.
Oh!
MARCY: Don't go!
OK.
I still have to go.
But I will be back
tomorrow morning
to take you shopping.
Oh, don't do that.
Oh, uh...
OK?
- OK.
Don't forget to lock up.
OK.
MARCY: David?
DAVID: Surprise!
Hey.
I know I said the paperwork
was gonna take seven days, but...
It only took a week.
Oh, you put some pictures up.
Nice.
Uh, so this is the paperwork
we need to sign
in order to get you
something to live on.
I've already filled out
most of it
we're just missing some things.
Um...
Do you happen
to remember your birthday?
Well, that's not a problem.
We'll... We'll...
We'll pick a day.
Oh...
Oh, wait! It's today.
What are the odds?
Well, one in 365
but so long as
we're saying today...
It's for... for my birth... birthday?
DAVID: Yeah.
Everybody deserves
a birthday present.
It's not brand-new
but, uh, it'll hold your stuff
when you go outside.
My mum always says
that it's bad luck
to give a bag as a gift
without putting money in it...
which, I guess, is why I asked
for a new bag every Christmas.
The only thing we need
to figure out now is your age.
I'm guessing
somewhere between 22 and 26.
You pick.
42.
56?
Seven?
No!
Well, you told me to pick.
OK. We'll go...
We'll go with 25.
Carly?
I see it.
Hit the claymores!
Wait for my order.
Philip, there's two more round the back!
PHILIP:
Understood.
It stopped short of the mines.
Carly!
FACTION MEMBERS SCREAM
MARCY:
“You're...
"a...
"big...
"girl now, '
"said...
M-Mary's teacher."
I couldn't have read it
better myself.
Have you been practicing?
Mm-hmm.
Well, that deserves a...
I better check to see what I have on me
before I start making promises.
Oh, no, no, that's for you to buy
things you need.
OK, we'll call it a loan.
Come on.
Marcy, what are you doing?
You're m-my...
you're my boyfriend.
I-I can't be your boyfriend.
I can be your friend.
It's not because I don't like you
or that you're not
one of my favourite people
in the whole world.
It's because it would...
it would be inappropriate.
Yeah, I know that's a...
that's a big word.
Listen.
Boyfriends come and go...
but if you want
you can be my B.F.F.
That means
"Best Friend Forever".
And I don't just
call anybody that.
MONITOR BEEPS RAPIDLY
MONITOR FLATLINES
4:00.
Where does the time go?
Is it over, Agent Hall?
Yeah, I think so, Anna.
You agree, Agent MacLaren?
Sure.
Gotta go! I'm late!
For what?
Mum? Dad!
Mum. Dad.
All these people were trying...
MUM: We know.
- I was so scared.
MUM: It's alright, Anna.
They told us what happened.
But we're here now
and we're gonna take you
some place safe, OK?
MONITOR FLATLINES
PHONE BUZZES
Hey, it's me,
I'm gonna be home around 5:00
which is when I'm usually home
but you asked
when I was gonna be home
so I am just confirming.
MUM: Did any of your people get hurt?
Everybody made it.
Why did you do this for me?
Ooh, no. That's... That's too bad,
that's question number eleven.
The future's gonna need
people like you.
Thank you.
And thank you.
Bye, everyone.
I assume her parents historically died
trying to protect her.
3:43 this afternoon.
We'll make sure she never knows.
Well, you'd better
take good care of her
or you're gonna be
answering to both of us.
We trained for years
to do just that.
Good.
Agent MacLaren.
Agent Hall.
Bugs the shit out of you, doesn't it?
Yep.
MONITOR FLATLINES
DAVID: I got your favourite.
MARCY: "Police were forced
to use tear gas"
to disperse a crowd shortly after
a not-guilty verdict
"was announced outside of the..."
What?
I don't want to say anything until
we talk to a doctor, but...
I think a miracle just happened.
Marcy?
Marcy!
DAVID:
You know what I think?
If I die in my sleep tonight
I'm good to go.
CARLY: One... two...
three... four...
One... two... three...
Where's her medical kit?
What happened?
What did she do?
I just got here myself!
Just get the bag and bring it over here.
Are you shot?
Get the bag!
Can you charge the defibrillator?
- What?
It's OK.
Just take over.
Get the bag and take over.
Go, go, go, go, go!
One, two, three, four, five...
Mm. I can't believe
how much you suck at this.
MARCY: This is nothing
like actual surgery.
DAVID: No, well, "wrenched elbow",
that's the easiest one.
MARCY: That's not even a thing.
- DAVID: No, it is.
DAVID: You know, I think I might be
a better doctor than you.
Oh, she's coming back.
Oh, thank God.
Alright. Help me.
Help me get her into the bed.
We've gotta get her body temperature up.
DAVID: I thought something
terrible had happened to you.
You must be David.
I'm told we're close.
"Close"?
Marcy, we're very...
close.
What's wrong?
KETTLE WHISTLES
No...
I'll yell at you later.
You find the missing pieces
you were looking for?
David...
you weren't supposed
to find that unless...
Unless you'd died.
Yeah, I figured that one out.
How could you do this?
Knowing that I was probably
gonna be the one to find you?
Right now she needs to rest.
Yeah.
Whatever.
Hey.
Sorry I was gone so long.
It's OK.
I was just dozing.
Everything OK?
Yeah. Everything's fine.
I saved a kid today.
David?
INDISTINCT CONVERSATION
DAVID: Oh. OK. Well,
I'll talk to you later.
Hey.
Hi.
I wanted to talk to you
before you left for work.
Yeah, no, I, uh...
thought maybe you'd want
to thaw some more.
Can we talk?
Sure.
If you wouldn't have found the note,
you would have never known.
Doesn't make it better.
It was the only way, David.
To do what?
To find the missing
pieces of myself.
To find you.
OK, so?
Was it worth
almost killing yourself?
Because honestly, this is...
Well, that was different.
I'm sorry that I scared you.
You have no idea.
If I hadn't...
What?
What is it?
Do you know who did this?
Uh, yeah...
some homeless guy,
lives around here.
Why?
I need you to take me to him.