Seven months ago
my consciousness was sent
from the distant future
into the body of Special
Agent Grant MacLaren
moments before he would, historically,
have died in the line of duty.
Since then, I have assumed his life,
his work...
his marriage...
pretending to be a man
very different than myself.
In truth, I am Traveler 3468.
One of thousands of Travelers
around the world
who have come from a time
when life is all but wiped out...
To save humanity, to change the path.
I know how that must sound,
especially to you, Kat...
but it's true.
PHONE VIBRATES
Good afternoon, Agent MacLaren.
Where is she?
- Perrow? She's safe.
Though her neck might be a little tender
after having to remove the com
she allowed you to plant.
Let her go, Ingram.
- Of course.
Soon as we put this to an end.
I'd like to propose a truce.
You kidnapped and tortured my team,
killed Travelers all over the world.
I needed to know if the Director was still
after me, and that suspicion was confirmed.
My mission was to die
immediately after my arrival.
By surviving, I committed a crime
against the Grand Plan
and was condemned to death.
Is that fair?
Not up to me.
- No.
No, it's up to the Director, who has
no understanding, no forgiveness, no soul.
Because it is a machine.
I am tired of running.
Take a selfie, you can end it right now.
- For me, the digital age
has created a prison around me,
one that's been...
shrinking over time.
It's no way for my son to grow up.
Are you trying to get sympathy from me?
No. No, I want your word
that you'll leave me alone
while I prepare my affairs
and face my accuser.
That's not going to go well for you.
- I have no illusions.
I know exactly what's going to happen.
I stole 16 years that I wouldn't otherwise
have had
and in that time,
I created a precious life.
My son shouldn't have to pay
for the mistakes of his father.
Do I have your word?
You don't have my anything.
That's not actually true.
Grant, please help me!
- You son of a...
MACLAREN GRUNTS
If you fucking hurt her...
- 3468.
If you want to see your wife again,
follow this simple instruction...
Stay out of my way.
He showed me a video.
She's being held somewhere.
MARCY: Is she hurt?
-  I don't know, I couldn't tell.
Boss, he's faked things like this before.
Are you sure it was Kathryn?
Yes, and her phone
goes straight to voicemail.
What does he want?
- A truce.
Fuck that.
He said he's going to show himself
to the Director and face punishment
But he wants us all to stand down
so he can make arrangements for his son.
Kat's his insurance.
He spent all this time hiding and torturing
Travelers, only to turn himself in?
I don't buy it either.
- Right now I just want Kat to be safe.
Philip, can you trace her phone 's GPS?
-  I can try.
I don 't think he can monitor our coms,
but let's be careful.
If he finds out we're looking for her...
- What about Perrow?
He claims she 's still alive, but you
should all check on your loved ones
and make sure they're OK.
'I'm going to Kat's place..
PHONE BEEPS
David's not answering.
Neither is Jeff.
- Gary, hey!
I'm just checkin' in. How is everything?
OK, let's go.
Mum's good, too?
No, I won't be home for dinner and
I gotta run, but you guys have a good day.
DOOR SLAMS
SHE EXHALES
Please!
SHE GASPS
I'm sorry for having treated you this way,
but we needed to remove the device
as quickly as possible.
Where's my daughter?
- Home.
I don't believe you.
Someone's supervising her as we speak.
PHONE RINGS
Hello?
-  Ava!
Sweetie, are you hurt?
- No.
There's a man here..
Are you coming home?
-  Soon, very soon.
Where are you? You said you were...
I promise you,
Ava is going to see her mother shortly.
SHE EXHALES
There's just one more
thing I need you to do.
David?
COM BEEPS
Guys, David's gone.
'CARLY: So are Jeff and the baby“.
'Marcy, the place is destroyed..
What do we do?
HE SIGHS
TV REMOTE CLICKS
Never thought my day would start this way.
You really want to mount an inter-agency
investigation into Vincent Ingram?
You're wasting time.
- Mac, think this through.
He has them captive.
- And he warned you things could get worse.
The man said he was going
to give himself up to the Director.
Let's just wait this out...
- And you believe him?
Why would he go to the trouble of...
- He's psychotic!
He's spent years hunting Traveler teams,
mine included.
They'd be dead
if I hadn't used NSA resources...
Which is one of the reasons
why they're onto us.
What are you talking about?
A few weeks ago, I saw a report.
DOD, Homeland Security, CIA, the NSA...
It wasn't just my host task force
that was suspicious.
We've been discovered
across all the intelligence services.
Probably worldwide.
Jesus.
They think we're some new terrorist
organisation.
Cells in over 100 countries.
They haven't acted
because they're scared as shit.
Our people at the NSA and Homeland Security
are concealing us as best they can
but at this point, it's only a matter
of time before there are leaks.
Going after Ingram
would raise a red flag we can't afford.
PHILIP: Boss, I managed to unlock
multiple locations from their phones.
The last one recorded was 3:28 PM
yesterday, all from the same place.
Send me the address.
Keep your eye on the back channels.
The rest of you, meet me there.
- Mac!
Hello, Kathryn.
DEVICE BEEPS
DOOR SLAMS
My name is Katrina Perrow.
I'm a psychologist.
Where am I?
- I'm not permitted to tell you that.
Why are we here?
There are questions I'm
supposed to ask you.
But I want you to know
that I am also doing this against my will.
They've taken my daughter, Ava.
Now, if we just work together and do
what they want, they'll let us all go.
Can we do that?
SHE EXHALES
When did you first notice changes
in your husband?
It's all been for the greater good.
The lives lost when Van Huizen exploded
ensured the survival of millions
who would have died
just over a year from now.
Millions of people who have no idea
how close they came to the end.
And they were saved by Travelers.
That's what we do.
Carly Shannon historically died at the
hand of her drunk, abusive boyfriend.
And now, instead of her child
being raised by a dead-beat father
he is surrounded by love.
My love.
Jeffrey Conniker Jr
will grow up to be a good man.
And millions of people around the world
won't suffer from the Helios catastrophe.
So, do you know what I have to say
about coming here...
and taking this body, and doing our work?
You're welcome.
Shit.
That's Grace's phone.
WHITE NOISE BLARES
TREVOR INHALES
Simon...
You said it wouldn't take long.
Yeah, but that's before
the interface overheated.
And yeah, I knew you were there,
you didn't sneak up on me.
There isn't much time.
TOOLS CLATTER
I know. I have a clock in my head.
I need more coolant. Did you bring it?
Everything you need is in this room.
Remember, we're doing this for you.
You said "multiple uses".
Multiple transfers.
Yes, and then we'll take care of you.
David?
David.
Sorry, I'm just...
Never been kidnapped before.
I've been held hostage, but that's a whole...
- Please, just...
Answer the question.
- Uh, yeah.
I am... Was, her social worker.
How do you know about Marcy?
Where is she?
She's safe.
As in... Safely captured, or safe at home?
They didn't take her.
- "They"?
The same people who took my daughter.
HE STAMMERS
I... That's terrible, I'm...
Then they're after me?
What did I do?
- David, please...
Just answer the questions
if you want us both to get out of here.
OK.
- Is it true that one day
Marcy's cognitive abilities changed,
and for all intents and purposes
she was an entirely different person?
Yeah.
Didn't that seem odd to you?
Of course it did. I thought
a miracle had happened, are you kidding me?
How did you justify that change?
HE STAMMERS
I'm pretty sure
I shouldn't be talking about this.
You have doctor-client privilege with me.
You're not my doctor.
- David...
She's a doctor.
- Marcy Warton?
With the FBI, undercover.
She goes on secret missions...
I've said too much.
- And you believed her?
Yeah, I met her boss. Grant MacLaren.
He's real. I've been to his office.
God, he's gonna kill me.
I cracked in like five seconds.
David... Marcy Warton is not an FBI agent.
She's a Traveler... from the future.
A who?
- A time traveler.
That is the stupidest thing I've ever...
- She was supposed to be killed
by a group of men
outside the library where she worked.
Seconds before her death...
a consciousness was sent from
the future, supplanting Marcy's own.
And that new Traveler survived the attack.
And just a few months ago,
that consciousness was replaced yet again.
She called it memory loss,
but in fact, she was...
Overwritten.
Lady...
What the fuck have you been smoking?
HE LAUGHS
Hi.
Sorta glad I'm not alone here.
I'm David.
Kathryn.
Kathryn...
Are they alright?
Still on whatever drug they gave me.
You don't know any of them, do you?
Uh... OK, wow. Yes.
- You do?
Ray?
Ray, wake up!
He got me out of a legal jam recently.
It was weird...
Flay! Flay! Wake up...
- I already tried yelling.
Oh, for God's sakes.
- What?
I know him too.
He's a cop.
He interviewed me once about Marcy.
Who's Marcy?
Apparently a time traveler from the future.
She said my husband was, too.
Dr Perrow?
- Yeah.
But you don't actually believe...?
- Of course not.
Of course not.
Oh, Shit...
It's alright, you're not alone.
Where's my son?
Where's Jeffrey? He's just a baby...
Oh, he's not with us, I'm sorry.
You're MacLaren's wife.
- Agent MacLaren?
You know who I am?
Yeah, I came to your house and told you
that your husband
was screwing around with my girl, Carly.
Carly?
What?
- Yeah, you don't remember?
No, and I think that's something
I would remember.
So then why would he bring us here?
What? Why would Grant do this?
She's right,
I don't think this is an FBI thing.
How do you know
my husband works with the FBI?
He's Marcy's boss, isn't he?
- David Mailer.
You're the social worker creep that was...
screwin' around
with the retarded girl, Marcy.
That's a hateful word.
- OK, wait, who the fuck is Marcy?
His client!
One minute she's mentally disabled,
the next minute
she's whoopin' half a dozen boys
outside the library...
Yeah, she was undercover!
- Alright!
Enough of this shit!
We talk, or we get out of here.
DAVID SCOFFS
JEFF BANGS ON THE DOOR
- Hey!
Whoever the hell you think you are,
you just kidnapped a Metro police officer!
That's a class-A felony, and I'm gonna
put your ass away! You hear me?
HE BANGS THE DOOR
GRACE GROANS
Do you have to be so loud?
Who the hell are you?
Hello. I'm... I'm David.
I'm a friend of Marcy's.
This is Kathryn.
She's married to Agent MacLaren,
who's Marcy's boss.
This is Ray.
He's still unconscious.
The unhappy man is Officer... Conniker
who I'm guessing is in a relationship
with Carly, who's also a friend of Marcy...
All of whom may or may not
be time travelers.
And you are?
I'm a high-school guidance counsellor.
Oh, OK. That makes perfect sense.
DOOR OPENS
Wait, no. Don't you touch me.
No. No. No...
Where are you taking me?
Let me go!
SHE SCREAMS: Let me go!
The lady asked you to let her go-
THUD
KATHRYN: Back off! No!
DOOR SLAMS
KATHRYN: Let me go!
Who's he again?
He's my lawyer.
COMPUTER BEEPS
Vincent's sending us something.
Boss!
KATHRYN SOBS
SHE EXHALES
Grant, in order for me to be released
unharmed, you must confess to...
being a Traveler on video.
You have one hour to send it to this IP,
or they'll kill me,
RAY INHALES
Shit, not again.
Ray?
RAY CHUCKLES
David.
- Yeah.
We've been kidnapped.
I know that sounds crazy, but...
How much do you owe Vargese?
Vargese, anyone?
- We're not sure why we're here.
Does this have anything to do
with the guy in your apartment who, uh...?
HE CLICKS TONGUE
What?
- Oh... Maybe?
DOOR OPENS
RAY CHUCKLES
What's with Mr Big and Tall here?
Hey, wait...
Come on, take it easy, what the f... Jesus!
Boss, I have to say this...
If we do this, it goes against everything
we trained for. I know.
I'm sorry.
I'm not going to let my wife die.
I feel the same way about David.
Look, listen, listen!
I want nothing more than to hold my son
right now, but the mission comes first.
If you sit down at that computer
with the intention of confessing,
you'll be overwritten.
I think I know how we can do this
and still maintain Protocol 1.
I got my hands on an advanced rootkit virus
that I can plant
in the code of the video file.
Is it traceable?
Four months ago, it compromised the Relicus
Maxicloud in Austria for 47 minutes
and they still don't know who did it.
- Do you?
The Faction.
I can track the video
on the back channels and find his location.
What if it spreads?
- I'll know where it goes.
When the time comes, we can shut it down.
Yeah, if the Director lets us get that far.
I'm still not struck by lightning.
Do it.
Ready when you are.
HE EXHALES
Seven months ago...
my consciousness
was sent from the distant future
into the body of Special Agent
Grant MacLaren.
DEVICE BEEPS
DEVICE POWERS UP
Cooling systems at -270 degrees.
Superconductor efficiency, 99.8%.
LOUD SPARKING ERUPTS
STEAM HISSES
Simon!
- It's overheating!
Shut it down! Simon!
WATER SIZZLES
SIMON BLOWS
It was supposed to work!
- Can you fix it?
I told you, the device requires...
- Simon! Can you fix it?
This was all for you. All for you.
I'm his only friend?
Man, that is tragic.
The guy travels through time,
becomes a junkie...
And his only friend is a lawyer
with a gambling addiction who uses him?
I'd like to, uh, keep us on track.
HE MUMBLES: OK...
How are things at home?
Where's my son?
Jeffrey's OK. For now.
What does that mean?
It means if you and I cooperate,
then you'll see your son
and I'll see my daughter, but that entirely
depends on you.
There are some things
about Carly you need to know.
'In truth, I am Traveler 3468...
Oh, Jesus Christ, Mac.
- We've got it under control.
Clearly you don't.
My teammate at the NSA flagged this during
her routine scan for Traveler activity.
If any other agent had found...
- Yeah, well, they didn't.
And we've taken
extra precautions with Philip's virus.
Now, once we get to Vincent,
we can corrupt the video.
I just need time to flush him out.
The intelligence agencies
already have a target on our backs.
Well, then, let's work together
and get ahead of it.
Those with my specialty are chosen
as infants in order to develop their minds
to specifically serve the Traveler
programme.
Some days I felt like an experiment.
Other days like a super-human.
Today, I'm...
The Director has kept watch
over my entire life...
Knowing the outcome of every decision,
crafting my path forward.
But here...
I see people every day
who still believe in free will.
They don't know any better.
JEFF GROANS
RAY HISSES
I've taken down bigger guys than you.
RAY SIGHS
Do any of you think
this could actually be true?
GRACE: What?
A few months ago,
I definitely noticed changes in Grant.
It was truly like he
was a different person.
What they're saying would explain...
- Oh, please.
Like time travel is actually possible?
OK, maybe you could send information
in the form of some coherent energy
across space-time.
But to calculate an exact position
would require an almost impossible level of
accuracy, not to mention
nearly a billion zettaflops
of processing power.
And then to unpack it somehow
without entropy, in a... Biological...
What do you do again?
Guidance counsellor.
PHONE BUZZES
He knows you tampered
with MacLaren's recording.
Now each and every one of you
must record...
your own confessions,
or we will all be killed.
Marcy, / just want to go home.
'I just wanna go home..
Alright, look, look, look, listen.
We know there's only one way in
and one way out, right?
Now, there's two of them, two of us...
Let's take 'em.
Oh, I can't wait to see this.
JEFF: Yeah. Yeah, OK.
Next time, we jump 'em.
You take the tall one.
Which one is the tall one?
DAVID GROANS
Oh, my God.
David... It's OK, I got you.
I can't see out of my right eye. Is it OK?
Uh... It's just swollen shut.
"Just."
- Try that shit with me.
Wait, wait, wait.
Don't.
I get it. I'm next. Let's go.
My purpose is to save lives...
Whether that's a teammate in jeopardy,
or someone that's part of a mission
ordered by the Director.
But I can't help but think
that I've put one person's life
in more danger than they deserve.
David...
You've suffered because of me, and
there's just... There's no excuse for that.
I cared enough to leave once.
I should have just stayed away.
STEAM HISSES
I've lowered the temperature in the room.
I know it's cold.
It's bracing, yes.
Is it ready?
- Almost. It's almost done.
For 2,000 years, mankind believed
that God was created in his image...
Guiding our lives, hearing our prayers...
Could you hand me the screwdriver?
But when those prayers weren't answered,
we just chalked it up to His divine will.
But then mankind
created the power to build God.
A machine more powerful
than any human mind could ever be...
It's just, uh, on the workbench...
- The fate of our existence
just handed to an AI with the ability
to monitor each and every shifting timeline
while we blindly obey its orders
with the belief that salvation will come.
It's the Phillips head...
- The problem isn't the fact
that we believed in God...
"It's that we didn't believe in ourselves."
Fine, I'll get it.
It's time to pull back the curtain
and take control of the present.
To fight for our future.
DEVICE POWERS UP
MACHINE HUMS
It's working.
Simon...
We can finally fix you.
GRACE: A psychologist? And you actually
enjoy talking to people for a living?
When I'm not under duress.
Alright, let's get it over with, then.
When are you from?
- When are you from?
What is your mission?
- What is your mission?
What is your specialty?
- What is your sp-
Alright, enough!
You can stop pretending, Traveler 0027.
Shit.
Hey, have you seen this?
Uh...
BETH SCOFFS
Is this supposed to be funny?
- I didn't do it - it's real.
Jesus Christ.
The videos have been disseminated
to servers in nearly every major city.
Any luck over there?
Locked out of everything.
You said you could control the virus.
Yeah, well, he's pretty good, too.
- What are you saying?
What I'm saying is that
I can't corrupt the video files
that are already out there.
The world is about to find out who we are.
Why isn't the Director stepping in?
We must eventually find
a way to solve this.
If not, it had its chance
to overwrite any one of us
when we recorded our confession.
COMPUTER BEEPS
He's sending us a message.
UDIDs, MAC addresses, possible coordinates.
He's making us work for it.
He's a dead man.
- WAKEFIELD: He '3 a psychotic rec/use!
You're asking me if
time travel is possible.
You say that out loud again, and slowly.
PHONE BEEPS
You've seen it too.
We couldn't get ahead of it.
He sent it to all the major news outlets,
intelligence agencies...
I have to believe that 21st-century
skepticism is alive and well.
Yeah, for the New York Times, sure,
but this isn't going to be something
that goes away with the news cycle.
The information he has fills in the pieces
on dozens of Traveler missions
the CIA could never explain.
It's only a matter of time
before they put it all together...
No, the Director will
never let that happen.
Yeah, well, here we are.
What about your wife?
PHILIP: Boss, I think I know Where they
are. Sending you coordinates.
PHONE BUZZES
This is the same...
What the fuck?
VIDEO PLAYS QUIETLY
If you have any questions about what
you've just seen, feel free to ask Grace.
She's one of them.
DOOR SLAMS
SHE SIGHS
PHONE BUZZES
Ava? Sweetie?
Mum! The man said you're coming home..
I'll be home soon.
I love you.
- I love you too.
I wanted to say goodbye.
I'm scared.
- Don't be.
You did it, Simon.
The device works perfectly.
Will you stay with me?
If that's what you want.
Thank you, Vincent.
Thank you.
TREVOR: I was part of the original test
program for consciousness transfer...
Something we had to master
before we could even dream
of traveling back through time.
And I lived in many bodies
which makes me one of the oldest
living people in human history.
I'll never forget what I saw
the first time I woke up...
My former body with glassy eyes
staring back at me.
There was no one in there anymore.
Just a husk.
FLY BUZZES
That image stays with me everywhere I go.
HE GASPS
HE BREATHES HEAVILY
Traveler 5692. Arrival successful.
Alright, there's two of them, two of us.
It's now or never.
Cancel the plan, cancel the plan!
What are you...? Ow!
THEY GRUNT
Where are you taking us?
Though this news is still breaking,
we can confirm that Vincent Ingram -
owner of one of the world's
leading securities firms -
is responsible for bringing to light
what may be a new terrorist group
with cells positioned throughout
the world...
Let me know when you have confirmation
that the device has been moved.
I need to speak with my son.
Hello, Taylor. Remember me?
Hi.
Did your father explain to you that you're
going to be living with me for a while?
Yeah, but he didn't say why.
So that we can be free.
I'm Dr Katrina Perrow, and Vincent Ingram
has been my patient
for the last four months..
'For the purposes of this recording'
he has asked me
to break doctor-patient confidentiality.
This is not a subject
one can discuss openly, because...
Frankly, it flies in the face
of 21st-century science
and what we currently
perceive to be possible.
'But everything you've heard is true..
Travelers do exist..
What do you see?
Nothin' but God's country.
Only reason to take us out to the middle
of nowhere is to kill us.
Might as well say your prayers.
Do people still pray in the future?
PERROW: They operate covertly
in cells made up of five members...
VINCENT'S VOICE JOINS IN:
.,.each with a specialty.
BOTH: Their missions are sent from an
advanced Al
that continuously keeps watch
over an ever-changing timeline.
'They are spies, terrorists...
and they will not stop
until their Director
has achieved its primary goal:
The Grand Plan..
VINCENT: They are our wives, our husbands,
our sons, and our daughters.
They know our secrets,
they know our future.
They gain our trust, our affection,
but it's all a lie.
'We must do whatever we can to stop them..
HELICOPTER WHIRS
Jesus, Kat, I was so afraid...
Who are you?
David! David!
Don't touch me.
- We can get through this.
I don't think so.
Ray, I am so sorry
that you had to go through that.
I gotta hand it to you, kid,
you were straight with me from the start.
But let's not pretend we're friends.
Please let me hold him.
- Stay the hell away from my son.
You hear me?
SIRENS APPROACH
TREVOR: Grace, are you OK?
I... I don't know.
SIRENS WAIL
I'm telling you, this whole thing...
- No...
No, I can explain who did this.
I don't want to hear anything from you.
You killed my husband.