PHONE KEYBOARD CLICKS
PHONE LOCKS
CAR ENGINE STARTS
I'll meet you outside Ops.
CARLY WHISPERS:
Copy that.
CAR HORN BEEPS
TREVOR:
Oh! That's the boss!
Road trip.
You're such a kid.
Yeah, on the outside.
What's that? Boop!
What a freak, man.
What?
DOOR KNOCKS
Oh...
Wow. They're beautiful.
Thank you.
Mum.
Mum remembered.
"Happy anniversary, Grant."
No service?
Not one bar.
Should've called
when we stopped at that gas station.
MARCY:
Told you.
Yeah, then we got lost.
How long till impact?
Twenty-three minutes, six seconds.
Ish?
No, pretty much exactly.
I'll have to call her after the mission.
I don't understand the big deal about
anniversaries anyway.
My father missed their 25th
a few months back.
And?
Gary paid a heavy price, boss.
Fortunately, Kat's a reasonable person.
MARCY: Reason's got nothin' to do with it.
You're already in the doghouse.
Oh, come on.
- No, she's right.
Your window was early this morning.
It's already closed.
How do you know this information?
- Covered it in training.
"21st-Century Female Behaviour."
Ah. Well, I'll buy her flowers, then.
What anniversary is it?
MACLAREN: Ten years.
- Yikes.
Whoa.
Ah, you're screwing with me now.
No, ten's a big one. Even I know that.
OK, well, help me out.
What's an appropriate gift for ten years?
Tin.
Yeah, ten.
- No, "tin."
As in the metal.
- Tin?
That's the traditional gift.
I'm supposed to give her something
made from tin?
If you're a traditionalist, yes.
There's a more modern anniversary theme
for ten years but you're not gonna like it.
Diamonds.
Now I know you're making this up.
- Technically, diamond jewellery.
Yes.
- Seriously?
MARCY: You might've gotten away
with flowers, if you'd called.
“Gotten away with flowers if you called...”
MACLAREN:
Where does it come down?
PHILIP: 600 metres
to our south-southwest
in seven minutes, eight seconds.
There-ish.
It's amazing this becomes
a dry lakebed in 50 years.
Do we need to worry about a wave?
Nah. Probably a splash,
but it's not too big.
TREVOR: Just extremely rare and important
to the future.
More rare than that other mineral...
What was it?
Diamond?
That's the one.
Alright, alright, just...
Let's get the recovery gear ready,
make sure everything's working.
The Director gave us an important mission.
Let's get it right.
ENGINE SPUTTERS
OUTBOARD ROARS
GUNFIRE
OUTBOARD RATTLES
HIGH-PITCH RINGING
- WOMAN SCREAMS: No!
SHE SCREAMS
No!
RINGING STOPS
PHONE RINGS
VOICEMAIL BEEPS
VOICEMAIL: You've reached Special Agent
Grant MacLaren. Please leave a message.
PHONE RINGS
Wakefield.
WOMAN: This is an emergency communication,
Protocol Alpha.
Protocol Alpha? Who is this?
{This is Traveler 5001..
We have less than 60 seconds
before signal loss.
I'm listening.
- I need armed air assets
to the following coordinates ASAP...
“9.3506 degrees north..
'1228599 degrees west..
'Can you do this?'?
Possibly. I have a helicopter
already in the air with agents aboard
but they're not Travelers.
I said Protocol Alpha!
Can you get them to these coordinates
in the next 17 minutes?
Negative. Best case is, is... 25 to 30.
What about assets on the ground?
WAKEFIELD: 25 minutes
is our closest anything.
You're talking the middle of nowhere.
I do have agents on the ground
within roughly...
SILENCE
Hello?
Give me the keys!
Ha. Right. How 'bout we just wait till
your little brother touches down first?
It's an emergency!
Give me the fucking keys!
They're in the ignition.
DOOR OPENS
- Wait. What emergency?
Carrie, what's wrong?
Just tell me what's going on!
I'll drive you myself!
Carrie!
HE SHOUTS:
Wayne! Your sister just took my car!
PHONE RINGS
VOICEMAIL: You've reached Special Agent
Grant MacLaren.
CARLY:
No service?
Not one bar.
Should've called
when we stopped at that gas station.
I told you.
- MACLAREN: Yeah, then we got lost.
How long till meteor impact?
Twenty-two minutes, 51 seconds.
Ish?
No, pretty much exactly.
I'll call her after the mission.
I don't understand the big deal
about anniversaries anyway.
My father forgot their 25th
a few months back.
And?
Gary paid a heavy price, boss.
Luckily, Kat's a reasonable person.
Reason's got nothing to do with it.
You're already doomed.
Oh, my gosh. That's a big gun.
Um... Am I on private property right now?
I'm so lost.
You... you want me to go back?
OK, I can... I can do that.
Um, can you just tell me where
Alouette Lake is?
Are you telling me the lake's back that way
or are you still telling me to turn around?
OK.
Jesus.
Callahan!
What is it?
- Where did the Fraser meteor come down?
A dry lakebed just north-east of here.
Why?
It wasn't dry this early in the 21st.
What's going on?
- I just got off the phone with a Traveler
who requested armed assets to the exact
same coordinates the meteor
was historically found, 50 years from now.
We got cut off,
but she said it was Protocol Alpha.
How's that possible?
What would've happened if Robert Fraser
hadn't discovered that element in 2068?
There'd be no room-temperature
superconductor for quantum processing
no leap in artificial intelligence
no consciousness-transfer technology...
- No Director.
Do we know when the meteor came down?
I'm no historian,
but I'm about to bet my job at the FBI
that it's sometime in the next 15 minutes
and that the Faction is trying to get to it
before we do.
The Director overwrote
all the Faction members.
Only Faction members it could get eyes on.
There could be hundreds still out there,
or worse, it's somebody else.
SHE GROANS
TRUCK HORN BELLOWS
SHE GASPS
Hey! What the fuck?
You alright?
SHE GRUNTS AND PANTS
SHE ROARS
SHE GROANS
CARLY: Amazing to me
this becomes a dry lakebed in 50 years.
MARCY: Do we need to worry about a wave?
TREVOR:
Nah. Probably just a splash.
Nothing too big.
Just extremely rare
and important to the future.
Even more rare than that other mineral...
What was it again?
You mean diamond?
That's it.
Alright, let's get the recovery gear ready
and make sure everything's working.
The Director gave us an important mission.
Let's not mess it up.
OUTBOARD ROARS
SHE SHOUTS: Get back from the water!
SHE WHEEZES
DISTANT GUNFIRE
HIGH-PITCHED RINGING
CARRIE SCREAMS
SHE SCREAMS
Carrie!
Carrie, what's wrong?
SHE SCREAMS
RADIO PLAYS
Buddy, open your chute...
HE SHOUTS:
Wayne! Open your chute!
God.
Oh, God. Oh, no, no, no, no!
Wayne? Wayne!
LARS SOBS
Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh...
Carrie!
What're you doing?
DOG BARKS
CARRIE SCREAMS
Carrie, what's wrong?
SHE SCREAMS
Well, then, help me out.
What's an appropriate gift for ten years?
Tin.
- Yeah, ten.
No, "tin".
Like soup tin?
- TREVOR: As in the metallic element.
That's the traditional gift.
I'm supposed to give her something
made from tin?
You cut the deployment close.
What happened?
We collided. He's unconscious
but I managed to get his parachute open
before we separated.
If he lands like that, he'll break his
neck. Do you have any weapons in the car?
What?
- Weapons.
No.
What are you doing?
The camera saw a knife in the pickup.
What? Carrie!
Carrie!
DOG BARKS
ENGINE STARTS
Hey. This place is where?
I'm lost. Can you help me?
OK. Fine, but... this place is where?
I need to know.
HE GRUNTS
MARCY: Might've gotten away
with flowers if you'd called.
MACLAREN: Yeah, we established
I made a mistake.
MARCY: Now you got to get her
a diamond-something.
MACLAREN:
Really?
Explain how buying something
hard and shiny, and artificially expensive
because it's controlled by a cartel,
gets me out of the dog pound.
MARCY:“Doghouse.”
- Were you trained at all
in 21st-century male behaviour, or...?
I think he's nailing it.
PHILIP: Historically, diamonds have
always been a rare and precious gift.
Oh, shut up.
Solve your own problems then.
Yeah, well, if it's rare
and precious she wants
I'll chip a fragment off the meteor
after we recover it.
It could come in handy
if Kathryn ever needs
a high-temperature superconductor
for quantum processing.
You shut up, too.
PHILIP CHUCKLES
TRUCK HORN BELLOWS
Hey! What the hell?
Asshole.
VAN HORN BLARES
PHONE RINGS
VOICEMAIL: You've reached
Special Agent Grant MacLaren.
Please leave a message.
BEEP
Hey, it's me.
Just giving you the benefit
of the doubt here.
I know you're probably busy on a case
and I married an FBI agent
but I'm assuming, when you write
“won't be by tonight, work”
in a text, it just means
that you're gonna be late
because tonight, of all nights
we should spend some time together
no matter what time it is.
Hint, hint.
OK, so...
I'm gonna plan something for later,
nothing fancy.
You just need to let me know
roughly when that will be.
You can even text me.
I'll be here.
Bye.
CARRIE WHEEZES
MacLaren!
You're in danger!
MACLAREN: Let's get the recovery gear
ready. Make sure everything's working.
The Director gave us an important mission.
Let's not fuck it up.
CARRIE, IN DISTANCE:
MacLaren!
Did you hear that?
- TREVOR: What?
CARRIE SHOUTS:
Your team is in danger!
MacLaren!
Run!
Carrie?
- Get off the beach!
What're you doing here?
I'm Traveler 500...
- GUNFIRE
GUNFIRE
GUNSHOT
CARRIE SCREAMS:
Oh, God!
SHE GASPS
Carrie, pull your chute.
Carrie!
What happened up there?
- We collided.
Then Wayne must be unconscious.
Give me your keys.
Wait, what?
- Your keys.
No. You're hurt!
- I need to go.
No, you're not going anywhere.
You're staying right here.
- The future is at stake.
No, you got a concussion.
But the Faction is gonna win
if we do not act.
OK, whatever. You're fucked up.
Just... just don't move, OK?
Your brother's in trouble.
CARRIE GROANS
He's gonna break his neck.
- CARRIE WHIMPERS AND GROANS
SHE PANTS WEAKLY
CARRIE SCREAMS
SHE GROANS
SHE GRUNTS
What happened?
Did you crash into each other?
SHE SPUTTERS
Too much strain on the host.
What? What?
There are five people on a remote beach.
It's not far...
Who?
- Doesn't matter.
Listen. You need to help them.
I can't make it.
You're not making any sense.
CARRIE GRUNTS
Everything is at stake.
You need to do this.
Do what? Do what?
I-I don't understand!
The coordinates. Y-You need...
You... You need to...
HE 8088 Carrie?
HE 8088 Carrie...
Oh, God...
Oh, God.
Oh, God!
Well, if it's rare and precious she wants
I'll chip a fragment off the meteor
after we recover it.
It could come in handy
if Kathryn ever needs
a high-temperature superconductor
for a quantum frame.
MACLAREN:
You shut up too.
Are you sure this is it?
PHILIP:
This is the place.
MACLAREN: It sure doesn't look anything
like the pictures when it was found.
This is beautiful.
Yeah, it's nice.
Nice? This is like seeing Niagara Falls
before it went dry
or the Great Valley
before the domes were built.
Yeah. I said it was nice.
She's not wrong.
HIGH-PITCHED RINGING
OUTBOARD ROARS
GUNFIRE
HIGH-PITCHED RINGING
HE GRUNTS
HE SCREAMS
Car keys! Give me the keys!
LARS SOBS
Oh, my God. Wayne, she's dead.
Give me the keys!
LARS SOBS
DOG BARKS
ENGINE STARTS
MOTORCYCLE ROARS
PHONE RINGS
VOICEMAIL: You've reached
Special Agent Grant MacLaren.
Please leave a message.
BEEP
Hello, Special Agent Grant MacLaren.
This is your apparently-not-so-special
wife of ten years
as of today.
Ten years, Grant.
I left you a phone message
and I sent you
a Happy Anniversary text before that
but neither really cover the range of
emotion that I'm feeling at the moment.
All I can say is,
you bloody well better be
shopping in a jewellery store right now
that happens to have shitty cell phone
reception.
Call me back when you get this.
Yeah, I said it was nice.
She's not wrong.
This is 026. Inbound with a full load.
About an hour out.
RADIO: 026, copy. See you then.
CAR HORN HONKS
Fuck you!
GUNSHOT
Got a sec?
Yeah.
Is everything alright?
If you mean with Kat and the pregnancy...
The pills you gave me-
- This isn't the time or the place.
No, I know. I was going to ask about you.
I'm fine.
I don't think you are.
Part of the team leader's job is to have
some inkling about the general welfare...
I said that I'm fine.
- You're not fine.
You're unhappy.
Look, Marcy, you can't possibly
remember this, but...
I didn't want to be reset?
Someone told you?
We should just get back to the mission.
No. There's plenty of time.
Let them take care of it.
Look, I didn't see the good in telling you
that information
and maybe I was wrong
but it's pretty obvious to me
and probably everyone else
that the new Marcy is
different from the old one
in ways she wouldn't approve.
She?
That's your word.
Well, hers.
I just...
SHE SIGHS
I just can't help but feel
that I'm not really...
What?
Whole.
That when Grace
sent my consciousness to the future -
repackaged it,
and then sent it back again, that...
she left out what made me “me”.
That very day
you told me you were afraid of losing the
most important part of who you had become
in your short time in the 21st.
- How do I even know what that is?
I don't think it's my
place to say, but I...
I can give you a hint.
After that plane crash
that should've killed me
when you and a million nanites
were trying to put me back together...
my own consciousness
took refuge in the memories
of Grant MacLaren.
Well, that's not possible.
There are none.
Only a few.
Disconnected fragments.
Of What?
Of how much Grant MacLaren loved his wife.
Memories even his death couldn't erase.
How do I possibly access that?
You're the doctor.
Where does it come down?
Six hundred metres to our south-southwest.
GUNFIRE
CARRIE: Killer day, huh?
MACLAREN: Yeah. Yeah. It's... killer.
What are you guys up to?
Uh, heading up to a lake,
do a little camping.
Fishing!
- Fishing.
What about you? What are you up to?
About 15,000 feet.
We're going skydiving.
Oh! That sounds... terrifying.
You know, it's...
Oh, yeah. No. It'll clear up.
You know, statistically,
it's actually safer than driving.
So people tell me.
You should try it sometime.
No. I'm not... I'm not so good
with things in the sky.
OK.
Gotta fly, Carrie.
See you later.
- Yeah, have fun... Carrie.
Isn't she a little young for you?
And I'm married. I know.
Uh, speaking of which...
Your wife just texted you,
saying “Happy Anniversary”.
What? Shit!
- Yeah.
You might wanna give her a call.
She didn't have any fresh fruit
like you asked
so I got you something called
a “fruit pie” instead.
Has the word “fruit” in it.
Sure does.
Thanks, Trev. That's great.
RADIO PLAYS
Whoa! Turn it up! This is my favourite
part! No, you'll just sing louder.
MUSIC: "What A Day To Shake A Heartache"
by Sherry Lynn
SHE SINGS ALONG OFF-KEY
Don't roll your eyes at me!
♪ Back to where I was before ♪
♪ Bye-bye, baby ♪
The problem is, when I said turn,
you didn't turn.
The GPS said there's no road.
- Well, there's one on the map.
So we'll turn around.
OK.
- There's lots of time.
Thank you.
HIGH-PITCHED RINGING
HE GASPS AND SCREAMS
HE SCREAMS
MARCY:
Are you sure this is it?
This is the place.
Sure doesn't look anything like
the pictures when it was found.
This is beautiful.
DOG BARKS
ENGINE REVS
Marcy, you can't possibly
remember this, but...
I didn't want to be reset?
Someone told you?
We should just get back to the mission.
No. There's plenty of time.
Let them take care of it.
- SHE SIGHS
Look. I didn't see the good in telling you
that information
and maybe I was wrong
but it's pretty obvious to me,
and probably everyone else
that the new Marcy is
different from the old one
in ways she wouldn't approve.
That very day,
you told me you were afraid of losing
the most important part
of who you had become
in your short time in the 21st.
How do I even know what that is?
- I don't think it's my place to say
but I...
I can give you a hint.
GUNSHOT
After the plane crash
that should've killed me
when you and a million nanites
were trying to put me back together...
my own consciousness took refuge
in the memories of Grant MacLaren.
But how do I possibly access that?
You're the doctor.
WAYNE, IN DISTANCE:
MacLaren!
Did you hear that?
HE WHEEZES
Oh!
MacLaren!
GUNFIRE
Identify yourself.
Traveler 5008.
I'm on a Protocol Alpha mission...
- We know, it's all over.
Marcy, all clear!
No, there's one more down the road.
I had to go around him.
I took care of him first.
We did it.
Thank you both.
That was close.
You don't know how close.
HE PANTS
We weren't the first.
We had to keep trying.
How many times?
I was the ninth volunteer.
Jesus.
If the element ended up
in the hands of the Faction
the whole Traveler program might never-
DISTANT BANG
See? Just a splash.
Our mission is to recover and secure the
meteorite upon impact, so...
We'll stay here and watch your back
till you're done.
I'll have him patched up by then.
There's one other thing.
We have your next mission.
OUTBOARD ROARS