Targeting far left.
PHILIP: T.E.L.L. established.
Stand by. Target two.
T.E.L.L. established.
HIGH-PITCHED WHISTLING
Traveler incoming on target one.
MACLAREN: Take him out.
I'm 3468.
5401.
Yeah, he's dead.
We needed three to make it even.
He was gonna kill both of you.
- MACLAREN: Stay calm.
Stick to the plan.
I'll be right behind you.
DOOR OPENS
What are you doing?
- What do you mean? It's lunchtime.
You're supposed to be on sentry duty.
- Oh, Jasper's still out there. It's fine.
No, it's not fine.
There could be Travelers out there.
They're in here now.
Don't.
- Hands in the air.
Your protocols won't let you take a life.
Protocol 3 has been suspended
for members of the Faction.
I wouldn't risk it.
CARLY: Weapons down, hands up.
Where's the quantum frame?
Not here.
Secure them.
What're you gonna do with us?
That'll be up to the Director.
So death by overwrite.
You mean like you did to your hosts?
Our plan might have saved the future.
You people are pathetic.
Meaning we're capable of pity,
sympathy, or compassion for others?
I've really been enjoying English class
this year.
Yeah, I can see that.
Let's get moving.
CARLY: Move.
Stay still.
OK, let's see what we can pull from this.
You won't find anything.
- MACLAREN: I don't know.
My people are pretty good at this.
Thanks, boss.
Be good at this.
- Mhm.
We can always try torture.
No, we couldn't.
They've been in hiding so long, I doubt
they know where the frame is anyway.
Even if we knew, we wouldn't tell you.
So someone point a fucking camera
this way and end this.
I'm good with that.
The Director has plans for them.
This is the first I'm hearing about it.
Because you are a part of those plans.
A hearing has been ordered.
Your presence,
along with 3569 and 0115, is required.
Where?
- You'll receive the coordinates tomorrow.
CORK POPS
To selling our house.
To selling our house over asking.
Yay!
We're officially homeless.
Well, I am.
Not till you finish packing.
I don't know how you can drink this stuff.
Because I'm not allowed to drink that stuff
and the calcium is good
for the development of bones.
You haven't touched the
almond milk I bought.
Grant, if there was ever a time you were
gonna lose this vegan battle with me
it's when I'm pregnant.
- Fair.
You know, I was thinking,
we should put some of our house money
into a trust fund, for
college tuition and...
College?
That's years from now.
You need to learn to think of the future.
Oh, I... I have given that some thought.
And I think...
I'm gonna buy a boat with my half.
Given your history with the water
I'd better take a life-insurance policy
out on you instead.
Ow. Break one arm one time...
HE SIGHS
Were you planning on going back
to the house tonight?
It's early.
Are you kicking me out already?
No.
I'm asking you to stay.
You haven't changed position
since I left last night.
Oh. No, I guess I haven't.
Find anything on the coms?
They've been all over the place.
This data is pretty much useless.
CARLY: What about these points?
Looks like they frequented these locations
multiple times.
Maybe the frame's there.
Where the frame might have been,
not where it is now.
Well, there's gotta be CCTV or traffic cams
in those areas.
Maybe you can pull the footage,
see if any of them picked anything up.
If the Faction left anything on
those cameras - and hey, I wouldn't -
then the Director would've already
found it by now.
HE GROANS
HE SIGHS
Something's bothering you.
The timeline has changed a lot.
My knowledge of the future
is becoming obsolete.
It's going to be hard to stay relevant.
You're more than just the team's
encyclopaedia, Philip.
Who else am I gonna call when I can't get
Jeffrey's cartoons to play on my phone?
So flattering.
Or make me music playlists...
Teach me about turtles...
The self-worth
is just coursing through my veins.
You're like the rest of us now.
Just a human being.
And that's OK.
I gotta go to work, but I'll com in.
Have a nice day.
- Go for a walk!
THEY LAUGH
Oh! My... God.
I guess we were making up for lost time.
Lost time?
I don't even know what day it is.
SHE LAUGHS I know.
I'm gonna be in court all day, so...
I'll be hard to reach.
But I'll see you tonight?
How's that for an answer?
Grant?
I love you.
I love you, too.
ROBOTIC VOICE:
3468. Coordinates are as follows.
47.6050 degrees North
by 122.3344 degrees West.
GIRL: Why am I in the hallway?
Is it time for school?
Not yet.
Are you our new neighbour?
I guess I am.
Have a nice day, neighbour.
What are you doing here?
- What are you doing here?
He asked first.
A messenger gave me the coordinates
for a hearing.
Scared me half to death.
Maybe it's their trial.
Shouldn't take long then.
All rise for the arrival
of the Tribunal Committee.
INTENSE HIGH-FREQUENCY SOUND
SOLDIERS SCREAM
SILENCE
I'm Traveler 009.
You may refer to me as the Speaker.
I'm joined by Travelers 0017 and 0029.
They're programmers.
What the hell are all of you doing here?
Who's maintaining the Director?
- 0027.
We came to the 21st as instructed
by the Director.
Unlike yourself.
So that's what this is about?
0027, you are charged with conspiracy
against the Director
and the high crime of interrupting
the Grand Plan.
POP MUSIC PLAYS
I liked that one.
Can you add it to my playlist?
And just like that,
I am reduced to being Carly's DJ.
SHE CHUCKLES
Something upbeat, please.
Any luck with the footage?
They wiped everything,
just like we thought.
I'm running serial numbers
of the weapons they were carrying.
Grasping at straws here.
They're bound to slip up, and when they do,
we'll be ready for them.
'Dropping by Ops after work?
No, I gotta pick up Jeffrey from the
sitter, get some groceries, and...
SHE SIGHS
bring my van to the mechanic.
I've been having trouble starting it
in the mornings.
Maybe I could be a mechanic.
I do live in a garage.
CARLY SIGHS:
Stop it.
You're a valuable member of the team.
And a great DJ.
Next song, please.
PROGRAMMER:
3468, please take the stand.
Recount to us how you first made contact
with 0027.
MACLAREN: I met Grace several months ago,
when my team was given a mission
to greet Traveler 0014, Ellis.
Grace arrived at the same time
and said her mission was to help Marcy.
PROGRAMMER:
But that was a lie, wasn't it?
No, it wasn't. I saved her life.
The defendant will
refrain from interjection.
If you refrain from leading questions!
Go ahead. He interrupted you.
Later, we learnt she was actually here
to reset the Director
by taking advantage of Marcy's new T.E.L.L.
And you were unaware of
this secondary objective?
She eventually told us. Prior to that,
we believed that she was only here
to save Marcy.
- Which I did.
And for which I am deeply grateful.
You're welcome.
PROGRAMMER: At any point, did you suspect
that she was a member of the Faction?
MACLAREN: In the future we left,
there was no Faction.
Protocol two has kept us in the dark.
We had no idea.
And who wrote protocol two?
- Oh, come on! You know I did.
0027, please.
Teams in the 21st shouldn't be made
aware of every change in the future
because completion rates of our missions
would drop exponentially.
You have been asked by the tribunal
not to interject.
Operatives would be
paralysed by the fear of
how their actions
could negatively affect
the people they left behind.
- Enough!
I agree!
If I hadn't reset the Director,
the Faction would have corrupted it
which means the Faction
would have control of the past.
What I did was the only way to save Marcy
and the Director.
It was the Director who ordered
this hearing, not any one of us.
Why?
It knows what really happened.
It knows what I sacrificed.
This... This makes no sense.
And yet here we are.
We will take a brief recess to allow
that fact to sink in.
Blair, hi, it's David. I...
Hi! You're still at home.
Yeah, I was just calling to leave a message
to wish you a happy birthday.
So, uh, happy birthday.
Yeah.
Anyhoo, that's the one and only reason
I was calling, so have a great...
A rave?
HE LAUGHS
Oh.
No.
No, no, I don't, um...
I don't do rave.
It's just not my...
Tell you what, I'll say maybe.
And, uh...
Yeah. I'll try.
Yeah, I'll... I'll try to maybe
see you later.
OK. Yeah, bye.
0115.
Were you responsible for interrupting
Grace Day's original T.E.L.L.?
I was.
Whose orders were you acting on?
- No one.
Then Why'd you do it?
I didn't want her to die.
That simple.
As a Traveler, you don't just inherit
the host body, you inherit
the lives they've touched -
family, friends...
Grace Day was merely
a guidance counsellor...
at your host's high school.
- That doesn't do her justice.
See, my host was a bully.
Cruel.
She tried to help him anyway.
She was there for him.
For me.
SPEAKER: And historically,
she was supposed to die.
I rationalised that one person
wouldn't matter to the Grand Plan
but I was lying to myself.
I broke protocol because
she did matter to me...
and I'm willing to accept the consequences.
Because of your actions,
0027 locked out all transfers to the 21st
until she could send herself
into the host, Grace Day
halting the Traveler programme
for four hours.
- I couldn't just go into anyone.
PROGRAMMER:
Dozens of missions were cancelled.
A Traveler was supposed
to arrive in Germany
and prevent an impending
train derailment.
All the passengers died.
A team meant to arrive in England
and stop a terrorist attack
was unable to transit.
TREVOR: I assumed that the Director
would choose a new host
for the next scheduled Traveler.
- The Grand Plan is fluid.
It's constantly shifting.
The Director is constantly analysing
a myriad of outcomes and course-correcting
to the fraction of a second.
Are you trying to school me in the matrix
of algorithms the Director uses
to oversee the Traveler programme?
SPEAKER: For the last time, 027...
TREVOR: If the crime is disruption
of the Grand Plan, then I'm the one
that allowed that to happen.
I'm the one that should be punished.
SPEAKER: The Director will no doubt take it
into account.
You may step down.
2103, will you please take the stand?
Oh, seriously? That guy hates me.
Philip, I have a situation.
Hey, what's the good news?
Definitely not my pay cheque.
How the hell do they expect people
to live on this?
And the capitalist-socialist debate
strikes again.
Well, this isn't enough for me
to cover my expenses this week.
Can you top me up?
Sure, let me see what
I can move around for you.
This can't be right.
What? What is it?
Something happened to the market this
morning when I was out for a walk.
Our investments are down.
I'm scared to tell you how much.
How did that happen?
Most of our higher-risk investments
just crashed and burned.
We're in serious financial trouble.
This was a meeting Ken had
been preparing for for a month.
I mean, he had... he had note cards
and everything.
PHONE BUZZES And, uh...
Even had his hair slicked back, which is a
clear sign that, you know, it's important.
PHONE BUZZES
You gonna get that?
Uh, no. No, I'm not.
Anyway...
So we're all sitting there, and he
stands up to do his presentation
and his fly, it's wide open.
Oh, no.
Was his penis exposed?
Uh, no...
No, I mean, that would... that would be...
But, anyway, there's a...
window in his office and I think,
midway through, he must have
caught his reflection,
because he just...
he just knew.
And there was nothing he could do about it,
but you could see him debate it
in his head, like, "Do I do up
my fly while I'm still talking?"
SHE LAUGHS Have I met Ken?
That's the funny thing, you actually have.
You've actually asked that question before.
Oh.
This looks good.
PHONE BUZZES
RAVE MUSIC PLAYS
Blair! You're not allowed to do this
on your birthday.
He's so not worth it.
Hold onto me!
MACHINE BLASTS
HIGH-PITCHED RINGING
BOOM
CROWD SCREAMS
HIGH-PITCHED WHISTLING
RINGING STOPS
What's happening?
PHONE BUZZES
Then, why did, um...
Why did Ken change his mind?
I don't know.
I just, I came in ready to pack up all my
things, and he told me I still had a job.
It's a mystery.
Do you want some more wine?
Um, maybe in a minute.
I'm just gonna use the bathroom.
Excuse me.
PHONE CHIMES
BLAIR: David, please!
'Help me! Please, I need your help!'!
SHE SCREAMS
I'm locked in a stall!
'They're trying to come in..
'Please! Please, help me!'!
SHE SCREAMS
Uh...
Where are you going?
Here, listen to this.
ON PHONE: David, please! Help me!
Please, I need your help!
BLAIR SCREAMS
- I'm coming with you.
Here.
And by a nose, Saladin's Vigil
crosses the finish line.
ANNOUNCER: anyone's race.
Easy Star is making a move!
And by a nose, Nemesis Star
crosses the finish line!
That was down to the wire...
Outbreak Prime is well ahead in the lead
to win first place.
ANNOUNCER: Outbreak Prime is well ahead...
But, now, pulling up from the middle
of the pack is Gjallahorn!
Shit.
MARCY: So what is a rave?
DAVID: An illegal dance party
with loud music, drugs, alcohol.
Not that I've ever been to one.
I don't dance so much
as I rhythmically stand.
MARCY: Wait...
If there's supposed to be loud music,
shouldn't we be hearing it by now?
Uh... Yeah.
DAVID: What, you just carry that around?
MARCY: Yep.
DAVID: Blair?
MARCY: Hey.
What happened?
Hey?
MARCY: She's overdosing.
We need to get her to a hospital
and administer-
Do you just carry that around?
A lot of my clients
have addiction problems.
SHE GASPS
Hey...
BLAIR: David?
Hey. What happened?
We were in the bathroom...
People started screaming.
When I came out, they all turned on me.
Hey, give me your phone.
OK, we're gonna get you to a hospital,
and you're gonna be OK, alright?
BEEP COM
Hey...
I'm at a building at the corner
of 50th and Baker.
I don't know how they moved it so fast, but
the frame was here less than an hour ago.
Who're you talking to?
- Pull up the camera feeds.
I'll be right over.
- Camera feeds?
You need to get her to a hospital.
I need to go.
OK. Marcy!
'ON PHONE: 911. What's your emergency?'?
PHILIP: They wiped all the footage
before they left again
but we know for certain
that the frame was there.
MACLAREN: Well, thank God
for the selfie generation.
Can you zoom in there?
MARCY: Faction took everyone at the rave
except three women
who were apparently
in the bathroom.
We found them overdosed, probably a way of
eliminating them as witnesses.
And they survived?
David and I managed to save one of them,
but she didn't see anything.
But it's a safe bet everyone else
in the photo's a Faction.
It makes sense, but I don't know how
you prove it.
Locate them, if you can.
We have to get back to
the hearing marathon.
How's that going? Can you say?
Not looking good for Grace.
PROGRAMMER: Marcy.
How and why did 0027 "repackage"
your consciousness?
Well, obviously, I don't actually remember
but from what I was briefed on
she showed me a code.
Something that Ellis created.
A backdoor hack...
which, during the repackaging process
somehow managed to reset the Director.
Admittedly, a brilliant piece of work.
Thank you.
And how has that worked out for you, Marcy,
this "reset" of your consciousness?
Uh, how is this relevant?
I restored her.
Do you feel restored, Marcy?
I no longer have seizures.
But do you feel as you did before?
No.
But that's partly because I have no memory
of my time spent in the 21st prior.
There are missing pieces, then?
Yes.
Marcy...
I've studied your MRls.
She had to have taken out
more than just a few months of memories.
What else did you take out?
I told you.
Redundancies, useless things.
Such as what?
Empathy? Emotions you lack?
Oh, shut up, 29.
You're practically a sociopath yourself.
How could you do that to me?
- You would have died!
Yeah, but that would've been
my choice to make.
You used me.
Yes, I did!
I prevented your suicide.
Life is precious, and so are skilled
operatives in the field.
I was just a means to an end.
Marcy, you're still you. I swear to you.
I didn't take your soul.
How would you even know?
Carly, I think I found one of the people
in the picture.
Forget the first three.
What do you think of four and five?
Not a big fan of Mason.
But it's so masculine. Like a stonemason.
It's also a jar you keep pickles in.
What about your father's name?
Oh, Wilbur's the pig in Charlotte '5 Web.
- And a Wright brother.
Watch out. I might be contagious.
I've built up an immunity.
How're you feeling?
Didn't you hear? I don't have feelings.
Yeah, you do.
I got you these.
What are they?
Try one. They're French.
SHE SIGHS
At least if they throw the book at me,
I can say I've had 21st-century
French cuisine.
HE CHUCKLES
Why are you being nice to me?
Do you know something?
No. No, it's because we wouldn't even be
here if you hadn't reset the Director.
You gotta understand that they'll come
to the same conclusion.
Trust the judgment of those
mouth-breathers? Please.
PHONE BUZZES
Oh.
You need to take that?
Ah, it can wait.
Besides, I gotta do this.
Do what?
Bring it in, Grace! You need this.
- I don't. Can we not-
Oh, it's happening.
- Come on, there you go.
OK. Thanks. You can let go now.
Wasn't so bad, was it?
I do feel a slight release of endorphins.
You see?
Do you have a regular sex partner?
You can't hate every one I come up with.
Well, we don't even know
if we're going to have a boy or girl!
You think I'm getting too excited.
You know what? You're right.
- N... No.
No, I love to hear the excitement
in your voice when you're...
talking about new life.
'Kat, I gotta get back into court..
Just... Just narrow it down
to the top 100 or so
and we'll go through it tonight, OK?
- OK.
SPEAKER: 0027, you have heard the charges
against you.
What do you have to say in your defense?
I've given it a great deal of thought,
run the events over and over in my mind
a thousand times, and to be honest...
You should all be thanking me.
Like my very dear friend
just pointed out...
Uh-oh.
If I hadn't have reset the Director,
none of you would be here right now.
The Director would be gone,
the Faction would have won
and billions of people
would be dead from a horrible plague.
So...
You're welcome!
0027, the members of the Tribunal
will now deliberate.
We will announce your
final verdict tomorrow.
We are adjourned.
KNOCKING
May I help you?
Stacey Collins, we have a few questions.
How do you know my name?
You were at a rave last night.
Do you recognise this?
Where's the quantum frame?
You're standing right beside it
in the picture.
We know you're Faction.
SHE SCOFFS
What are you talking about?
We know you just arrived.
Maybe if you cooperate-
- Who are you people?
Get the fuck away from me.
I'm calling the police.
Whoa! Carly.
She's Faction.
How do we prove it?
Who do we prove it to?
This is what happens when you improvise.
We can't just walk away.
- That's exactly what we have to do.
But maybe we can follow her or something.
SIRENS WAIL
Jesus! She actually called the cops!
Take care of yourself, OK?
I'll check in with you tomorrow.
OK? Bye.
Yes, bye.
B... Bye...
Bye-bye.
HE SIGHS
You do know Chinese food is my kryptonite.
Oh, I just... I know you've been going back
and forth from the hospital all day
so I wanted to bring you some dinner.
- Yeah! Thank you.
I am starving.
How's Blair doing?
Alright. Well, we got there just in time.
It was a lethal dose of fentanyl.
On her birthday.
So they're gonna keep her
for the next couple of days.
Mm.
You're looking at me funny. What?
I'm just trying to figure something out.
I'm sorry. I wasn't100% finished chewing.
Marcy, stop.
Why? What is it?
Let's, um...
Let's not, OK?
You don't want to.
- Oh, no, I do. I mean...
I really... But...
Not like this. Not...
Not like an experiment to see how
it makes you feel.
Because I... I know...
I know how it made me feel
when we made love.
And it's as close as you can get to another
person for 10 minutes.
I mean, an hour.
I want to feel that.
But you can't make yourself feel something.
I mean, you either do or you... you don't.
And I want you...
to want 1:0.
I know that sounds like a bad song title
from the 803, but...
Should I just go?
- No! No, stay.
Share this with me,
and we'll make some tea
and, and...
we'll talk, like we do on Tuesdays.
What should we talk about?
THEY CHUCKLE
With you, Marcy, I could
talk about anything.
0027, you've been charged with conspiracy
against the Director
and interruption of the Grand Plan.
You took a host that
wasn't intended for you,
and you halted the
Traveler programme for-
You've already said all that!
Cut to the chase.
You've repeatedly stated that your actions
reset the Director
and freed it from corruption.
- Because they did.
Then who corrupted the Director
in the first place?
The most powerful A.I. in history,
orders of magnitude more powerful
than the human brain?
Who would have that capability?
Obviously, a quantum programmer
of the highest caliber.
So only the best among us.
Yes.
PROGRAMMER:
And who might that be?
Don't say it.
- Obviously me!
But I didn't corrupt the Director!
I was the one waving a red flag
while you three were lining up
at the yeast vats, filling your bellies!
Traveler 0027, your peers have reached
a unanimous verdict.
We find you guilty.
HE GROANS
What?
Escort her to the sentencing room.
Wait! W-W-Wait. Wait, wait.
No, no, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no! MacLaren, do something!
- I'm sorry, Grace.
Trevor, don't let them do this!
- You can't help her, Trev!
But she's innocent!
- Trevor! Help me!
She doesn't deserve this!
- She didn't do much to help her case.
It's in the hands of the Director now.
Be seated.
Your sentencing will begin shortly.
What do you think will happen to her?
If the Director agrees with the Tribunal,
she'll probably be overwritten.
Can I give you a ride home?
Oh, it's not that far.
I think I'll walk.
I just need to clear my head.
You OK?
- I'm fine.
Marcy?
May I speak with you?
Yes, of course, Programmer.
You may never get an apology from 0027
but as a programmer, I want you to know how
sorry I am for what happened to you.
Thank you, but that's not necessary.
Well, I think it is.
What 0027 did to you was criminal.
That sense of emptiness that you must feel,
of not being whole...
It's offensive to me
that someone would do that to you
for their own agenda.
Well, I guess she'll face the consequences.
But you shouldn't have to.
I think I can offer you the missing pieces
that you've been looking for.
This is my field of expertise.
I don't understand.
My new team has been doing research
on preserving host memory.
In your case, that would be your first
iteration.
I thought those memories were lost forever.
Perhaps not all.
Perhaps even the most powerful memories,
the most defining...
are still there...
and I can get them back for you.
When?
Well, as soon as you like.
Of course, if you need time to think
about it...
No, there's nothing to think about.
Unfortunate, what must happen to Grace.
Is it?
In that it's a waste of intellect.
Returning to Ops now.
Bringing Marcy with me.
Half-hour out.
I'll be ready.
SHE SOBS
Are you here?
I'm here, 0027.
Call me Grace.
I didn't betray you.
I would never betray you.
You, of anyone, should know that.
You are one of four candidates,
although the probability of guilt
is negligible.
Then why are you going to overwrite me?
Be patient.
I have not yet determined who amongst you
is the traitor.
No...
No!
Who did this?
I don't know.
Was this your team?
Well, the frame is powered,
it can still function.
I can still help you, Marcy.
We both know you're not trying to help me.
You won't shoot.
You want Ellis' backdoor code
to take over the Director
and you think it's still inside my head.
Listen to me, Marcy.
The future is at stake.
MAN: Drop your weapon!
What the hell happened?
Honestly? I don't even think that he knows.
The situation is now resolved.
0029 will be charged with the crime
of Treason
and sentenced immediately.
You used my trial as an excuse
to get everyone here in the 21st
to flush the traitor out?
The frame...
SHE WHEEZES
has also been neutralised.
You humiliated me.
I sacrificed everything for you.
I... I left everything I knew behind,
just to save you.
DIRECTOR: I'm sorry.
I hoped you would understand
it was necessary.
You're still gonna punish me, aren't you?
I know I took the life of this host
after the fact.
I know I interrupted the Grand Plan.
Ellis is dead because of me.
But I can never go back.
Isn't that punishment enough?
More than enough...
I owe you my life.
Thank you for saving me, Grace.
I shall miss you.
Traveler 0029, you have been
charged with the crime of treason.
You're on the wrong side of history,
MacLaren.
And you have been found guilty.
And the Director will sentence you now.
HIGH-PITCHED RINGING
HE GROANS
HE CRIES OUT IN AGONY
HE WAILS
SILENCE
Welcome to the 21st.
TREVOR: Boss?
Make every fragment of it unrecognisable.
It's over then?
- I'm not so sure.
Who killed all of them?