CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYS
Grant...
Grant?
Grant, we are not spending that much
on football tickets!
Have you seen these seats?
This is a bargain.
Do not get caught in a bidding war.
Kat, it's for charity!
Think of the children.
I wonder how my steak knives are doing.
- No, Grant-
Doesn't cost nothing to look!
Oh, shit, I'm sorry, that was my fault.
Let me get you another one.
Do you want another one, too?
I'm going to get you one.
I'll get us all one.
My husband doesn't get out much.
Neither do I.
This is a great event.
Do you work for the hospital?
Someone my wife was very close to
received care here.
We became supporters.
You?
Uh, we live nearby.
I donated a chair.
You endowed a new position.
SHE LAUGHS Oh, sorry, no...
Um, I literally gave them a chair.
I'm a designer.
Is the chair in the auction?
It is.
And I would be very happy
to show it to you, Mr...?
Ingram.
But please call me Vincent.
Kathryn.
Um...
It doesn't have any bids, unfortunately.
Well, we'll have to see
what we can do about that.
My wife always put us down
for all...
The, ah...
all the auction items
that could use a little support.
She sounds lovely.
She was. Unfortunately, she...
Forgive me, this work
has left me speechless.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Apparently, these were created
by one of the patients.
Do you see a piece you like, Mr Ingram?
All of them.
I'll buy all of them.
GUN FIRES
Beth, where's the Petrov file?
Excuse me?
All my material on the Petrov case,
it was right here.
It was reassigned.
Why?
We weren't expecting you all week.
Well, I'm here.
I can see that, but no-one
would think worse of you if you weren't.
What is that supposed to mean?
Nothing, I was just trying to be nice.
Here.
Knock yourself out.
He keeps to himself mostly.
He has some issues with coherent thought
but, hey, who doesn't?
How long have you known him?
About a year, year and a half?
I met him, actually, not long after
I met you.
He's a good person inside,
he just doesn't trust many people.
Paranoid? Delusional?
Oh, yeah. He's on a mission from
"the Director."
Whatever that means.
Hey, here's some more.
They look new.
Just finished.
Hi, Marcy.
I like your hair.
It looks nice.
♪ In the shadows of denial  ♪
♪  You are hiding from the world ♪
♪ All the promise on your... ♪
MUSIC DISTORTS
'CARLY: Philip?'?
Philip!
♪  Or right where you belong?  ♪
'Can you change the song, please?'?
I'm not your DJ, Carly.
'CARLY: This song is so slow..
I'm not your DJ.
'But you're so good at it..
♪  Or right where you belong?  ♪
♪  Were you too far gone?
Na na na na na na na na... it
MUSIC CHANGES
Thank you!
You say something?
- Hmm?
I like those moves.
SHE CHUCKLES
I'll see you tonight?
Hey!
You bring it on yourself.
You know, I should have asked
if you want to drive.
Give you the practise.
In a few years, cars are going to be
driving themselves.
That's true.
You know, your mother and I heard about
what's going on with your coach
at school.
Nobody had any idea that was happening.
He seemed like a normal guy.
I hope he fries - sick bastard.
Anyway, uh...
I want you to know that we're here for you
if you ever want to talk about it
or whatever.
We'd feel awful if anything like that...
You don't have to worry, Gary.
It didn't happen to me.
Yeah, good.
Good.
That's what I figured.
No way, not my son.
Yeah.
So strange to see these in the 21st...
I remember him from the institution.
You do?
Host memories from a long time ago.
Which means he's several years
into a psychotic existence.
Hey, Simon.
Simon, this is a friend of mine,
he has a couple questions for you.
Questions, yeah, right.
You got a gun, I can see it.
I see everything.
And I'm on your side, Simon.
Can you tell me your Traveler number?
Do you remember any of the rest of
your team or where they might be?
I checked the area in the shelter
where he sleeps.
Seems like he's been on his own
for a while.
You want what's in my head
but there's just so much
that you don't understand.
You might be surprised
what we can understand.
OK, so you know that an emission
of Hawking radiation
concerns two mutually
entangled particles?
Who doesn't?
And if that particle enters a black hole
it emits a finite amount of information,
leaving you with what?
A paradox.
The monogamy of entanglement
requires that the
outgoing particle be fixed
inside two independent systems
at the same time.
Definitely upper echelon.
Probably a specialist.
Is that right, Simon?
Are you a specialist?
Yes, I am.
And if you don't believe me,
ask the Director!
Ask the...
- Simon.
Shut up.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry...
Hey, Simon? Simon...?
- No, I can't.
He's here.
Who's here?
I can't!
That's Vincent Ingram.
Yes, it is.
How do you know that? You never met.
There are no photographs.
He was at the institution.
He experimented on patients.
And you remember that?
He's 001.
What?
Simon.
-  I didn't say anything!
I told you, Simon.
I was very clear.
- No!
You know what you have to do.
- I don't want to!
You have to.
HE SIGHS
Now I have to take extreme measures.
Whoa, whoa! He has a weapon!
- Simon, take it easy!
Stop him!
SIMON WAILS
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
THEY GRUNT AND GROAN
MARCY: It's OK, it's OK...
Lower him down.
OK... You're OK.
What'd I miss?
Sorry, it's a bitch getting here.
Can we meet at an easier place
next time?
Crazy how small they're getting, right?
- Can I get another one next week?
Next week?
I can try, but... I gotta ask
what are you doing with all this stuff?
- VINCENT: Don't tell him.
What did you just say to me?
I... I said, just, what are you building?
I mean, I just hope it's nothing,
like, illegal.
I'll see what I can find,
but I can't promise anything!
VINCENT: Simon...
Simon... Simon... Simon...
Simon!
HE GASPS'
What are you doing here?
You need to leave.
Hey.
Marcy said you'd be feeling
better when you woke up
but there's still a few hours
left to go before dawn.
You can relax now, by the way.
You're safe here.
DISTANT CLICK
CLICK
- Shit.
Oh, come on...
LOUD CLICK
Grant?
Sorry. I...
It's four in the morning.
There, there's a sound...
What sound?
- It's like a, a clicking.
There's a clicking, do y...?
DISTANT CLICK
There. There!
HE SIGHS
Um...
The lamp's on a security timer.
Oh...
OK...
- Now will you please come back to bed?
Yeah.
HE INHALES
Oh...
HE 8058
Shh...
We can take turns being the strong one.
Morning. I didn't want to...
oh.
That's a new interface.
It's cleaner.
And it's in colour.
Colour?
Do you mind if I...?
Sure.
Multi-homed...
Asymmetric crypto...
Hello?
COMPUTER CHIMES
No...
SIRENS APPROACH
SIRENS BLAHE
No...
No!
HELICOPTER WHIRS
HE YELLS
I surrender!
HE YELLS: I surrender!
Hi.
Hey.
Are you OK?
I don't know.
Just tell me what's wrong.
Maybe I can help.
Alright, I'll just get right to it.
So I've been away and you've been home
and that's totally fine.
Yeah.
And I've been learning all this new stuff
and meeting new friends,
having these experiences and...
it feels good, you know?
But then I come back home and everything's
the same but it's not.
I don't know what I'm trying to say.
You're breaking up with me.
No, I'm not...
Am I?
Yeah. You're growing into the woman you're
going to become, and that's exciting.
You don't have to leave.
No, for sure, it's just that you told me
it was an emergency
so I kinda dropped
everything I was doing...
Yeah, it's an emergency
for our relationship!
I don't even know what I want right now.
I understand.
Just take all the time you need.
You'll make the right decision.
PHILIP: Boss?
Go ahead.
You're going to want to see this.
Agent MacLaren.
David, what do you need?
I'm just...
- Yeah, I just had some questions.
They're mostly about Marcy.
Mostly?
All.
I'll ride down with you.
I wrote them down...
- Yeah, I can see that.
Uh, has Marcy's situation changed at work?
You know I can't talk about our work.
Right, but in general,
is she under more stress?
Maybe she's dealing with
a difficult situation?
Let me...
"Have I noticed a sudden
personality change?"
"Is she giving away
any personal possessions?"
This one here seems to be, like,
that's more of a statement...
What, what is this about?
OK, well, I've had some training in this
and recently, I've witnessed some signs
of self-destructive behaviour.
I'm well aware of what happened
with Marcy, if that's what you're asking.
With the tub and the ice...
I know how that must have looked,
but that wasn't self-destructive -
it was experimental.
Cutting-edge science-
- It was extremely dangerous.
Look, would I have approved? No.
Do I understand why she did it?
Yeah, I do.
So should you.
Come on.
We have some new information.
Simon was one of the first Travelers.
004.
His mission was to set up
our communication infrastructure.
So what happened?
Schizophrenia manifests
itself later in life.
He was sent into a compromised host.
How well do you understand the Internet?
I'm... Good with languages.
OK, well, broadly speaking,
there are four layers:
Application, transport, Internet,
and physical.
One of the first things
that Simon did when he arrived
was create a whole new physical layer.
A dedicated backbone that piggybacks
off cell phone networks and
communications satellites.
Our back channel in the deep web.
Turns out our back channel
also has layers.
He's watching you.
Vincent's spying on us there, too.
He's using secret layers
in the back channel
for secure communication
and to spy on other Travelers.
That's the bad news.
The good news is, now that we know,
we think we can use it
against him to find out where he's hiding.
Show me.
He presented very classically.
Persecutory delusions,
fear of authority and surveillance...
The neuroleptics levelled him out
and we've been working on
the other stuff ever since.
He believes he was sent from the future
on a mission to save the Earth.
He literally doesn't think
he's living in his own body.
The art therapy has been
a successful intervention.
As you know, he's a natural talent.
Simon, you have a visitor.
This is the man I was telling you about.
Hello, Simon.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Dr Carroll...
Would it be possible for me to speak
with Simon alone?
You wouldn't be in any danger,
if that's what you're worried about.
I'd like to talk about his work
and I want him to feel free to open up.
Well, I suppose I could go
grab us some coffees.
Simon, will you be nice to our visitor?
Mr Ingram is a close friend
of the institution.
You're not supposed to be here.
Simon, you heard what Dr Carroll said.
You were supposed to die
in the North Tower.
You know who I am.
- I know that voice.
We searched for it for years.
Then you also know that I'm important
to the program, Simon.
I'm the very first Traveler.
The Director is not happy.
You were supposed to die.
Not anymore.
The Director gave me a new mission.
What mission?
The Director feels terrible
for what happened to you
and wants to fix it.
It sent me to help you.
We're going to make you whole again, Simon.
There are 16 continental switches
on the back channel but only four
that handle subchannel traffic.
Simon helped me set up alerts
to log any suspicious network activity.
So what are we looking at?
This is Vincent communicating
with somebody late last night.
With who?
- We don't know.
What does it say?
We don't know that either.
- So where's it going?
We don't know where it
was sent or received.
Hops are encrypted along the subchannels
as well as both ends of the pipe.
Except for this one.
He's getting a call.
Well, grab it.
It looks like the access point is unsecure.
We might be getting a phone number.
PHONE BUZZES
- TAYLOR CHATTERS
This isn't the last phone I sent you.
Those phones are meant for your safety
as well as mine.
DR PERROW:
I can't find that one.
And this won't take long..
Vincent, you need a more thorough
treatment regimen -
one that at least allows for
the possibility of medication.
No. I don't need drugs,
I just need to talk.
We have an appointment.
- And I'm calling to cancel it.
That is unacceptable.
Vincent, I'm sorry..
I can recommend...
- No.
I don't want to talk with anyone else..
I just want to talk with you.
And I will, just as we agreed.
- Goodbye, Vincent.
Please don't contact me again.
PHONE CLICKS
Call's over.
We got the originating number.
Good. I've gotta get back to the Bureau.
You track down that location.
Everybody else, Protocol 5.
The minute we find out where Vincent
is hiding, we're going to knock down
his fucking door.
Hey, Carly, hold up.
What?
I was thinking maybe you could stay.
For?
Protection?
SIMON CLEARS HIS THROAT
I gotta pee.
I think you got this. Bye, Philip!
Mr Ingram?
Mr Ingram!
I'm so glad I caught you.
I just wanted to thank you
for the personal interest you've taken
in Simon's care.
Oh, I'm happy to help.
- But I'd also like to talk to you about
all the equipment you've
been bringing in...
Surplus electronic parts
from my various companies.
Most of it isn't even functional.
Still, Simon's convinced it'll help
with his "consciousness" issue.
Is that what he's saying now?
Of course, the problem is we have procedure
to follow.
Safety and compliance,
various approval committees...
I understand. These things are expensive
and take time.
Hopefully, this will address
the first problem.
Perhaps you can help me with the second.
This is very generous.
Not at all.
Charity is a gift you give yourself.
Have a nice weekend, Doctor.
Marcy?
In here!
I'm making dinner.
Really?
I just... I've never seen you cook before.
- Well, it's dinner, David.
It's not brain surgery.
It's pasta.
Yeah.
How long's this been on?
Not long enough to boil off the water yet.
There's definitely still water in there.
I had a late lunch, so there's no rush.
You surprise me every time you do that.
ELEVATOR CHIMES
Shit, I'm sorry.
You're avoiding me.
No, I just...
I'm...
- I see it when you look at me.
I remind you of what happened,
and I'm not taking it personally.
But it does convince me that we need this.
Take-out?
This is caponata...
This is moussaka - that's for me...
And this is Mexican, because there are no
Spanish places around here.
Ah...
We just sold our house and you have
a ton of vacation saved, so...
Palermo...
Santorini...
Barcelona.
You need a break, Grant - we both do.
We take off for a couple of months,
spend a ridiculous amount of money
and hit reset on our entire life.
That would be...
incredible.
But you can't imagine leaving work
for that long.
- I know.
Which is why I started thinking
about a different plan.
One that costs just as much and...
will definitely reset
the hell out of everything.
Adoption...?
It's too soon to be
diving in, I know, but...
We could at least start talking about it.
It never would have occurred to me.
Meaning what?
Meaning I think it's a good idea.
Carly.
Carly!
What...? What is this?
Are you drunk?
Yeah, I mean, I had a couple drinks.
What do you want? You want me
to disrespect my boss on his birthday?
OK, Jeffery's sleeping, and you're drunk.
I'm not dealing with this right now.
HE SCOFFS
Oh, you're not dealing right now?
How long are you going to hang this
over my head, Carly?
Come on, I been good and you know it.
Plus, you were the one
that was sleeping around.
OK. Get out.
I'm not going anywhere.
Don't touch me again, Jeff.
Hey, come on. I been good. You owe me.
- Owe you?
Am I gonna get some or what?
Never, Jeff.
Not now, not ever.
SHE GROANS
Stop it.
HE GROANS
OK. OK, OK. OK.
SHE PANTS Stay down.
You shouldn't've done that...
HE GRUNTS
SHE GROANS
HE GROANS
SHE GRUNTS
Stay down!
I said, stay down!
PHILIP: ♪ When you're smiling... ♪
♪ When you're smiling... ♪
Not now!
♪ The whole world smiles with you ♪
♪ When you're laughing, when you're... ♪'
Not now!
Damn it!
BABY CRIES
PHILIP: ♪ The sun comes shining through ♪
♪ And when you're smiling,
the whole world ♪
♪ Smiles with you... ♪
Morning.
Hi.
Were you watching me sleep?
You should try looking
at yourself some time.
SHE CHUCKLES It's hard not to.
You're ridiculous.
I am ridiculous.
I'm glad you stayed.
Well, this place is much cosier
than the place I've been staying, so.
Are you using me for my duvet?
SHE CHUCKLES
I'm sorry it's taken me so long
to find my way back.
Well, to be fair...
I was kinda playing hard to get.
80 help me understand.
How could whatever it was you were doing
make things better?
I mean, even if you can't tell me
the top secret details.
Well, for example, do you remember when we
played the "Operation" game
and you said you were
a better doctor than me?
Because I do.
You do?
- Mm-hmm.
There's a lot of things that I...
I remember...
Most of which I can't tell you, but...
I can tell you that...
I love you.
You have no idea how happy
that makes me.
Do you remember that you owe me $20?
Oh, uh... I'll go get it.
Oh, no, I'm kidding!
HE LAUGHS
I wonder if that pasta's ready.
Probably.
HE LAUGHS
Hey, look, you survived.
Yeah.
He started seeing Vincent
again in the night
but at least I got him to start
wearing pants.
How about you? How are things at home?
I knew it.
Ow!
That wasn't a random call.
What? I was up, I was bored!
Bullshit.
You knew something was going to happen.
How? That's impossible.
- I don't know how, but you knew.
The timing was too perfect.
No, I...
- What was I going to do?
Was I going to go to jail?
Was I going to kill him?
How is Jeff?
He'll live.
Probably won't even remember it.
So what are you going to do?
Hey. You got something?
The phone that called Vincent
was a burner -
paid for in cash, no user info.
But I was able to use its IMEI
along with cell tower data
to find the neighbourhood
that it was last used.
TREVOR: Fancy part of town.
Right, which made this next part easier.
Most people who live in this area
are upstanding citizens
who have actual names
attached to their phones.
Narrow the search to nameless devices...
and our list drops close to zero.
Simon and I spent the night checking
security footage at these locations
and came up with our prime suspect...
Katrina Perrow.
Specialises in treating panic disorders,
social anxiety and agoraphobia.
Text me the address.
Carly, you're with me.
Yup.
VINCENT: You've been given
every resource to make this work!
SIMON: We need more time.
We need to be operating at the exascale,
minimum.
The meteor...
- VINCENT: I told you! I told you...
I keep telling you...
The meteor doesn't happen for years.
Then we find another way, right?
Look, we've got the node clusters,
the math libraries...
We just need a qubit engine
and a field generator...
Where are we going to get that, Simon?
- The Director!
Oh...! This was a mistake.
- No...
I've wasted so much time...
- No, we just need the plans.
No. We're finished here.
- We've hurt so many people!
We hurt Marcy!
Just ask the Director for the materials!
HE YELLS: Ask the Director!
PHILIP: Why didn't the Director
help him?
Afterwards, I mean?
Why did it abandon him?
Probably for the same reason
it sent my consciousness...
Well, yours, too, for that matter -
into a compromised host.
SHE SIGHS It didn't know.
No records from the institution
made it out of the 21st.
Vincent covered his tracks.
SIMON: I want to go home...
What's that?
Can I go home now?
Can I ask about...?
- No.
Dr Perrow?
I'm Special Agent Grant MacLaren
and this is my associate, Carly Shannon.
We'd like to speak to you
about one of your patients.
The FBI has been monitoring
Vincent Ingram for some time.
We know all about his paranoid delusions
and, unfortunately,
he's starting to act on them.
He's hurt someone?
- Yes, and we believe it will continue.
I didn't know. I would have reported it.
None of that matters now.
We're just interested in stopping him.
SHE SIGHS
Our professional relationship deteriorated.
I just called him to cancel an appointment.
We're aware of your phone call.
We want you to keep that appointment.
What?
Why?
Ingram is in hiding.
You want me to keep my appointment
and you're going to follow me?
We have a device.
It's completely untraceable but it will
allow us to be in constant communication.
You mean like a wire?
Little more high-tech than that.
Will you help us?
I just got out of a board meeting
and they told me that
you are withdrawing funding.
I told them that this must be
some kind of mistake.
It's not a mistake.
At least give us more time.
A more gradual reduction
of funds would allow us to-
I'm sorry, I've made my decision.
The institute has come to rely
on your generosity.
Whole programs will be shuttered.
And what about the patients?
A lot of them will be
put out on the street.
Well, then it's fortunate you care so much
and I've been able to compensate you
so well over the years.
You can take my place as a benefactor.
Alright. This should be enough
to last you for a while.
Give us a call when you need more -
you know how to find us.
I'm glad it worked, Marcy.
Glad what worked?
The device in room 210.
I thought you were gone forever,
but then you got better.
Maybe I can get better, too.
Take care of yourself, OK?
PHILIP: OK, the car's approaching now.
Good luck..
Alright, she's leaving the city.
Signal looks good.
TREVOR: Yeah. We see it, too.
Following at a safe distance.
COM BEEPS
CARLY: Dr Perrow,
you activated your cam.
Everything alright?
-  It's fine.
We're right behind you.
All you need to do is lead us there
and we'll do the rest.
It's a fine day out there.
MACLAREN: There it is.
GPS says she's inside.
I was gonna say we need to deactivate
the cameras but I don't see any.
In fact, I don't even think
the barn has any power.
Makes sense if you want to hide
from the Director.
Why do these things
always end up in barns?
Philip, you got Perrow's com?
PHILIP: She 's holding position.
'This is a message for
Agent Grant MacLaren..
'I was acting on Agent MacLaren's behalf'
kin an unsanctioned operation..
I was found out...
and will be released unharmed...
SHE SOBS
k... along with my daughter...
'as long as Agent
MacLaren presents himself'
to these coordinates
in the next two hours..
He must come alone and on time...
or I Will never be heard from again.