Hey.
- Hey.
Thanks for picking me up.
I know you're working.
No problem.
Have you told Walt?
I haven't told anybody.
MAN: Don't. I can't. I can't.
I can't. No. I can't.
I can't.
HE 8083: Don't.
MAN CRIES OUT
Please!
You.
You sick fuck, we're after you.
Please.
GUN FIRES
What?
Hit a snag in the basement.
Pipe leaking water.
Show me.
WATER TRICKLES
Get a sledge.
SLEDGE HAMMER CLUNKS
TENSE MUSIC
INDISTINCT CHATTER OVER POLICE RADIOS
BOYD: Agent Mac Laren.
Alive and well.
Officer Boyd.
I'm very glad to see your vest worked
as advertised.
Yeah, you didn't
have to shoot twice.
Sorry.
Professional instinct.
He's with us now.
- Ah.
4112. What the hell
happened in there?
Exactly what
happened to my team.
Except these four
weren't rescued.
I can't imagine
who'd do something like this.
When I last saw you, you said something
about some faction in the future
that exists now.
The faction's been around for years.
It started as a movement in...
- Shelter 41, I know.
Shelter 41 collapsed.
Not in the future he came from.
Least it was there when I left.
Guys, I think we need to keep Protocol 2
in mind here.
Right. Well, this couldn't be
the work of the faction anyway.
Why not?
You told me, when my team went missing,
that you'd seen
this kind of thing happening
long before I arrived in the 21st.
The faction didn't exist when I left.
I always assumed it was the Director.
There's no way the Director's capable
of what we just saw in there.
Isn't letting it happen just as bad?
When can my team have the scene?
Forensics will be another
few hours at least.
But after that, it's all yours.
Trev?
I don't want you to feel down
on account of this thing taking months.
You shouldn't feel down either, Gary.
I know, I know, but I can't help it.
I mean...
Kid, you used to fly!
If you had pressure in the pocket,
you would just put on those afterburners
and blow right through the defense.
It was a thing to watch.
Must be hard for you.
It is.
It's really hard.
You'll get through it.
I know you will.
Thanks, son.
Hey...
you too.
TREVOR: Know what?
This... This is good right here.
I can walk from here.
Thank you.
HE GROANS
You OK?
Yeah, I got it.
Thanks for the lift, Dad.
PA: Dr Thomson, you're needed in
Radiology 2. Dr Thomson in Radiology 2.
You're up next.
Excellent photography.
Dr Barker. How are you doing today?
Great. You?
Oh, fine, thanks.
Great. That's really, uh...
I should probably...
Oh. Yeah, uh...
Don't... Don't let me get in your way.
I was just gonna ask, uh...
You're busy.
Uh, I'll come by later.
OK. Are you sure?
Yeah. Yeah. I've... I've got a...
But I will definitely...
OK.
- You too.
I mean, uh...
Right this way.
You don't think I would've
told you if we had a mission?
Well, maybe another team got one.
It's been a long time.
- 2163 hours.
Not that I'm counting.
You really are an optimist.
Yeah. Yeah, I really am.
You can quit if you want.
HE EXHALES DEEPLY
HE STRUGGLES Come on.
Five.
HE GASPS AND WHEEZES
Time.
Alright.
We did it!
I just thought you might want a little bit
of human contact.
HE GROANS Oh...
Two minutes recovery and then we go again.
No problem.
FIZZING SOUND
REPORTER: a construction site
in the area of Edmondvi/le.
Four missing persons reports came
to a heart-breaking conclusion today
as a demolition team found their bodies
in an abandoned building.
Out of respect for the families,
police have yet to release any names.
'However, foul play has been assumed..
Adena Moore is at the site now..
Adena, are you able to give us
any details on what happened there?
ADENA: Well, What we are looking at now...
REPORTER FADES OUT
HE SNIFFS
That's the smell of death.
Police forensics came up with nothing.
Your turn.
WATER SPLASHES UNDERFOOT
PHILIP: Trevor and I kind of
just threw this together...
But it should work.
PIERCING WHISTLE
- THEY GROAN
Sorry! Set too high.
We're good.
Hey! I got a com over here.
Get out of the building now!
Go.
Go!
Go. Go, go! Go!
GUN FIRES
EXPLOSION ROARS
SHE SIGHS DEEPLY
Morning.
Mm. Smells delicious.
You never cooked this much
when we were together before.
You just never liked my cooking.
Oh, you're definitely a better cook, but...
it's like you're a different person now.
Nope. Same guy.
On the outside, maybe.
Yeah, and on the inside,
nougat and caramel.
SHE LAUGHS
Otherwise, I am the same guy
you broke up with.
I didn't know what I had, David.
Same guy.
Hey! I'm trying to give you
a compliment here, OK?
You're... You're more confident.
I used to be able to read you, but...
it feels like there's so much more going on
in there now.
It's mysterious.
HE SCOFFS QUIETLY
You don't know mysterious.
You know, there's an ingredient in
these eggs that's gonna blow your mind.
SHE GASPS IN PAIN
You OK?
Yeah, I'll be fine. It'll... It'll pass.
Blair, this keeps happening.
Let's get you in to see a doctor.
I'm fine. Really.
SHE GASPS: Ah!
- OK, that's enough. Let's go.
Hey, Carly?
It's hard for me to focus with you pacing
around with a gun in your hand.
CARLY: Sorry.
TREVOR: It's OK.
PHILIP: So judging by the T.E.L.L
of these four host candidates
I think I've figured
out who our group was.
A team of five, just like us.
Which leaves one member unaccounted for.
PHILIP: Traveler 2192.
Let's find them.
- TREVOR: If they're still alive.
I think I can narrow it down by checking
which candidates didn't die
the day 2192 arrived.
TREVOR: This com isn't telling me much,
other than it's been all over the place.
Get that com working.
Look, I'm sorry, but we've already
contacted all of the victims' families.
But Jacob went missing at the same time
as those other people.
I mean, isn't it possible that
there were more victims?
No, there were only four found
at that location
and none of them were named Jacob, ma'am.
- Beth, Beth...
I am sorry.
- Let me talk to her.
If you say so.
Special Agent Grant MacLaren.
Come on in here. We'll talk privately.
Thank you.
Have a seat, Mrs...?
Ward. Sylvie.
You say your husband's been
missing for some time?
Three and a half months.
That... That is a long time.
The police haven't been able
to find anything.
I don't even think they're looking anymore.
What can you tell me about him?
Jacob's wonderful.
I mean, we had our troubles
through the years
but lately, the last year and a half
or so, our marriage has never been better.
What changed?
Before, he was loud, he smoked like a
fiend, he wasn't health-conscious at all.
But I always knew that he would come around
and he did.
Almost overnight,
his priorities completely realigned.
He became more attentive, compassionate...
Did you ever see him in the company of
any of the other victims?
He didn't run away with another woman
if that's what you're thinking.
- That's not what I'm thinking.
I'm just wondering if there's a connection.
Say, in the workplace?
No. Jacob didn't believe in
bringing his work home with him.
He said that was our time.
And you've had no communication
with your husband's cell phone?
Any activity in his bank accounts?
- No. Nothing.
But I believe that he is still alive,
Agent MacLaren.
I have to.
TREVOR: Didn't you just take some of that?
She said to take it as needed.
And I need to focus.
Does Marcy know what's in this?
It's Marcy-approved.
Let's get back to work.
You guys there?
PHILIP: Yeah, boss, What's up?
I got a name on our fifth traveler.
Jacob Ward.
We're on it.
Philip, I want you to put a
tap on his wife '3 cell phone.
Sylvie Ward
She just paid me a visit.
I'll text you the address.
Will do, boss.
Shit!
I gotta go.
JEFF: I'm sure Carly will be here
any minute now.
Her new job's...
been a little crazy.
In the meantime, how are you doing?
Fine.
JEFF CLEARS HIS THROAT
Lot of change in your life.
How's it going?
Ah, it's all good.
Just living through the changes.
When Carly's here,
I sometimes get the impression
that you're going out of your way
to agree with her.
Might be useful to use this time,
while we have it, to talk about you.
JEFF CLEARS HIS THROAT
Yeah, I can do that.
OK.
Do that.
How much do you know about guilt?
Hi! I am so sorry I'm late!
Hey... there she is!
Traffic was just...
SHE SIGHS
Well, you're here now.
Yes.
Big week for you two.
Your final custody assessment from CPS.
How are the two of you feeling?
Good.
Yeah, it's really good.
- Really good.
That's good.
Marcel
Hi!
I've been looking everywhere for you.
Uh, is everything alright?
Yeah.
Everything's fine.
No. Urn...
I got back together with... with Blair.
And, um...
Good for you.
- HE SCOFFS: Right.
I wasn't looking for you
to tell you that, but, uh...
I think there might be something
wrong with her.
Uh, well, did you take her to Admitting?
Yeah, see, that was the original plan
but then I learnt that
she didn't have insurance.
Um... But she's been having these harsh
stomach pains
for over a week now and I'm worried that
if she doesn't get it looked at-
David, I... I'm just an X-ray technician.
I think we both know that's not true.
Besides, I think an X-ray's
exactly what she does need.
Alright. Uh...
Bring her to Imaging in block C.
Thank you.
You two are really gonna hit it off.
PHILIP: Hey, boss.
- Hey. What have you got?
You were right.
Our man, Jacob,
is definitely our missing Traveler.
He went off the grid sometime mid-May. If
he's still out there, he's good at hiding.
Any action on the wife's cell?
There's already a tap on her line.
Someone else is watching her besides us.
Trevor, you got that com working yet?
Ready when you are.
Hello?
This is Traveler 3468.
2192, are you there?
CRACKLY VOICE:
How did you get on this channel?
STATIC NOISE
I'm sure you've heard by now,
the rest of your team is dead.
We found this com at the crime scene.
We want to help.
Is your mission from the Director
to assist me?
No. But my team was captured,
same as yours.
I think it's important that...
- Then stand down!
Do you have a tap
on your wife's cell phone?
What?'?
Someone besides us is tracking your wife.
Is it you?
[JACOB GROANS AND CRIES OUT IN PAIN]
Jacob?
- JACOB GRUNTS
He's still there.
The signal's still strong.
He's cutting out his com.
JACOB PANTS AND GROANS
Do not remove your com! Jacob!
Your wife is in trouble!
She's...
- JACOB CRIES OUT
STATIC CRACKLES
SILENCE
We lost him.
HE SIGHS
OK.
Keep monitoring her phone.
I think I know where he's going.
Hi.
You found something, didn't you?
Uh...
The scans did show a foreign mass
in her stomach.
Oh, God, here we go.
I'm afraid to even guess at what that...
You don't have to.
It's cotton balls.
Cotton balls?
How could she possibly have ingested-
It's a weight-loss thing.
It's supposed to make you feel fuller.
I don't know.
David, I don't think that
you realise how...
I know.
Not to mention unbelievably dangerous.
I mean, she's lucky she didn't eat enough
to cause an obstruction.
Yeah, that's what happened last time.
Alright. Uh...
SHE SIGHS
We'll get her stomach pumped
and she'll be on her way
but you cannot let her-
I know, I know.
I know.
I'll talk to her.
Um...
HE SCOFFS
Thank you.
You're welcome.
KNOCKING
Agent MacLaren. Is there news?
Actually, I was hoping Jacob
had contacted you.
Contacted? I haven't heard a thing.
Mind if I come in?
- Is everything alright?
I hope so.
I just have a few more questions.
I just... I'm late for an appointment.
Maybe I could drop by your office later?
How did you break this?
I told you to leave me alone!
- Jacob! I'm here to help you!
JACOB: No!
- Jacob!
He's running! Back stairs!
Jacob!
WOMAN SHRIEKS
You alright?
THEY BOTH GRUNT
Stop it!
I'm Traveler 3465.
We're here to help you.
And you're making that
awfully goddamn difficult.
You people have no idea
what you're getting yourselves into!
Traveler teams from all over the world
are being abducted and tortured.
We know.
The Director assigned us to investigate
their disappearances
but they found us before we could...
GUNSHOT
- JACOB GASPS IN PAIN
JACOB GASPS FOR AIR
It's bad.
Marcy, drop what you're doing.
Get back to Ops.
We got a patient.
Keep your eyes open.
We're getting you to our medic.
Call Sylvie.
You need to tell us what you know.
What did your team find out?
Who's behind this?
Whoever it is, they covered their tracks.
We do know that the buildings...
Every one Travelers were taken to
all... all around the world...
HE SPUTTERS
What about the buildings?
They're owned by numbered companies.
Sh... Sh... Shells...
But under one conglomerate.
- Give us a name, Jacob!
HE SPUTTERS AND GASPS
Jacob! Jacob!
His lung's collapsed.
We need to re-inflate it.
Carly?
MONITOR BEEPS RAPIDLY
We need to shock.
Charge?
- Mm-hmm.
Clear.
Charge again.
MONITOR FLATLINES
He's gone.
PHONE RINGS
Hello?
'GRANT: Hey, it's me..
What a total surprise.
Funny.
Hey, before I drop by tonight,
you want me to stop at the grocery store
and pick up anything special,
craving-wise?
Oh...
Um...
SHE GASPS
Yes! Some kind of smoked meat.
Meat...?
I need the iron!
What's the smoke for?
SHE CHUCKLES
Nobody craves broccoli, Grant.
You're the one who offered.
- CAR PHONE RINGS
Kat, someone's on the other line.
I'll call you back.
Mhm. OK.
MacLaren.
OK, so, the sole owner
of the company that
owns that building
is Vincent Ingram.
He's got an estate
about a half-hour from downtown.
I let one of his people know
that you're on your way.
OK, great. Thanks, Beth.
Text me the address.
Just did.
TREVOR: Hi.
PHILIP: Have you seen my eye drops?
Nope.
I just got here.
You were the last person who had them
yesterday when we were working.
I didn't take your drops, Philip. Relax.
What's that supposed to mean?
Uh... look around.
Just give them back.
What's going on, man?
- I know you're trying to monitor me.
I can take care of myself.
So just back off
and give me back my drops.
Here.
TREVOR CLEARS HIS THROAT
Jeez.
It's a good thing these are helping
with your addiction, huh?
Jeez...
PHONE DIALS
ANSWER MACHINE:
Hey, this is Marcy. Leave a message.
BEEP
Hey, Marce... y.
Uh, I just wanted to say thanks again
for your help with Blair.
Uh, I really appreciate it,
and she's doing better, so...
Um...
Anyway, I was hoping you could, uh...
you could join me...
me and Blair, for dinner tonight
as a way to say thank you.
Uh, so if you're free,
that would be great...
to see you.
I know I just saw you,
but it would be...
it'd be great to see you again.
I do, like, a fish dish now.
Uh, branzini.
I know you like white fish
and all those Omega 33.
No cotton balls, I promise.
Anyway, uh...
All this to say, I hope you can join me.
Us.
I mean, because Blair will be there, too.
HE LAUGHS AWKWARDLY And you...
I hope.
Oh, for God's sakes.
HE SIGHS
But we've grown up a lot.
And Carly's an amazing woman
and I'm thankful every day
that she's a part of my life.
How's your landscaping job going?
Still great.
I see that neither of you
have missed a session with your counsellor.
How have they been going?
Very helpful.
- Good, yeah. Very.
JACQUELINE: Tell me how.
Well, I was...
angry.
And hurt.
But, by talking things through,
we found out that we were both angry.
We just didn't have as much to be mad about
as we thought we did.
The counselling has helped me forgive Jeff.
And to not let the past stop me
from seeing who he is now.
SHE GIGGLES
I have to admit, you're doing very well
at keeping up the act.
Oh, please.
I've been doing this along time.
You can't fool me.
Jacqueline...
But it's not necessarily a bad thing.
It means you want to try.
Most marriages include at least a
little bit of faking it, trust me.
I can see how much this means
to the both of you
and how committed you are.
You may not ever
be great spouses, but...
I think you could be good parents.
Special Agent Grant MacLaren.
My office called.
HE CLEARS HIS THROAT
I apologise for the conditions of entry
into my house.
Please, don't take it personally.
That's alright, Mr Ingram.
Special Agent Grant MacLaren.
Have we ever met, Agent MacLaren?
Well, I usually remember the people
who decline to shake my hand.
How do you close your business deals?
Through a legal representative.
And a large transfer of money.
I'm investigating the four bodies
that were found in the basement
of the building at 46 Henderson Avenue.
Why are you speaking to me?
One of your companies
owns the property.
I suppose, on paper,
that's technically true
though I think the company that leased it
from me would be better able to provide you
with the day-to-day operations.
Have you spoken to them?
Not yet.
If an employee of a Microsoft store
was involved in a criminal act,
even a serious one, would most
FBI agents think to question Bill Gates?
The four victims were tortured extensively
and over an extended period of time
so I hope you won't take it personally
if I'm being thorough.
Well, I don't know how much use I can be.
I've never seen the building
or stepped foot inside
and I operate all my business remotely.
I never leave this house.
Never?
My therapist encourages me to be blunt.
I'm agoraphobic, germophobic
and I don't like personal contact.
Well, I'm very sorry
that I have to be here.
You don't.
You're naturally curious about
the wealthy recluse
and your badge gets you in my door.
That is blunt.
Please, ask your question
and get this over with.
You founded one of the leading
digital security firms.
I am curious why you're so strict
about outside electronics in your home?
Well, despite the best precautions,
Agent MacLaren, privacy is an illusion.
With cameras and microphones
built into every personal device...
My therapist says I'm paranoid
but I think it's human nature
for us to do anything
to protect ourselves and our families.
TAYLOR: Dad?
I'm just finishing up a meeting.
Go... Put your coat on.
I'll be out there shortly.
HE SIGHS
I try to reserve a couple of hours
every day to play with my son.
Do you have children?
No.
Well, I'm sure there's still time
for you and your wife.
I remember now!
We met five years ago at a charity event.
It was before my condition
became so debilitating.
You were there with your wife...
Kathryn.
Sorry... Didn't recognise you.
A stunning woman, if I remember it.
This dark hair,
and a wonderful dance partner.
In your shoes,
I would never have let a single soul
steal a dance from her.
Please send her my regards.
That is, if our business is concluded.
It is.
For now. Thanks for your time.
Happy hunting.
MACLAREN: The event would've been
five years ago.
Liberty Banquet Hall.
Looks fancy.
I have no idea, but I'd
be on the guest list.
"MacLaren plus guest."
That's you.
Yeah.
OK. Look for Vincent Ingram.
There's no sign he was there.
Doesn't mean he wasn't.
Can you hack into his private server?
You know it.
How you doing? What's that? What's that?
CORK POPS
Jeff!
We did it.
We deserve to celebrate. You...
deserve...
to celebrate.
You made a promise.
A couple hours ago, we didn't know
if we were ever gonna see our son again.
Come on, I'm just trying to say thank you.
JEFF LAUGHS
Hey, big boy!
Come here. Come here.
HE LAUGHS
I missed you.
JEFFREY CRIES
PHILIP: Redundancy number six?
That's just excessive.
Just try again.
TREVOR: The Director didn't order us
to investigate this guy.
We're breaking Protocol 5 by doing this.
As far as I'm concerned,
this falls under Protocol 1.
The mission comes first.
The whole grand plan's in jeopardy
if we can't stop teams from being taken!
Now, maybe this guy didn't pull the trigger
but if he's involved in any way-
PHILIP: He froze me out.
That's redundancy number seven.
I thought you said you could do this!
There's a reason why he's the best
in the 21st.
Shouldn't you be the best,
considering the century you come from?
Hey, look.
Yelling at it worked.
Oh, my God.
KNOCKING ON DOOR
Wow.
You look...
I can't even finish my sentence.
That seems to be going around.
Hi.
- Hi.
Uh, Blair just texted
and she's running a little late
but the fish is ready, so if you want
to eat, we could eat.
Uh, let's wait.
Yeah, you know, we probably should.
Um... I wasn't, uh...
I wasn't sure if
you were actually gonna come.
Well, you invited me.
How's your therapy been going?
No more panic attacks.
HE CHUCKLES
I still find it hard to fall asleep
when I'm in bed with Blair, but...
You know, I didn't mean it like that.
You know, like we don't - we do,
but just, you know...
you know, not excessively,
just a normal frequency.
Not like...
What was I talking about?
How you can't sleep.
Right!
Uh, she snores.
Hey, would you do something for me?
Anything.
Tell me about me.
Like, things you don't remember, or...?
Okay, um...
HE CHUCKLES
I used to call you Batgirl.
From you running off
at all hours, fighting crime.
Uh...
You liked listening to country music.
Which country?
No, it's a...
It's a genre.
Um, you liked honey in your tea, but not-
No, I mean, uh, what I was like.
Oh. OK.
Um...
Stubborn.
HE CHUCKLES
You drove me crazy sometimes,
I'm not gonna lie to you.
Uh... fierce.
Little yell-y, now and then.
Generally... amazing.
I'm not really sure that's what I'm asking.
Um...
I'm just trying to find the missing pieces.
All I can tell you is what you did to me.
How I felt...
whenever you would walk
through the door...
Every time.
Like butterflies, you know?
That feeling in your stomach.
Even more so when you would go out again.
Someone like you...
does not happen to someone like me.
And I know that doesn't
answer your question
and I know that you're just trying to
remember the missing pieces, but...
maybe someone is best defined
by how they affect the people around them.
I think I just made that up,
but I think it may be true.
DOOR OPENS
Hey, guys.
Um, I'm so sorry I'm late.
That's okay. We were just, uh...
GRANT: Marcy, Carly...
I need you back at Ops, right now.
Um, actually I have to go,
something just came up.
Oh. No, really?
You don't need to...
I do.
Um, thank you for the wine.
Bye.
PHILIP: There's a file for each of us.
CARLY: I can't believe we found him.
Open mine.
We take him tonight.
Before another Traveler dies.
You're fucking right we do.
Let's gear up.
OK, we go in quiet and fast.
Kill him and we get out.
Boss, I don't agree with this.
Yeah? Well, we're gonna need you.
How about you, Philip?
Oh, I'm in.
Alright, there are four
armed guards outside.
Here, here, here, and here.
I don't know how many staff inside.
CARLY: Alright.
Let's park behind this tree line
and proceed on foot.
TAYLOR: And, after lunch,
Miss Henry let me read
From The Chrysalids“.
She said I had a very
impressive vocabulary.
Go get it!
Good for you.
Come on. Come on, boy.
DOG BARKS
DOORS CLANG SHUT
BANGING ON THE DOOR
VINCENT: Taylor?
- Good boy. Come on.
Taylor!
Not so far. Not so far!
Come on.
ROBOTIC: Traveler 001.
ROBOTIC: Traveler 3468,
you are off-mission.
Stop your pursuit of Traveler 3468
and his team immediately.
- Stand down immediately
or face repercussions.
ROBOTIC WHIZZING
CHILDLIKE: Where's my mum?
Dad? What's wrong?
Come back inside.
Quickly. Quickly!
It's alright, sweetheart.
I'm a policeman.
Boss?
- PHILIP: What do we do?
Taylor and I are leaving tonight.
We won't be returning.
Stand down.
What?
The Director must have a reason.
The Director's the one
who wanted him found!
We found him! Let's finish it!
It's not our mission.
Not tonight.
Come on, sweetheart. Let's get you home.
Come on.
Do you know your address?