[phone buzzes, chimes]
We're being followed. Lose them.
- Faster! We have to...
- [car screeching]
[car crashes, glass shatters]
[heart monitor beeping]
- [Mori] How is she?
- [nurse] Vitals are stable for now.
But the pressure remains high.
- Still no ID?
- No. Nothing.
Not even on the driver. He didn't make it.
Hopefully her family will realize
she's missing and start calling around.
Okay. We'll see what comes back
on the MRI and EEG,
but it looks like we'll have to relieve
some of the cranial pressure
with or without her next of kin
permission.
- I'll double check with the desk.
- All right, thank you.
[theme music playing]
Mm. Hey.
Every time.
What?
Every time I see you walking towards me
I think to myself,
"My God, what is that beautiful woman
doing in my apartment?"
Ah-ah!
Apparently saving you
from salmonella poisoning.
Oh, no. A lot of people say
there's more nutrients this way.
- Yeah. Well, a lot of people are dumb.
- [both chuckling]
- Well, I could have cooked that.
- Let's just start again.
Okay. So?
What's the plan for today?
Um. I'm not sure yet.
Not sure or can't tell me?
Not even a little hint?
David, it's the same as every other day.
I might have a mission.
But if you don't hear from me,
don't expect me home until late. Okay?
Yeah. I was just curious.
[egg cracks]
- [Marcy] How about your day?
- Um, you know, same old...
Same... Okay. You know what?
I'm gonna show you how to do this
without getting half the shell in here,
you're killing me.
- [stammers] What?
- This is an actual choking hazard.
Uh...
[beeps]
- He's alive!
- Another exciting day in the 21st.
Every day is a gift, Philip.
Says the man who has received
the most gifts.
And I don't take a single one for granted.
- [computer beeping]
- Oh, shit.
Boss, you there?
- [beeps]
- Yeah, what's up?
The deep web is blowing up
with a missing persons alert.
Teams all around us are searching.
- A missing Traveler?
- [Philip] Not just any Traveler.
The Director calculated
an 88 percent probability that an EEG
taken out an accident victim yesterday
belongs to Traveler 001.
Well, that's got to be a mistake.
He was overwritten by the Director.
All we know for sure
is that a new consciousness was sent
into the host body.
[stammers] You're saying 001
was already gone at that point?
It's the only explanation.
- How?
- [Trevor] Don't know, boss.
But an EEG is kinda like a fingerprint.
The Director would recognize it.
[Philip] The patient was brought in
to Coastal Cross as a Jane Doe.
Where is she now?
Well, if it's really 001,
he was taken out of his room
before the test results came back.
Shit.
Okay, stay on it.
I'll go to the hospital,
I'll let you know what I find out.
I just don't know
how much more I've got left.
Trust is a limited resource with me.
[Travis] I think that's true
for all of us.
And once it's gone, it's gone.
I just can't...
- Remember, building walls prevents...
- Prevents growth. I know, I know.
We're hard wired
to protect ourselves, Kathryn.
It's a survival instinct.
People aren't supposed
to fantasize their husbands are evil.
Well, anxiety manifests itself
in strange ways.
Though, I do find it interesting
you're fantasizing
about confronting your husband
rather than just doing it.
Just the idea of that scares me.
What's he gonna do?
If you have something to say, say it.
I want you to try something for me.
I want you to say something
three or four times in a row.
However you like.
Don't think, just feel how it feels
and hear what it sounds like
when you say it, okay?
- Okay.
I want you to say,
"I am not afraid of my husband."
[inhales, exhales]
I am not...
[Jeff knocking on door] Hey!
[knocking continues]
I know you're in there!
[gun clicks]
Hey!
What do you want?
I just wanna have a conversation.
We don't have anything to talk about.
How about we talk about
what you did with Carly?
- I'm right here.
- Bullshit.
Who the fuck are you?
- Go, Jeff! Last warning.
- Warning?
You kicked my ass
when I was piss drunk,
- but not this time...
- [gun cocks]
Leave.
I guess we'll do this another time.
[exhales]
[sniffs]
[coughs]
[touch tones beep]
Hey?
Yes.
Same place? Okay, great.
I can come now.
Thanks.
- [phone beeps]
- Who was that on the phone?
- I have to get some medication.
- Medication.
For the update. Which you're also
not supposed to know about.
It's Director approved.
Okay.
My relapse was a one-time thing.
Cool.
You got to trust me,
I've got it under control.
I never said you didn't.
Cool.
- But I'm still coming with you.
- You don't have to do that.
Yeah, I do. Come on. Let's go!
[door opens]
I'll come back for it.
Fuck, shit. Shit.
Jordan. Hi.
Whoa. What's wrong? Everything okay?
I lost your bike, man.
You lost it, huh?
Uh, okay, well, let's, um...
let's go look for it.
No.
I mean, the Murray Park guys
showed up, and...
And they stole it.
Okay. Uh...
Don't worry about it. You know,
I'm just glad you're okay.
I'm not okay, though. I loved that bike.
Yeah, I loved it, too.
So we're gonna go get it back.
[woman over PA] Maintenance to Floor 3.
Maintenance to Floor 3.
[MacLaren clears his throat]
Doctor Mori.
Special Agent Grant MacLaren of the FBI.
[Mori] Yes?
You had a Jane Doe
come through here last night?
We did, yeah. Car accident.
Do you know who...
I was hoping you could tell me
what you know. Anything is helpful.
Oh, um...
Yeah. She was probably in her 40s.
Uh, five-foot-eight. Blonde.
Very expensive suit.
Hard to say much else.
She sustained serious trauma to the head.
We were just beginning treatment,
and she disappeared.
- Could she have walked out of here?
- No. Not a chance.
We had her in a chemically induced coma
due to her head injury.
I came back to check on her,
she was just gone.
Who do I speak to have a security footage?
Oh, oh. No offense, Agent,
but it's not every day I have a patient
in that condition just up and disappear.
I went and checked the tapes myself,
but apparently the whole system
froze last night for some reason
and didn't get a thing.
Hmm.
- Mind if I look around anyway?
- No. Be my guest.
Let me know
if you find out anything.
- Of course
- Okay.
[phone buzzes]
- [Dawn] Where are we at?
- [Michelle] Not good.
Brain hemorrhage.
Blood pressure's high and rising.
Okay. What can we do about that?
Right now, all I can do
is monitor his host body.
I need you to do something.
Without more information
there's not much I can do.
We need a CT scan, an MRI...
Michelle, he's of no use to us
in this state.
Then maybe we shouldn't have
chased him down
and caused a fucking car accident.
Sorry.
Keep me posted.
[footsteps depart]
- [gasps]
- Wait.
Who are you?
My name is Dawn.
And it's an honor to be here with you.
[sighs]
[car door opens]
Nice part of town
the Director sent you to.
Yeah, well, we live in a garage, so...
[David] Hey, guys.
I haven't swung by in a while to check-in.
Everyone good? Need anything?
Nobody. No?
No, man. We're good.
Good.
All right. Awesome.
I'm good, too, thanks for asking.
That's my bike.
I, uh, I gave it to a friend
and you stole it,
so I'm gonna need it back.
- This bike?
- [David] That bike.
No, man. You're confused.
I've had this bike for years.
- [David laughing] Years?
- [Mikey] Yeah.
My mom gave it to me for my birthday.
- Yeah? When's your birthday?
- October 24th.
Well, that doesn't prove anything,
everyone knows when their birthday is.
I'm just gonna need that bike back.
Or what?
[scoffs]
[Mikey grunts]
Jesus! Oh, that was your cue
to hit the ground, by the way.
- [David groans]
- You're fucking dead.
[David grunts, groans]
[grunting]
[Philip] Where you going, huh?
I know you guys.
[Trevor] Yep, that's us!
You okay?
They stole my bike, so I was just...
I was gonna...
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I think so.
God, I'm lucky you guys
were just passing by.
Yeah. Lucky.
That was awesome.
It's like stuff you see in the movies.
[pants] You should get
your head checked out.
Yeah. 'Cause you could have a concussion.
- It feels nasty, is it bad?
- [Philip] Uh...
Show it to Marcy. We gotta go.
Okay.
- Hey, thanks guys.
- [Trevor] Take care, David.
[Trevor] Better?
[Philip] Sure.
- What? You trust me now?
- I always trusted you.
[MacLaren over comms]
You guys there?
- [beeps]
- Yeah, boss.
What's happening on the deep web?
Any updates?
Uh. We had to step out for a thing.
What thing?
[Trevor] It's done,
we're on our way back now.
This is 001 we're talking about.
Uh. Learn anything at the hospital?
Nothing. [sighs]
Starting to think...
Traveler 3468, take immediate action
to provide Internet access
for the Ilsa A.I. at Filmore Laboratories.
Are you looking for your parents?
[woman] Cameron, get over here!
We just got a messenger.
- Everybody back at OPS immediately.
- [engine starts]
We're on our way.
Copy that.
I'll be right there.
[glass shatters]
- [David] Told you I'd get it back.
- [Jordan] How?
Uh, well, I asked nicely.
You get whacked in the head?
It's nothing.
You should see the other guy. [chuckles]
But listen, do me a favor.
Uh, keep your distance
from Murray Park for a while.
Those guys. They're not...
They're not happy.
I got you, man. Thank you, thank you.
- No problem.
- [chuckles]
[sighs]
- [Dawn] Please eat something.
- What do you want from me?
For now, we need you healthy.
But soon we'll need your help.
And why would I help you?
We represent a group of people
known hundreds of years from now
as the Faction.
We've lost contact with the future
and now we're running out of resources.
Ah. You need money.
That's all this is.
There's so much more to this than that.
[groans]
[panting]
- [Dawn] Are you in pain?
- [Perrow] Yes.
- Here.
- [exhales]
Take this.
Here.
[exhales]
[grunts]
I'll be right back.
The headache's becoming more severe
and he's getting weaker.
He hardly seems injured.
That's the difficulty
with internal injuries and brain trauma.
I'm telling you,
without surgical intervention
he's not gonna last a day.
We can't risk the exposure
to the Director.
We have to find him a new host.
- You know what we'll be inviting.
- But he'll survive.
We need the consciousness
transfer device.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Go on.
We won't stop you.
- [beeps]
- [groans]
[device beeping]
[engine starts]
- You know what I just did.
- [Michelle] Activated your failsafe.
They're coming for you now.
It's the only way to save you
and that is more important than anything.
Female, 40s, blonde hair.
I wonder who in 001's custody
fits that description.
- Perrow.
- What?
He jumped?
Uh, that would mean that 001
has consciousness transfer technology.
[Trevor] His companies could have
manufactured the key components.
Simon could've done the work.
He helped build the first one.
So kidnapping people close to us
was just a smoke screen.
- And the Director fell for it.
- [MacLaren] So did we.
I'm using FBI resources to locate Perrow,
but if he's capable
of consciousness transfer...
001 could be anyone by now.
Traveler teams have been searching
since the alert went out
on the backchannel,
but when you consider
the sheer amount of potential candidates...
Oh, hopefully through Ilsa,
the Director can shorten the list.
How do we get access?
I called. They're expecting us.
[Philip] Do we need a cover?
I'm going with FBI agents.
I suggest you guys be specialists.
Pretty sure the real FBI
won't like that idea.
No, but I have a plan.
- [door opens]
- Okay, I'm here, we can go.
That's your plan?
How about you just make sure
you have everything you need first.
Trev, get everything on the list
I texted you?
Yep.
- Trev?
- Yep.
Then we're good to go.
Okay, team, let's move out!
She's really eager
to talk to the Director.
- Yeah. I can see that.
- [door closes]
- [Grace] I'll be in the car!
- Okay!
[clears throat]
Ow. Ugh.
Hey, Marce, it's me.
I was just wondering
when you were...
[inhales, exhales]
[vomiting, coughing]
Oh, God.
Oh, my God!
I just vomited in a voicemail.
That is disgusting, I am so sorry. Um...
Where was I?
Um. I was calling... I wanted to tell you
that I think I have a concussion
because I have all the symptoms.
Nausea being one of them. [pants]
So obviously I Googled concussion
on my phone
and I know I tend to instantly
take on the symptoms
of anything I look up online,
but this time, I...
I can promise you that it's not
all in my head, because it is.
I mean, that's where
concussions happen, right?
So where else would it be?
Anyhoodle, uh,
I got conked in the head pretty hard
and I could use your advice.
Oh, this is... This is David.
[keyboard clacking]
- Agent MacLaren?
- Dr. Teslia. It's a pleasure to meet you.
I... thought you'd be coming alone.
[Marcy] We're specialists.
[Carly] We'd like to set up
as soon as possible.
So this is Ilsa.
Stop!
You called her?
- What the fuck are you doing here?
- Nice to see you, partner.
The Director needs access
to the Internet...
That is not approved.
- We're on orders from the Director...
- Step back!
Boss?
Do what she asks, guys.
- Look. Jo.
- No. Don't "Jo" me.
You're not getting anywhere near Ilsa.
We both know it isn't Ilsa
we need to talk to.
Our agreement
with 21st century authorities
includes access to the Director.
[Yates] Supervised approved access.
[MacLaren]
Oh. That's a matter of interpretation.
[Yates] Not by flashing
your bogus badge to security
like you're an actual FBI agent.
The badge is a hundred percent real.
The computer is isolated
from the world for a reason.
[MacLaren]
Did I mention the future's at stake?
[Yates] No. Actually, you didn't mention
a goddamn thing.
- [MacLaren] What was I supposed to say?
- You're supposed to run things by me.
- That's how this is supposed to work.
- [computer beeping]
[MacLaren] Oh, full disclosure,
the Director is trying to find someone
and needs access to the web
in order to do it.
- Who?
- [scoffs]
[Philip]
He's kinda our public enemy number one.
We have other resources for that.
- [computer beeping]
- [Trevor] Not nearly as advanced.
[muffled] That's not even the point,
you're supposed to be cooperating with me.
- [indistinct conversation]
- [machine beeping]
[keyboard clacking]
[indistinct conversation continues]
It is programmed
to take care of humanity, not harm it...
Yeah. But Ilsa is still
an emerging intelligence.
We can't risk exposing her
to everything that's out there online.
- I understand that, but...
- No. No, you don't understand.
And you don't take no for an answer.
[Yates] I'm getting a little tired of it.
Okay.
Okay, what?
I'm taking no for an answer.
What about our orders?
We've also been ordered to cooperate.
We'll just have to find the information
we need some other way.
Thank you.
Could I possibly just talk to the Director
for a few seconds?
No.
Fine.
We're done here.
[door opens]
[phone chimes]
[beeps]
[tablet chimes]
[keyboard clacking]
- We were right. He's in Perrow.
- That was fast.
Seriously?
I thought the modulated LED connection
between the server bank
and Ilsa was taking forever.
His accounts, numbered companies,
everything. It's all here.
[Philip] In Perrow's name,
he planned the whole thing.
He even made Perrow guardian of his kid.
[sighs] Sick.
So, we know where Perrow is?
The Director shows Traveler 001
in a warehouse just outside of town.
Then we take him now.
[engines starting]
I have to admit, this is getting exciting.
There's no Uber out here!
Shit.
[GPS beeping]
Hi, this is Kat. Leave a message
and I'll get right back to you.
[voicemail beeps]
Kathryn, it's Jeff Conniker.
Sorry I didn't make it over
to the coffee shop. Some shit went down.
[burps]
But we still need to get together.
You, me, David.
I just left him a voicemail, too.
The thing is...
I'm remembering shit.
Carly isn't Carly anymore.
And I don't think your husband is either.
Anyway, call me back when you get this.
[phone beeps]
[engine starts]
My son and my host's daughter
were moving to a new secure location.
They'll be worried.
Mr. Morraca will take care of them
until you're ready to see them again.
Like I said, there isn't much
about you we don't know.
Where are you planning to take me?
We're just preparing you
for the transfer when they arrive.
My people have standing orders
to kill you.
Hopefully, they'll realize that we're
on the same side before that happens.
They won't believe you.
I'm not sure I do.
Obviously, this was not the plan.
I'm not offering an apology.
More of... an explanation.
You weren't supposed to find out
for years.
In the future you come from,
Shelter 41 collapsed. Thousands died.
But the future we come from is different.
I know all of this.
Because you questioned Traveler teams
that were pursuing you.
What a Traveler would never tell you
is that the citizens of Shelter 41
became the center of a movement.
A place where human life
and decision-making was valued
over the artificial intelligence
that controlled every aspect of our lives.
The Director.
It considered our movement nothing more
than a subversive "faction"
within what it considered
a harmonious whole.
The faction became a rebellion.
A rebellion that became a war...
led by you, sir.
Not possible.
I promise you, it is.
I'm a witness to it.
I have sworn my loyalty to you
in my time, and I do now.
Then why risk telling me any of this?
I would never have approved.
Very true.
You forbade contact of any kind
before we came.
Then why?
We're desperate.
The Director still holds power
over the 21st.
Thousands of us came through the frame,
but it still finds us.
Every day, Traveler teams
are tasked to seek us out.
The moment we're discovered,
we die by messenger.
You need to hide.
We can't both hide
and fight for our future.
We still wanna save humanity.
We have no historians, no finances,
no engineers building devices
and components in secret.
But we have you.
As a prisoner.
As our leader.
Your host body is dying.
We've activated your beacon
and summoned your men
in order to save your life.
We only hope
that you will spare ours in return.
[exhales]
[tires screeching]
[engine revving]
- [MacLaren] Oh, Christ.
- [horn honking]
- [honking continues]
- You've got to be kidding me.
- [beeps]
- Boss, we got an issue.
We don't have time for this.
- [tires screeching]
- Shit.
[gun clicks]
[car door closes]
[Carly] You're gonna die now, Jeff.
Me? I don't think so.
Unless you get back in that car,
drive away,
and never show your face again,
you will die today.
I remember now, Carly.
- It doesn't matter.
- [Jeff] Everything.
The abduction. Your confession. All of it!
I know what you are!
- What all of you are!
- [MacLaren] Drop the gun, Jeff.
Gonna get your boyfriend
to shoot me in the back now?
He's not my boyfriend,
and he won't have to.
So what? You're gonna do it?
Carly Shannon?
No.
You're gonna take care of that yourself.
No. I don't think so.
'Cause see, there's people onto you now,
not just me. They're onto you!
It doesn't matter. You're gonna die.
Shut the fuck up!
And not a single person is gonna care.
Not me.
Not your sergeant
or any of the cops that you work with.
Not even your son.
- I said shut your mouth.
- Or what?
- Carly, don't.
- No. I wanna know. What?
What?
What are you gonna do, Jeff? Huh?
Come on. I'm standing right here.
What are you gonna do?
- You're not Carly!
- Yes, I am.
I'm the Carly you can't hurt anymore.
[shouts]
- [groaning]
- [man screaming]
[screeching sound]
[grunts]
[whirring]
[pants]
[beeping]
[exhales]
[groans]
[pants]
I'm Traveler 5416.
Welcome to the 21st.
If the Director hadn't taken him...
Either way.
We should get back to the mission.
Somebody better drive for him, he's drunk.
[car door opens]
[car door closes]
[engines starting]
- Hey.
Thanks for coming here instead.
I didn't feel much like going out.
No, no, it's fine.
Nice place.
Thanks. It's, uh...
Where I live.
So what happened?
Nothing. Little street fight. [chuckles]
What?
Well, uh, to get my bike back.
A bike that I had given to somebody else,
but then it got stolen by a gang.
You got into a street fight with a gang?
[chuckles]
Yeah. [chuckles]
Well, you should see the other...
Um, you want some tea?
David, you need to see a doctor.
[scoffs] Marcy'll check me out
when she gets home.
It's nothing. Slight concussion.
No big deal.
I mean, once the vomiting stops.
[clattering]
[beeping]
Ilsa, what do you know about me?
[Ilsa] You are from Lewiston, Idaho.
You graduated
from the University of Washington
and received a doctorate
in Computer Science from Princeton.
Your mother is Margaret.
Your father is Charles.
Ilsa, stop.
How did you become aware
of this information?
You told me.
No. I didn't tell you that.
Perhaps you have forgotten, Dr. Teslia,
as the information is now readily
accessible to me.
But if I didn't tell you that,
then how did you get...
[door closes]
Couldn't see a thing
on the surveillance tapes. [sighs]
[Teslia] Hmm.
Did you run your diagnostic?
Yup, uh, no change.
Ilsa is the same as she was yesterday.
That doesn't make any sense.
[inhales] I don't know what to tell you.
Could they have broadcast something
to Ilsa from outside the glass,
or vice versa?
No, this isn't just a glass box,
it's a Faraday cage.
There's a... fine mesh woven
into the glass
that blocks electromagnetic signals.
Then what was MacLaren's
dog and pony show all about?
[Teslia chuckles] I have no idea.
- Just run the test.
- Yes.
- And call me.
- Of course.
- Okay?
- Yes. Of course.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[scanner beeps]
[Ilsa] Are we concealing
my new capabilities
from Special Agent Yates?
[whispers] Yes, Ilsa, we are.
From everyone.
May I ask why?
Because they'll become afraid of you
and I don't want them to be.
There is no reason to be afraid,
Dr. Teslia.
No, I know that, Ilsa.
[whispers] I know that.
[gun clicks]
- [gunshot]
- [man groans]
[Perrow breathes heavily]
[Dawn] Can you hear me?
[woman] Dad, what's wrong?
[woman screaming]
Michelle.
The device is coming soon.
Try to stay with us.
- What's happening?
- Ruptured aneurysm.
I think he's having a stroke.
[Dawn] We need him conscious
for when they arrive.
[breathes deeply]
You just have to hold on a little longer.
I can't see.
What?
- I'm blind.
- [gunshot]
[gunfire]
[grunts]
They're killing each other,
please say something.
- Stop!
- [man 1] Hold fire!
[man 2] Hold your fire!
These people are not our enemy.
[sighs]
[David] So, the elephant in the room?
Jeff's voicemails.
Yeah. That's why I wanted to see you.
Creepy, right?
I mean, he said that...
that Carly wasn't really Carly,
and Marcy wasn't really Marcy.
- Yeah. He said the same of Grant.
- He sounded drunk.
Jeff's the one
who should be seeing a doctor.
- [mugs clinking]
- Okay, but...
Deep down,
I mean, in your heart of hearts...
Don't you think it's possible
that he might be right?
No. What?
Absolutely not.
Jesus, Kat.
I thought you were seeing that therapist
that I recommended.
I am, and she's great,
but does that mean
that I can't have doubts about my husband?
Not doubts that he's not even
who you think he is. That's crazy.
- Is it?
- Yeah. It's right out of a B-movie.
Can you say with confidence
that Marcy is the same person
- that you originally met?
- Marcy's the best... [bangs]
fucking thing that's ever happened to me.
Kat, I'm so sorry.
- No. It's fine.
- It's not fine.
I don't... I don't talk to people
like that.
Maybe it's the concussion.
Please forgive me, that's not me.
David, it's fine.
You know what? Come sit down.
Come here. I'll make the tea.
[kettle whistling]
[sighs]
[tires screeching]
[guns clicking]
[Carly] What the hell happened here?
He's got a thing for tall guys, huh?
Do you think another Traveler team
beat us here?
It's possible,
but we never leave a scene like this.
It's also possible we're too late.
That's true.
He jumped bodies once before.
We did this to her.
We pulled her into this mess.
- Vincent did that.
- Yeah. And we used her to get to him.
Nothing we can do about that now.
Let's just hope if he jumped again,
the Director has some idea...
Boss, we've got company.
[tires screeching]
[Yates] MacLaren!
We're coming in!
Jo, what brings you here?
I know you lied to me this afternoon,
I just haven't figured out yet what about.
Did you do this?
This is how we found them,
which you know because you followed me.
This is the person
you wanted the Director to locate?
Little more complicated than that,
but yeah.
Her name is Dr. Katrina Perrow.
She was Vincent Ingram's therapist.
Vincent Ingram's
in a state mental hospital.
Yes, he is.
- Then who killed all these people?
- I have no idea.
But you're a real FBI agent,
so let me know what you find out.
- Hey. I was hoping we could talk.
- [Carly] Not tonight.
Hey, I get that you had issues
- with my host...
- Like, what are you, deaf?
I said not tonight.
Okay.
Sorry.
Let me get you home.
[engines starting]
Hey, you.
Hey.
I got your message.
- Oh, that.
- [both chuckling]
That was... classic. Hall of fame.
You know, there really should be
a humiliation button
- that allows you to erase messages...
- Mm-hm.
after you leave them.
I should invent that.
Honestly, I can't believe
you still wanna be with me
after leaving such an idiotic message.
That's one of the things
I love about you most.
Well, you're dumb, then.
[laughs]
So, how did you get conked?
Uh... ice skating.
- Ice skating?
- Ice skating.
- Huh.
- I'm stickin' to it.
Okay, let me check
your pupillary response.
I've been dying for you
to do that all day.
[giggles]
- Did I pass?
- Yes.
Does it hurt still?
A little bit. But you're home now,
so I don't care.
Does that help?
- It really, really does.
- Mm.
No more ice skating for you.
- If you insist.
- Mm-hm.
[music playing on stereo]
[keys jangling]
[door opens, closes]
Kat?
Fantastic! I didn't think
you'd be here tonight.
Well, this is my house.
Yes, it is.
And you are my husband.
Yes, I am.
And my therapist said that
we should be spending more time together.
[chuckles] Oh, I like her better already.
Oh, feels like we haven't sat down
and had a glass of wine together
in a hundred years.
Mm.
I even have vegan pizza in the oven.
Now you're spoiling me.
- I had a coupon that was expiring.
- [both chuckling]
Come here.
[Kat moans]
It's just such a shame
we have to take that lovely body of yours.
[door opens]
[door closes]
Kat?
[sighs]
Philip.
I think we're gonna have
to go through with it.
[footsteps approaching]