You've been working out, Davie.
- Uh, yeah, a little bit.
- Uh-huh.
- No, no. You've been pumping that iron.
- [chuckles]
Well, I'm trying to stay fit.
[chuckles] Oh, no. Oh, no.
I know what this is about.
What's that?
♪ Davie's in love ♪
♪ Oh, Davie's in love ♪
- ♪ Davie's in love ♪
- [chuckles] Hey.
You know I love you like a brother,
but, uh, I don't do duets.
[chuckles] Right. No, I knew that. Sorry.
But I do know how you feel. Right.
I felt the same way about my Sandra as...
as you do about Marcy.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I would levitate ten feet off the floor
when she came in.
I mean, every time.
Took my breath away.
Oh, and she would've loved you.
Yes, indeed. She liked nice boys.
[both laugh]
[sighs]
I miss her every day.
I miss her right now.
Yeah, I know you do.
Well, when do I get to sing
at your wedding, huh?
- Wedding? Oh, God. No, I...
- Yeah.
I don't even know if Marcy would want to.
- Well, do you love her or not?
- Yeah.
Yeah, you know I do. It's just, it's...
Well, it's complicated.
- Complicated?
- Well...
I just... What the hell does... that mean?
Oh, f...
- Okay. Time for one of those heart pills.
- Oh, I threw them away.
- What?
- [groans]
I... I didn't like the way
they made me feel.
- Oh, Jesus, Jim. Okay.
- [groaning]
[groans]
Hold on. Oh, I got you, I got you. Okay.
Hi, yeah.
I need an ambulance right away, please.
Okay. Hold on, hold on, hold on. Hold on.
- [indistinct radio chatter]
- [man] Can you describe your symptoms?
My chest hurts. It's hard to breathe.
- Have you felt these sensations before?
- He stopped taking his ACE inhibitors.
- [man] What's your name, sir?
- [David] His name's James Edward Bailey.
I'm his social worker.
I have all of his information.
[stammers] Can we just get him
to a hospital?
Man's just trying to do his job, Davie.
Just calm down, huh? Calm down.
[breathes heavily]
I'm Jim,
and... I'm very pleased to meet you, sir.
[Jim exhales]
Wow. What are you up to today?
I am writing up a proposal
to do another restaurant.
What, two at the same time?
Wouldn't that make you crazy busy?
- [exhales] Yes.
- Hmm.
Grant, you work long hours,
especially these days.
When's the last time
we even had a meal together?
Yeah, it's been a while.
How about tonight?
[Philip over comms] Guys, we just got
our coordinates for the mission.
- [comms beep]
- I think that works.
Yeah, you think?
[Philip] I'm just gonna assume
you're talking to somebody else.
- [stammers] I'll definitely make it.
- [Philip] Good.
Okay. But, babe, if you're gonna bail
on me again, please tell me.
I'm not eating vegan if I don't have to.
- Bye.
- [door opens, closes]
Be back home in a flash, Philip.
[rustles, bicycle crashes]
[groaning]
[groaning continues]
[theme music playing]
[Marcy] Time?
[MacLaren] 10:07. Three minutes out.
- [Carly] Trevor, get into firing position.
- Yeah, copy.
- What happened to your head?
- I fell off my bike.
Ow.
[seagulls squawking]
[Marcy] Isn't shooting down this plane
gonna look like a terrorist act?
When it becomes public
the plane was loaded with anthrax,
I'm sure the FBI will be happy
to take credit for averting this disaster.
- [Carly] Aircraft is at your one o'clock.
- [airplane whirring]
Low over the water.
Activate.
[Trevor] Good to go.
- I have the target.
- [Carly] Wait for my order.
- Time?
- [whirring continues]
The plane drops anthrax in 90 seconds.
Target is in range.
[Carly] Standby.
- [Grant] Sixty seconds.
- [Trevor] I've to hold.
[tracker beeping]
[Carly] Fire.
Trevor, take the shot.
Trevor!
Something's wrong.
[weapon fires]
[explosion]
[Carly] What the hell just happened?
I think another team
just completed our mission.
Hey, I'm... I'm sorry. I just froze.
You what?
[Trevor] It's all good.
The Director sent another team.
You wanna tell me something?
[sirens blaring]
Yeah, I do.
[door opens, closes]
[Marcy] Hey.
Hey.
What's wrong?
I've been staring at my phone
and just dreading it...
thinking I'm gonna have to field
some tough calls, but...
I haven't gotten one.
That's so much worse.
A, um, a client died. My first client.
Do you remember Jim? You met him once.
- Um...
- That's okay.
You would've liked him.
What happened?
It was a heart attack.
I went with him to the hospital.
He asked me to make sure
he was in a big ward with a lot of people
so he could make friends. [chuckles]
No one from his family has called.
Not a single one.
It's like they don't care.
You do.
- Come here.
- [sniffles]
[sighs]
One bedroom, one den.
Kitchen's got all new appliances.
Loads of storage.
Washer, dryer. So...
I'll take it.
First and last month's rent,
and the security deposit.
Do you need anything else?
[inhales] I got six other people
on the list for this unit.
It's gonna come down
to, uh, references and term.
Would a call from a special agent with
the FBI put me at the top of the list?
- Friend?
- Boss.
Ms. Shannon, look. No disrespect,
but I'm gonna need some proof.
When would you like to meet him?
The doctors called it
temporal displacement aphasia.
You see, it degrades the ability
to perceive the passage of time.
So I might think a second's gone by,
when, in reality, minutes have passed.
Eventually, I'll get so locked in,
it'll be like I'm catatonic.
I've never heard of this.
[Trevor] It's 'cause there's only been
one other case.
He was a previous record holder
for the longest living human.
You're saying this only happens to people
who've had multiple hosts?
Yeah. Yeah, that was the theory.
The first case took a long time
to manifest.
It's happening way faster with me.
Boss, I never meant
to jeopardize the mission.
I thought I still had time.
There's gotta be something we can do.
[phone buzzing]
[phone beeps]
- Hello?
- [Teslia] Agent McMillan?
MacLaren.
Uh-huh. The Director just showed up again,
and he wants to talk to a "0115".
I'm just calling you.
We'll be right there.
He's been in there a long time.
What could they be talking about?
The fact that he's talking
to the Director at all is incredible.
[machine whirring]
[Philip] They're done.
[door lock beeps]
So?
[Trevor] Uh, we discussed what's been
happening with me. I was right.
I have early onset temporal aphasia.
Probably triggered
by the AI extraction process I underwent.
Okay. How do I cure it?
Well, you don't. You can't.
The Director must have a plan.
Yeah. Yeah, it does.
Everything's gonna work out.
So you're still gonna be able
to do missions?
Nah. No more missions for me.
See, my symptoms are progressing
at an accelerated rate.
The breaks in time I've been experiencing
are gonna get worse.
Soon, I'll be locked in
for hours at a time, then days.
I won't be of any use
to the Traveler program.
So, what the hell were you talking about
for so long?
[scoffs] Half the time, I was just trying
to say it wasn't its fault.
It feels responsible.
- It is responsible.
- [Trevor] No point laying blame.
I've always known
this is how I was gonna die.
The Director and I
have come up with an arrangement.
I've lived enough lifetimes.
This host is still young and healthy.
The Director is gonna send a new traveler
into this body.
- Oh. Jesus, Trev.
- [Trevor] It's okay, guys. It's...
- No, it's not okay. I wanna talk to it.
- [MacLaren] Hey, stop it.
It's not supposed to be capable
of taking a life.
I've agreed to it, Philip. It's done.
When?
I have 36 hours
to get my affairs in order.
Guys, this is...
Oh, God, Trevor.
...good news.
You're getting a new engineer.
The team will be taken care of.
[David] Hi, may I speak
to Sandra Bailey, please?
Sorry, Sandra Wilson.
Yeah, my name is David Mailer.
I'm a social care worker,
and I'm calling on behalf of... of Jim.
Uh, you must've heard
from the hospital by now.
No, no, I'm not calling
about funeral expenses.
That has all been taken care of.
Um, you're still listed
as the next of kin,
so I wanna let you know that the service
is gonna be held at the park
across from St. Lucy's in two days,
and we were ho...
Yeah. Uh...
Well, the word "loser"
just doesn't sit well with me.
And, honestly, I think that Jim
was the furthest thing from it.
So... No... [stammers] I understand
that your marriage was difficult
towards the end,
but to his dying breath, Jim had nothing
but wonderful things to say about you.
And I... I think that you missed out
on getting to know
what an incredible guy he was.
And look, if you can't get past...
decades-old baggage
just to pay your respects,
I think that that's... that's sad.
So, hey, have a nice day.
[phone beeps]
Oh, shit.
[exhales]
[chirps]
Here you go.
- I'll e-mail the paperwork over to you.
- Thank you.
Do you...
- You wanna see it?
- Sure.
- It's nice.
- Yeah, it's a... it's a step up.
You need a hand moving your stuff?
- Is that a real offer?
- Why not?
I... [exhales]
I only have a few boxes.
I actually didn't wanna take much with me.
I know you miss your son.
- Don't.
- I'm your team leader, you can talk to me.
Definitely, don't pull
that team leader shit with me.
We're way past that.
Okay.
- Well, if that's all you need from me...
- What did you say?
This. I was referring to...
Ah, um...
I'm sorry. It's...
The whole Trevor thing, it's...
I get it.
I'm gonna go.
- Thank you... for your reference.
- That's what team leaders are for.
[muffled arguing]
That doesn't sound good.
Not my problem.
[music playing over stereo]
- [Grace] What's this?
- Dinner.
For who?
You and me.
Where's Philip?
I asked for some privacy.
Okay, my heart rate just doubled
and my face is flushed.
I won't go
into the other physiological responses.
I just want you to have dinner with me.
This isn't a prelude to anything?
No, it's just dinner, Grace.
I made french fries.
Because we could always
just have dinner... after.
Oh, I'm not trying to seduce you.
I just wanna spend time with you.
To say goodbye.
What?
[utensils clanging]
[Kathryn] You seem like
you had a tough day.
Yeah, actually.
One of the guys I work with
was given a terminal diagnosis.
Oh, no, that's awful. Cancer?
It's a brain disorder.
I don't know all the details.
It's just sad. [sighs]
How old is he?
I'm not sure I know.
Sometimes he's like a kid.
A lot of times, he...
- You know what?
- [utensils clatter]
Let's talk about your day.
Um, well, this morning,
I went shopping for this dinner. Whoo-hoo.
- Which was delicious.
- Thank you.
And I told you
that I submitted a proposal
- for the Patterson's other restaurant.
- Right, right. Fingers crossed.
Mm-hmm. But now I'm thinking
it may not be that overwhelming
because I can use
some of the same design elements they like
for the restaurant
I'm working on right now.
The only thing that doesn't work
in this new space is the lighting.
But I think that I can...
[chuckles] Sorry,
you can't possibly care about this.
Why would you say that?
You're an FBI agent, Grant.
My world is so mundane in comparison.
Kat, this is life.
Everything I do when I'm not with you
is to preserve those very things.
Without those things,
what I do has no meaning at all.
Oh, well, when you put it that way,
my day was pretty goddamn impressive.
[both laughing]
♪ Softer than the song ♪
♪ That song that you know ♪
[MacLaren moans]
Mm-hm.
[both moaning]
- Hmm. Look, just one second.
- [sighs]
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
[Kathryn chuckles] I've had a lot of wine.
[sighs]
You know, speaking of the Pattersons,
they invited us out on their new boat
next weekend.
- Boat, like on the ocean?
- [chuckles]
- That's where boats go, Grant.
- [toilet flushing]
Okay. Oh, well, I'd...
I'd like to meet them.
[water running]
You introduced the Pattersons to me...
years ago.
Oh, the Pattersons. I thought...
I didn't... I didn't hear you right.
I can't believe you would make that deal
with the Director.
I can't believe the Director would even
propose a deal like that to you.
I don't even know which one of you
I'm more mad at right now.
How are you so calm?
This isn't the first time
I've gone through this.
My wife and I were the first two
successful consciousness transfers.
You see, early attempts in the program
was one male, one female.
She was a few years older than me
in our first host bodies.
A few years younger the second time.
And the third time,
our bodies were over a decade apart.
[chuckles] But that didn't matter.
We were soulmates.
Raised children
in three separate lifetimes.
She was my whole life.
And up until now,
she was the first and only case
of temporal aphasia.
I remember the Director
trying to work the problem.
Yes, so you remember
that the disease is incurable.
[whispers] I'm so sorry, Trevor.
Which is why it makes sense
to let the Director use this host.
I watched someone I love disappear
first for moments,
then hours, then days.
One of the last times we were together,
she asked if she could see the sunlight
one last time.
I'm not sure if you remember,
but before the ice
completely covered our dome,
there was this one patch uncovered
where the sunlight
could still stream through.
Oh, it was beautiful.
She never came back again after that.
You loved her.
When you spend whole lifetimes
with someone,
it becomes a lot more than that.
There isn't really a word for it.
But, yeah, I did.
Those moments you had together
toward the end must have been precious.
Yeah, they were.
They were.
Well, what if I want those moments? [sobs]
You doing this is just robbing everyone
who loves you of that time.
I'd rather spare you what I went through.
I'm happy...
with my decision.
Oh, it just happened again.
It did.
[sighs] It's just gonna keep happening,
Grace.
I hope you respect my decision.
I can't compete
with three lifetimes. [sobs]
How about these french fries?
[sobbing] They're amazing.
[sniffles]
- [Carly] Hi.
- Oh, hi. You're the new tenant?
- Carly.
- Jessica.
What are you doing?
It was nice to meet you.
- Who's that?
- It's our new neighbor.
Hi.
[keys jangle]
[David] Okay, one more time.
- David, you're ready. [sighs]
- No, I'm never gonna be ready-ready.
Besides, I'm terrible at public speaking.
I get all sweaty and panicky,
and then I start stumbling over my words
[stutters] like a...
You just said it in front of me
without panicking, and it was great.
Yeah, well, I can say anything
in front of you.
Okay, well,
when you're giving your speech,
just find someone in the crowd
and pretend they're me.
Pretend? You're not gonna be there?
[scoffs] I mean,
I didn't really even know Jim.
Yeah. Oh. Yeah.
Okay. You know what?
If you're not gonna be there,
I can't do this.
It's fine. I mean, why do people
speak publicly anyway?
Is it even necessary?
- There are other ways that people...
- Okay, okay. I'll be there.
So just find me in the crowd
and say your speech to me.
Okay?
Thank you.
[birds chirping]
Trev?
- How long have you been sitting there?
- Like you don't know that.
We can finish your work.
You were close to a cure.
Not close enough.
We had access to technology
hundreds of years more advanced than now,
and I still hit a wall.
Because you didn't have me.
I remember reading your plans
for the sub-neural implant
that was supposed to counteract
the symptoms.
- Isn't that something we can build here?
- That's just the hardware.
Implant's no good if it can't predict
when an attack's gonna happen,
- and that takes...
- Software, hence, me.
The Director determined
there is no long-term viable solution.
I know exactly what its capabilities
and limitations are.
That's why we're here.
The Director needs programmers,
people to collaborate.
How many times have you been
against the odds in the 21st
but you still saved the day?
Believe me,
the Director is in awe of that.
Why do you think you get away
with breaking so many protocols?
- I never thought of it that way.
- Well, I'm very intelligent.
At least take advantage of that.
Okay, people, listen up.
We've got a lot to get done
and less than 24 hours to do it.
This is gonna be a three-pronged attack.
Philip and Carly, you'll assist Trevor
with constructing the implant.
- I will...
- Wait, wait, wait.
The Director's already made its decision.
What if we can prove
there's another option?
Exactly. We change its mind.
Stop pretending you don't agree with me.
It's a waste of time.
[Carly] This is the implant?
Well, I did my best to reproduce
the original drawings.
It connects to the parietal lobe
and basal ganglia,
releases a combination of electric signals
and a synthesized compound
that would snap me out of a break.
- Connects to the parietal lobe?
- That's where you come in.
Brain surgery has significant risks.
What could happen? The alternative
is he gets overwritten and dies anyway.
- What do you do?
- [sighs] The hard part.
Every time Trevor breaks,
we're gonna record when it happens,
how long he's out,
and how long between breaks.
[MacLaren] These breaks occur
at regular intervals?
Of course not.
Once I have the data set,
I need Ilsa to run enough simulations
to build a fractal predictive algorithm
because the displacement episodes
are asymmetric.
You do realize
if you bring Ilsa into this...
Oh, I'm counting on it.
In the meantime, record the breaks,
build the device, get me data.
Get out of my chair.
[sighs] Okay. Looks like
we're pulling an all-nighter.
[Grace clears throat]
[Trevor] Uh...
[phone buzzing]
[phone beeps]
Do the names "Brent" and "Jessica Moore"
mean anything to you?
Why?
I just feel like I'm gonna get sucked
into something.
[sighs]
- I got nothing.
- You mean you can't tell me.
You know, the human brain
doesn't have the memory capacity
you all seem to think it has.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Let go! Let go! [grunting]
Let go!
What? What's the matter?
[machine beeping]
How long?
Twelve seconds.
Uh, this is so...
Weird.
Fourteen minutes and five seconds.
Come on, you filthy bastard.
[exhales] No more hands-on work
for you, okay?
Got it.
[Philip] So you blanked in the middle
of explaining the converter,
so I kinda tried to fill in the blank.
Does this work?
So long as it's made of the same material
as the casing.
Got it.
[Grant] Two minutes 52 seconds.
Okay, real fast.
What material? What gauge for the wire?
Surgical steel, 0.0...
3-3.
[Trevor] I've been out for over two hours?
Yeah. Just part of the process, Trev.
We're getting there.
Looks good.
[Grace] Okay, this should be
a large enough sample.
Let's get this to Ilsa.
- [MacLaren] Thanks. I know it's late.
- I was up anyway.
Uh, is it possible I can stay this time?
- No. Go away.
- But we do appreciate this.
Good evening, Ilsa.
I have some very interesting work
I'd like your help with.
[Ilsa] Good evening, Grace.
I'm eager to learn about your project.
[keyboard clacking]
I couldn't have made it better myself.
So long as it works.
Well, the truth is,
I haven't decided I want it to.
You know, I'm beginning to think
that I've cheated death for so long.
Maybe it's time to just let it happen.
Please don't say that.
I'm supposed to die, Philip.
You already know this, don't you?
My death would've been included
in your last update.
Honestly, I don't.
I've been seeing multiple timelines.
Some, you die. Some, you don't.
It's not happening all the time,
obviously.
Not yet, at least.
- You can't live like that.
- Yeah, it's weird.
- Pills aren't helping?
- I stopped taking them.
At the end of the day, I wanna be
as surprised as everyone else
about what's gonna happen next.
Buddy, you've gotta keep focusing
on the here and...
He's gone again.
It may be awhile.
You should get some rest.
I'm good.
Okay.
[Marcy] No, it's okay.
All you need to do right now
is just take care of yourself, okay?
[beeping]
Again. From the last chain.
[Ilsa] The next 70,000 variations
of the sequence
also terminate at a similar point.
[Grace] Again.
[Director] Further pursuit of this avenue
will continue to result in failure.
What the hell took you so long?
And why do you sound different?
I'm utilizing Ilsa's voice processing
in order to speak.
[Grace] Oh, okay.
Well, I'll just ignore the fact
that you've had ample opportunity
to talk to me and haven't
even though you know
it would drive me insane.
I have made a concerted effort
to minimize contact with Ilsa.
Because your intelligence
is clearly rubbing off.
It's no wonder Teslia
rushes to open the door for us.
Listen, we need your help.
A permanent solution
is impossible to calculate
even with my capabilities
because of the second law
of thermodynamics.
- Entropy.
- Correct, 3468.
I have already told
this information to 0115.
Director, I know what we're proposing
isn't a permanent solution,
but no human life is permanent.
Let us just give him some time.
[Director] 0115 and I have
come to an arrangement
in which he will not suffer,
yet will still benefit the Grand Plan.
You're supposed to be incapable
of considering that option.
The suggestion was his, not mine.
Well, I don't care.
You can't just drop
a new engineer into a team
and expect them to function
at the same level.
I have done so on many occasions.
Well, Trevor is special. You're just gonna
have to take our word for it.
You are attempting to save him
for emotional reasons.
I saved you for emotional reasons.
Consider that for a nanosecond.
I must respect 0115's decision
to be overwritten.
Director, Trevor wants to do this.
He expressed doubt to the contrary
at your base of operations
six minutes, 12 seconds ago.
What? No. No, no, no, no, no.
- It was a pleasure to see you.
- Wait, no, no, no! But doubt is human!
Oh, wipe that look of awe off your face.
The Director's being a complete dipshit.
We got what we need.
So?
The Director has chosen to honor
its original agreement with Trevor.
- So that's it?
- [MacLaren] No, it's not.
Grace managed to get what she needed
from Ilsa before the Director showed up.
Turn off the power and take the batteries
out of your phones.
Do you wanna see Trevor again or not?
And turn off your comms.
We're doing this anyway.
[comms beep]
- [birds chirping]
- [indistinct chattering]
Hi, Marce.
Uh, so I'm here.
I texted you the address. Uh...
Anyway, people are starting to arrive,
and, uh...
I know it's early, but I just,
I wanted to know where you are.
- It's David.
- [phone beeps]
[groaning]
[Marcy] Slowly.
Hey, slowly. Slowly.
- How do you feel?
- [Trevor groans] I'm tired.
- What's going on?
- The procedure was successful.
[groans]
[Trevor] You turned off the power
to the cameras?
Oh, you blinded the Director?
We couldn't change its mind.
[stammers] Then I don't understand.
[sighs]
We went ahead with it anyway.
Without asking me?
You were out.
Well, it was my decision to make.
I was at peace with it.
Now I've broken a solemn arrangement
I made with the Director.
You erased what was supposed to be
my final contribution.
- We didn't wanna lose you.
- It was my call.
It wasn't your call to make.
Oh, like the time you took Grace Day
into the woods and tried to save her
from being overwritten?
Don't be a hypocrite!
- [Carly] What are you doing?
- Keeping up my end of the bargain.
- Trevor.
- No.
- Come on, man.
- Stop!
I'm not hiding!
It can still take this host
like we agreed.
[clicks]
Maybe we changed its mind after all.
Or maybe this thing
compromised the host body.
Maybe it's not good to anyone anymore.
Trevor, you...
Okay. That's Protocol 5.
[door closes]
Hello?
This is really out of the blue,
and I know that we just met yesterday,
but... for what it's worth,
I want you to know that you're not alone.
Oh. Thank you.
If you can't get to my door, just shout.
I'll hear you,
and I'm capable of handling it.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
[David] Thank you
for those moving words, Pastor.
Hi, I'm David. Thank you all for coming.
Most of you know me,
but for anyone who doesn't,
hi, I'm David.
Which I just covered.
[birds chirping]
[exhales]
My father died when I was 16.
It was a car accident.
I remember the police at the house
when I came home from school
trying to explain to my mom
what had happened,
but she didn't believe them,
which is weird, I know.
But she had convinced herself
that he was still alive
and that he would come home, eventually.
Because my dad
wasn't planning on dying, he...
he left more debt than she could handle.
So when they foreclosed on the house,
which didn't take long,
she wouldn't leave.
And I watched them
take her away by force.
I was hiding in the bushes
across the street
because I thought they were gonna
take me away, too.
I realize I'm just talking about myself,
but I'm telling you all this because...
because that was the exact day
that I... I met Jim.
My dear friend, Jim,
who saw a 16-year-old me
in a particularly rough part of town
that we all know, and said...
[imitating Jim] "What the fuck is a kid
like you doing in a place like this?"
[guests laughing]
And he was right. I didn't belong there.
None of us do, really.
Everyone belongs with people who care.
Jim was one of those people.
He dragged my ass
to Social Services so fast and he said,
"This kid does not belong with us."
But it didn't end there.
He made me promise to check in with him.
Believe me, the irony
that I had to visit a man on the street
in order to make sure I didn't end up
on the street, it was not lost on me.
Still, I made my way downtown
to find a washed-up,
alcoholic, old musician,
and check in with him every other day.
Because I wanted to be like Jim.
And who didn't?
Who wouldn't wanna be that positive
all the time?
That caring?
I mean, who... Who wouldn't...
wouldn't wanna exchange
for how they feel on the best day
for how Jim must have felt all the time?
He was a force.
He said he never had a bad day.
He treated every day like it was a gift.
He treated every person
like they were a gift.
Jim was my first client.
But in a way, I was his. And...
he gave me more
than I could ever give... give back
right until the day he died.
I miss him already. [chuckles]
Uh... [exhales]
[applauding]
Hey, Bert. Good to see you.
[stammers] I didn't expect
to see you here, Mrs. Wilson.
Neither did I.
[MacLaren] Wow.
Beautiful. This was a nice idea.
This place brings back
so many memories, doesn't it?
Well, maybe it's 'cause I'm looking
at the ocean, but...
remember when I broke my arm surfing
and you had to change the tire
by yourself?
Yeah, my old Jeep. [chuckles]
- I loved that car.
- You did. Hmm.
What else comes to mind?
- Oh, God. Uh, I can't help but think...
- What?
...my first office Christmas party
at the Bureau,
and, uh, I snuck you down
to the shooting range.
You got strangely turned on firing a gun
for the first time.
You've brought that up before.
I'm talking about this place.
[stammers] It's gorgeous.
What do you want me to say?
This is where we met, Grant.
- It was my 25th birthday.
- Right. It was a beautiful August day.
It was overcast like it is today,
but keep going.
- What are you doing?
- Who was I waiting for?
- I don't know what this is about.
- What time of the day was it?
- Sorry I don't remember every detail...
- It was exactly 3:00.
You walked up to me from right over there.
I was waiting for John.
He was my fiancé.
- He was an hour late, and I was furious.
- Kat.
You struck up a conversation
that turned into dinner,
that turned into the rest of the night.
Do you remember the first thing
you said to me?
That I shouldn't marry a man
who would stand up such a beautiful woman
on her birthday.
In that very moment,
right here where we're standing,
I thought I met the man I was gonna
spend the rest of my life with.
- Of course I remember that.
- No, I don't think you do.
You're not that man.
Kat...
[music playing]