Joanne...
Listen to me carefully.
- Who are you?
- Explain who did this.
You killed my husband.
Hey, slow down a little.
You can scream at the top of your lungs,
they're not gonna wake up for hours.
Yeah, but Carly's baby might.
The kid just settled down.
He's been traumatized enough.
It'll work out, boss.
Sure it will.
Maybe we should go over our story
one more time.
Not for my sake, obviously.
Vincent?
Vincent, where are you?
I'm right here, Simon.
Can you hear me?
- You're in my head.
- In a way.
I've given you a comm.
Now close your eyes.
That's the most important rule.
Good. Make sure they stay closed.
I've sent people for you.
You said you were gonna fix me.
And that's
just what we're going to do.
Then why are you taking me away?
The Director is testing you.
The device works now!
I did what you said!
Multiple uses, multiple transfers!
And it's going to be put to good use,
I promise.
You've done well.
I'm cold.
I know. This won't take much longer.
I don't like this place. I wanna go home.
This is the test. Remember the rule.
Eyes closed.
You've been very helpful to me, Simon,
and I will always be grateful.
- Are you ready?
- No! I wanna go home!
- Be strong, now.
- You said you would fix me!
I am fixing you.
You promised me!
Your host had been so loyal,
I just couldn't bring myself to kill him.
But I knew the Director
would have no such compunction.
Welcome to the 21st.
There he is!
Oh, Jesus, keep it down a bit, man.
- How did I get here?
- I took your keys.
Made you crash.
You were "celebrating."
Well, I must've had a good time, Phil,
'cause...
I don't remember how I got here
or what we were celebrating.
You were in trouble with a loan shark,
uh, named Varghese.
Oh, right.
I got picked up by a couple of his boys.
I don't remember what happened after that.
Well, they gave you 24 hours
to come up with the money.
You came to me,
asked me to place some bets,
we came here to watch them come in
and hilarity ensued.
- You really don't remember?
- No.
I maybe forgot to tell you
I probably shouldn't drink.
Oh, we established that.
But, my hungover friend,
you're out of the hole
with a little extra.
Oh, I owe Varghese more than this.
Well, he's been paid.
That's... That's the extra.
Fuck off.
Man, I love you. Oh, come here.
Ray, that's, uh...
what friends are for.
Agent Yates.
Please, take a seat.
First, let me say
how sorry I am for your loss.
- I know from experience.
- Thank you, sir.
I'm fine.
Good.
Then please explain your request
that I issue a cancellation order
of a highly classified,
highly complex operation
of which you should have had
zero knowledge
and which is scheduled to begin
worldwide in 23 minutes?
The request isn't mine, sir.
It's from the Director.
- He is the FBI director.
- Last I checked.
I think everyone in this room knows
to which director I'm referring.
How was this communicated to you?
It began several days ago.
And you waited until now?
Sir, if I can explain my reasoning
for not coming to you sooner.
Go ahead, Agent Yates.
Start at the beginning.
Boss, Ray is taken care of.
So the memory inhibitor worked.
He was the easy one.
That and the cash.
Now you can get back
to cleaning up our mess.
- On it.
- Tanner.
Mac.
Lot of people here,
they can't all be Travelers.
Nowhere near.
But Wakefield handpicked them,
they're good agents.
- How's it going up there?
- Same as 20 minutes ago.
David and Jeff are just taking a break
to get some medical attention.
- I thought we'd be on by now.
- These things take time.
Maybe you could go for a walk.
We just did.
Then go for another walk because
we're having a private conversation.
Sorry to interrupt.
Where were we?
- I think we were done.
- No, no, no. Um...
We were talking about your... feelings.
- You were talking about my feelings.
- Right.
The logic's inescapable.
001 kidnapped every significant other
on your team.
Mnh-mnh. Philip and Ray?
- Oh, I don't judge.
- Yeah, you do.
- Look, Trev.
- Trev?
It's obvious I was taken
by 001,
held against my will,
and frankly starved.
We were only given water
for what seemed like days.
Thirty-one hours.
Because of the inevitable impact
it was gonna have on you... emotionally.
I'm important to you
in a way neither one of us foresaw.
And the sooner we both accept that...
Grace,
I am delighted you were the one kidnapped
and interrogated, not my parents.
There, I said it. So...
That is the second nicest thing
anyone has ever said to me.
So can I go now?
Oh, no, no, no. Your team needs you.
I'll go.
Oh.
It's thrilling, isn't it?
The primal rush of hormones
bursting from your endocrine system.
Remember we're much, much older
than these bodies.
And I can't wait
to try them out.
You train for years
to be a part of the grand plan.
Studied medicine.
Combat.
Finally, you get assigned a team
over hundreds of other volunteers.
And all you can think about
is your boyfriend.
I hope I never see Jeff again.
You can still make work.
He won't remember the last 24 hours.
Please. They're gonna need to forget
a hell of a lot more than that
and you know it, Marcy.
It's what we've got to work with.
They'll definitely remember
being abducted.
Meeting each other.
Maybe even their first session
with Perrow.
How do we even know
she'll cooperate?
She's already made a statement
saying that her actions were under duress.
Beyond that,
she wants nothing to do with us.
Frankly, I don't blame her.
As far as Perrow's concerned,
Vincent Ingram
was a deeply paranoid serial killer
who thought that time travelers
from the future were out to get him.
Crazy talk.
Fortunately, no mainstream news outlet's
taking it seriously.
And once the new Traveler in Ingram
confesses he went off his meds...
Yeah, but, see, you make it
sound ridiculous.
Hey, I'm from the future,
I'm not sure I buy it myself.
Jeff sure as hell believed it.
So did David.
- No. What is that? What is that?
- Let go of me.
So did your wife.
Which is why we have to make sure
our stories are straight.
So we can all get back to our Protocol 5.
- Oh! This is about Protocol 5?
- That is the mission.
Oh, now you care about the mission.
What is that supposed to mean?
You risked the entire Traveler program...
for her.
And you did the same.
What do you think,
you can just undo all of this?
- Just put it all back into a box?
- We try! Yes!
Shit was about to hit the fan
anyway, Carly.
Exposure was imminent across every major
intelligence agency worldwide:
CIA, FSB, Interpol.
All we did was speed up the process.
- Then we need to move.
- No. The Director sent us here.
The Director has been making it up
as it goes along, Marcy.
- I think it's about time we all admit...
- Keep your fucking voice down.
The point is, what happened was inevitable
and obviously there's now a plan in motion
to deal with that.
Meantime, we stick to the protocols.
You gonna order me to stay with him?
You gonna tell me what the bruising
on your knuckles is all about?
Hey, guys!
Grace just left.
I was about to rustle up some lunch.
I do a mean veggie stir fry, boss.
Does it have to be mean?
I just wanna go home!
And we're gonna take you home.
But you've been kidnapped,
held against your will,
probably brainwashed.
Apparently by a man I met
at a charity auction a decade ago,
as if that makes any sense.
At least tell me some things
I wanna know.
Like, where are we?
And how long have I been in these clothes?
An FBI safe house in the country,
and... a couple days.
Kathryn, you were found unconscious
yesterday
in a room with four other people:
David Mailer, Jeff Conniker,
Ray Green and...
- All of them claimed to know my husband.
- There. See?
New information.
Exactly why we have to keep
talking this through.
You've been through a traumatic ordeal
and without proper debriefing,
you could suffer long-term consequences.
This is what we do
if something like this happens
to any one of our agents in the field.
What's the first thing you remember
about the abduction?
His men...
They were twins.
Also new information.
We woke up in a room with five chairs.
And then they took us out one by one
to talk a woman.
- A doctor.
- Dr. Perrow.
- Yes.
- She was there against her will, too.
Oh, God, they have her daughter.
- They're fine, we've been in contact.
- Oh, that poor woman.
You know what, that's it,
that's all I remember.
Why did they drug me?
To move you to another location.
It's lucky MacLaren found you.
We can give you something
for the headache.
No. I don't like to take pills.
Can I see him now? Is Grant here yet?
He's here and you will see him very soon.
But first, I need you to go over
one more time
what you talked about in that room.
Hey! I need a ride,
who's the lucky driver?
The bus is for the 21sters.
Fine, let me take that one.
Parsons, we need a driver, over.
Parsons, what's your status?
How's your vision in this eye?
Well, can I see out of it? Yes.
Can I feel my pulse in it? Also yes.
Swelling's down, won't be pretty.
When I was a kid,
I got a black eye
the day before high school started.
"You should see the other guy!"
You're not the other guy, are you?
If it was me, you'd look a lot worse.
Yeah, okay.
Well, maybe you should look in the mirror.
He's at the roadblock down the road
a ways, his radio battery must be dead.
Never mind, I'll walk to him,
I've been cramped up for days without...
You don't care.
We good to keep going?
All yours.
I'm not talking to no one else
until someone shows me my son.
I told you, Jeff Jr.
is being well taken care of.
And I told you that that is unacceptable.
So is your attitude, Officer Conniker.
Okay, why don't you give the guy a break,
we were kidnapped for chrissake.
And I don't need your help neither.
Come with me, Mr. Mailer.
Maybe ask him
why he's sleeping with the girl
who's in the care of the state.
Simon?
Traveler 5069.
You knew my host?
Uh...
Yeah, I did.
I'm sorry, I'm just surprised Simon's
death wasn't in the historical record.
My host was supposed to be
a John Doe, attempted suicide,
but obviously he was a Traveler.
Have you ever seen a comm do this?
Ouch.
Let me get you something for that.
Someone tried to speak to him.
I couldn't hear over the train.
It wasn't just any Traveler, he was 004.
Didn't know he had a comm, though.
There's some things you need to know
about him.
First things first.
We need to reactivate
that code you embedded
in those obscene
confession recordings you made, ASAP.
What were you people thinking anyway?
I was thinking that we could locate
and erase the recordings
before they got out into the world,
but Vincent had countermeasures.
Of course the Director would have devised
a countermeasure for 001.
The Director can calculate in seconds
what would take a lifetime for you or I.
I find... your lack of fealty offensive.
This body is dehydrated,
do you have water?
You should know,
your host body suffers from extreme
paranoid schizophrenia.
Severe enough that our medic
couldn't synthesize a drug to prevent it.
Simon was pretty much incapable
of functioning in 21st society,
let alone as a Traveler.
You'll probably experience a psychotic
episode in the next few hours.
That's the body...
the Director chose for you.
David, I know it's complicated...
No, no, no. What's not to get?
This Vincent Ingram character
had it in for Agent MacLaren
because MacLaren was onto his whole
torturing people in wheelchairs
and burying 'em alive fetish,
so Ingram kidnaps,
drugs and/or beats the crap out of anyone
who's close to Agent MacLaren,
with the likely intention
of, you know, doing the same to us.
- That's pretty much it.
- Right.
Except I'm not even remotely close
to Agent MacLaren.
In fact, I don't think he likes me.
He hasn't said he doesn't like you.
You know what?
Mac and me,
we are just two different kinds of guys,
just one is no less manly than the other.
Just two different kinds of manly men.
- David.
- On the other hand,
if this is the new normal,
then I better buck up a little bit.
- You know what I mean?
- No.
Yeah.
I better grow a pair of kahunas.
I'm pretty sure that's not the word,
but I'm gonna go with it,
because if I'm gonna hang out
with an FBI doctor,
I better pack on some muscle,
you know, maybe do some,
like, what is it,
is this Taekwondo, Pilates?
David, calm down.
Agent Callahan...
I have never been more calm in my life.
Hello?
Are you people seriously
gonna make me walk
- the rest of...
- Hands on the vehicle now!
- What the hell...?
- Turn around
and put your hands on the vehicle
or we'll take you down!
Don't let her touch the comm!
This is drop leader 31...
One of the primaries attempted
to leave containment on foot,
we have her in custody.
This is Deputy Oslin. Yes?
All right. Keep us apprised.
We just captured
the Traveler designated 0027
attempting to escape before the assault.
Did she activate her comm device?
If she has one, she didn't try.
Then we're still on.
You were saying
the Director communicated to you?
Yes, it spoke to me.
That's not possible.
The Director is only
capable of communicating directly
through what they call "messengers."
Specifically, children.
Because for reasons we don't know,
the process kills an adult.
Apparently, it found another way.
Dr. Teslia?
Yes.
Hi.
And you're...?
The person you called
and insisted I come here
as a matter of national security.
I just forgot your name.
- Special Agent...
- Yates, yes, I knew that.
So...
Come, come.
This is Ilsa.
And Ilsa, this is...
Uh, what's your first name again?
Good evening, Dr. Teslia.
Would you like to play
a nice game of chess?
No one ever gets that. Okay.
Ilsa is AI that replaces Boolean logic
with quantum law on an algorithmic level.
There's maybe three others
as powerful in the whole world.
It gave you my cell number?
No. No, Ilsa is practically a newborn.
The Director gave me your number.
What Director?
That is the question.
All right, we're done.
I am very sorry
for your mother's diagnosis, Joanne.
I just heard the news myself.
How would it know that?
That's the Director talking now.
It's taking over Ilsa to communicate.
You were chosen
among seven potential candidates
within this jurisdiction.
Okay, who are you?
A sentient multi-zettaflop
quantum frame
speaking to you
from centuries in the future.
Matter of national security...
- ...only recently possible because of...
- Okay, stop!
I don't know if this is some kind of joke
or you're trying to sell me something,
but either way, you picked the wrong
person on the wrong goddamn day.
Agent Yates...
Call me again and I'll arrest you.
I take it he called you again.
Actually, he sent me a text.
It just didn't make sense
until the next day...
I was about to head out.
Maybe you should do the same.
Oh, I, um...
I wanna be here in case she wakes up.
Joanne... this last stroke was extensive.
She won't be waking up again.
Well, I spoke to her
the day before yesterday.
Here. Might as well
have something to read.
How could you know?
- What?
- You texted me yesterday.
- How did you know this would happen?
- I didn't!
I just texted
what the Director told me to text.
- Wow.
- Well, I wanna talk to the Director.
Yeah? Well, get in line!
I tried to all last night,
it wouldn't say a word to me.
Good morning, Joanne.
Dude, I'm standing right here.
How did you know?
From my time, the bird strike
and emergency landing of Flight 0718
is a part of historical record.
As was your mother's diagnosis.
- Have I convinced you?
- No.
What do you want from me?
To deliver a message
to your superiors.
Tell them yourself.
I have no means of directly
communicating outside of this room.
Ilsa is built inside an AI box,
it's completely cut off.
You can't just give a potentially emerging
super-intelligence the car keys.
You need to control what it learns.
What's the message?
Your superiors
must order the cancellation
of the coordinated assault planned
tomorrow on Traveler teams worldwide
or face an unstoppable series
of civilization ending events.
Discovery was inevitable
at this juncture of the grand plan.
Cooperation with the 21st century
authorities is now the optimal path.
You get that?
And you just left?
Deputy Oslin, did you believe in time
travelers the first time you were told?
Truthfully, no.
I reluctantly told the agent
who brought it to me
that he could pursue the matter,
but you're right,
I didn't believe him.
- How did he convince you?
- He didn't.
The agent was overwritten
along with his entire task force.
I'm sorry, I don't understand.
Special Agent Wakefield
told us
he was on the verge
of providing the proof he needed...
The next day,
he was a different man. Literally.
The man I had worked alongside
for ten years
had been replaced by an impostor.
How?
A traveler
supplants a host consciousness
with his or her own,
then pretends as if nothing's changed.
When Wakefield called us
that evening
ostensibly to assure me that his task
force had found nothing,
we knew he'd become one of them.
I take it the Director didn't share
that information with you.
No.
It's how they come here
from their own time. It's... insidious.
It's murder.
And the reason this operation
must continue on schedule,
however much you try
to convince us otherwise.
- You don't think that I'm...?
- Never met you before, Agent Yates.
How would we know?
Seasoned with exotic spices
from all around the world.
- Ellis had a whole rack of 'em.
- Thanks, Trev.
Hey, wanted to give you an update on...
Oh. Uh, I haven't eaten in hours,
would you mind if...?
Be my guest.
Mm.
Mm, this is amazing.
What spice is that?
All of them.
Mm.
- You mentioned an update?
- Right.
Okay, so we, uh,
we think we're in the clear
as far as the recordings
are concerned across the board.
Obviously, they're still traumatized,
but the inhibitor wiped the worst of it.
Who knows how David's gonna handle this?
David's fine. He's chatty...
Uh-oh.
He and Kathryn
will be ready for you soon.
But, uh, Jeff's a different story...
Your medic is worried that
he's resistant to memory inhibitor.
He's an alcoholic.
I gave him a stronger dose to compensate,
but his tolerance may be high.
Well, whatever, we gotta
release him anyway. Protocol 3.
He, uh, he doesn't wanna talk to you.
Fine by me.
- He does wanna speak with you.
- Huh.
Also, I'm, uh, I'm down a couple of
Traveler agents driving your people home.
Can you spare anyone to keep an eye
on the back of the property?
We can spare me.
Yeah, you can spare me, too.
Mm.
Agent 443.
Keep your comms open.
Jeff, I am so sorry
you got caught up in this.
I'd been investigating Vincent Ingram
for some time, and unfortunately...
Yeah, yeah, they told me all about it.
It all went down
because I'm close to Carly
and Carly's close to you.
So how close?
Okay. You want the truth?
Ms. Shannon has been working for me.
- The FBI?
- Yes.
Carly Shannon, FBI.
- For several months.
- I don't think so.
'Cause she... she don't got it in her.
Not my Carly.
But then again, my Carly's gone.
Because this girl, this girl's not Carly.
This girl's a completely different person.
And I don't know what you did...
but I don't like her much no more.
Judging by the condition of your face,
she doesn't like you much either.
That is funny.
Well, least we can laugh about it.
No, I don't want anything to do
with this girl, you can have her.
You sure?
'Cause I think she missed a spot.
- Keep it up.
- You're the one that wanted to talk.
I wanted you to know
that I remember things that
I didn't tell your boy upstairs about.
It's not all there yet.
Not all at once.
Just itty bitty pieces percolating
like the morning after
a night you been drinking.
Well, you'd know more about that
than I would.
But it'll come to me...
it will.
And the only thing that you need
to make it happen from there
is sunlight and water.
Food just rises up from the soil.
It's beautiful when you think about it,
you know. How...
Nothing out here.
Yeah, let's head back.
- We're being surveilled.
- By who?
Can't say who or how many,
but we saw some footprints.
Footprints, that's it?
We need to get proper reinforcements
and take them out.
Take them out?
What if it's nosy next door neighbors?
Wakefield's got a small army protecting
us, Carly. Dial it back a little.
One of the secondaries just passed through
the checkpoint. It's the cop.
We'll get the driver
at the same time we get their historian.
That's lockdown. Nobody else in or out.
This water is incredible.
Not recycled 10,000 times.
Well, I'm done.
The Director's code should allow
traveler teams to identify every copy
of your ill-conceived confessions
that's out there.
Thanks.
Although, the effort
hardly seems worth it.
No one from the 21st
would actually believe that...
What's wrong?
I, uh, thought that I saw...
Maybe I'm exhausted.
Was your transition here tiring?
Well, I was going through
heroin withdrawal, so...
How could you leave me behind like this?
I was assigned a mission.
You ran away.
- No.
- Because things are getting worse here.
I'm trying to save you!
It's already too late for me.
Simon?
What are you looking at?
My friend's not really there, is he?
No. We're alone.
Why would the Director do this to me?
It makes mistakes just like us.
Come on, you gotta try the food.
Carly and Trevor think
we're being surveilled.
- Faction?
- Wouldn't be the first time.
We've got plenty of cameras
set up outside.
The Director will take 'em out
if they get close.
- I can get Philip on some back up if...
- Mac, I got it covered.
Hell, I'll bring in air assets
if I have to.
Well, now you're just showing off.
They're upstairs waiting for you.
Kat's in the room
at the top of the stairs.
Hey.
I wanted to see you sooner,
but Wakefield insisted on debriefing you.
I've felt like this before, Grant.
- Like what?
- That I've lost something.
Time.
I woke up once months ago
feeling this way.
My head was pounding like it is now
and I couldn't remember anything
that happened the day before.
Remember the day your SUV was stolen?
You said I had too much to drink.
Well, you went at it pretty hard, Kat.
What do you want to me to say?
That you drugged me.
To make me forget something.
What are you trying to make me forget?
Jesus, Kat, why would I...?
Shit.
Guess I just have to try again.
No!
Hey.
- Hi.
They said I could,
I could talk to you now.
It's about time.
I've been asking for you all morning.
I'm sorry.
I'm going too fast.
No, it's okay. It's me, I'm just...
Come here.
Kat...
everything is gonna be like it was before.
I promise you.
I'm so sorry.
Let me see. Does it hurt?
This? Nah, you should see the other guy.
What other guy?
I have no idea,
I'm just assuming there was one.
Hey! Let's get out of here.
I'm craving sesame chicken
for some reason.
Okay, we can't just pretend
like this didn't happen.
You deal with this sort of thing
every day.
What's a minor kidnapping?
There's nothing minor about this.
I was on the other end of the phone
while you were giving CPR to somebody
after some explosion, for God's sakes!
I refuse to make this
a bigger deal than it is.
Okay, David.
You were held by a mass serial killer
who thought time travelers
were out to get him.
I know. Isn't that the stupidest thing
you've ever heard?
Uh-huh.
Go.
One of our assault teams was forced
to move early on a Serbian cell.
They were about to lose containment.
Casualties?
All five members of the Traveler team
confirmed dead.
Sir. You can't go ahead with this.
You have about 90 seconds
to change my mind.
Shit.
Tell Wakefield and get a weapon.
Mac, Wakefield's team
just bugged out of here
and there are soldiers taking up
positions all around us.
I know you need me
and I'll be there for you.
God damn you.
- I'll say it again,
- We've got company.
I'm Senior Special Agent Wakefield
and I need armed air assets
to these coordinates now.
They're not faction.
- I've got 20 armed men out there.
- No, you don't.
Most of 'em are already gone.
Then they're on to us.
Here.
Mac, we are outmanned and
out-gunned! Get your ass out here!
Kat, I'm sorry. I gotta go back outside.
- Wait... What?
- I'll be right back.
Okay, I need you to stay here
and stay away from the window.
The window? Okay, get behind me.
How do we know...
The last time the Director spoke to me,
it was not through an AI in Teslia's lab.
You received a messenger.
But it wasn't a child.
I was just told my mother
was essentially brain dead,
but it was gonna take time.
I wanted to be with her.
Last night, she spoke to me.
Listen to me carefully...
Tell him the bargain he made
that autumn morning
was not with his God, but with me.
Mom.
Those were her exact words.
She died in that moment.
It's not something
I'm ever likely to forget.
Sir?
This is the day.
- Get down.
- How many?
More than we can fight.
Where's Wakefield?
He's inside trying to get Traveler backup.
Maybe we should go back inside the house,
where there's cover...
We're not getting into a fire fight.
It won't be up to us.
The Director hasn't waived Protocol 3.
Fuck that.
They're on our six, too.
Sir, we're waiting on your order.
Sir.
Sir?
All units stand down.
Operation's canceled.
No go. I repeat, no go.
All units stand down and pull back
by order of Director Stevenson.
They're leaving.
What?
She's right.
Everybody out of here! Move!
Okay, lady.
Come on. You're free to go.
Go where?
I could care less.
Are you fucking kidding me?
That autumn morning,
I was also in a hospital room.
My daughter Claire
was dying from a rare form of cancer.
There was very little time left.
She spoke to you.
I will save her life,
but there will come a day of reckoning.
I never told a soul.
She began to improve the next morning.
I thought it was a miracle.
Daddy!
It was a miracle.
The Director cured her.
I've read reports
of their advanced technology.
Keeps me awake at night.
I wonder what made them stand down.
I have to believe the Director
had something to do with...
So... what's going on?
David, I told you to stay in the room.
Yeah, but then we didn't.
A jumpy junior agent got over-excited.
Honestly, it was nothing.
Why don't I believe you?
You made the right decision, sir.
We'll see.
So...
What do we do now?