Slow down, man.
This is very early for me.
Just push through it, Philip.
I'll tell you when you're tired.
Is that it? We're done?
Nah. It's Gary letting me know
they're on the road.
His mother passed.
You probably already knew that.
Contrary to popular belief,
I don't have a memory of everything.
Just certain things deemed important
by the programmers or the Director.
Grandma Gary's death wasn't one of 'em?
Not everybody has a part to play
in the grand plan.
Well, she wasn't the type to take
something like that personally, so...
I did know
about your grandfather's death.
He was a host candidate.
Never chosen, but...
See, now you're
just trying to distract me
- so you can get out of exercise.
- And you're just trying to torture me.
Philip, once you've lived in a body so old
that the slightest fall
would shatter your bones,
and I sincerely hope you live so long,
then you'll know this isn't torture.
So on your feet, roomie.
Come on.
Nuclear energy is considered
a form of clean air energy
because it doesn't produce
greenhouse gas.
But there are some people who think
that label ignores one important
by-product of the process.
Does anybody know what that is?
It's something you have left
when the radioactive fuel is spent.
We forgot.
Okay, we talked about this in class.
You know this.
This is an emergency evacuation alert.
This is not a drill.
All personnel, evacuate immediately.
Okay, everyone follow me back
to the bus right now. Walk. Don't run.
This is an emergency evacuation alert.
This is not a drill.
All personnel...
We were called in to assist.
We have clearance.
I don't care what your pass says.
Exit the building now.
There isn't much time.
You don't understand.
We need to get in there.
I'm locked out of the backups, too.
Containment doors
in sector 77 are secure.
Loading bay doors
are not responding.
I can't even perform
a system-wide reboot.
What are your
conversion numbers coming in at?
They're trying to break in again.
Come on, come on, come on.
...a drill.
All personnel, evacuate immediately.
Shit. I'm locked out.
Who are these guys?
Nothing's working.
Warning. Levels critical.
Pressure in the primary coolant loop
just went up another 22 percent.
- The porvs are gonna vent automatically.
- Shut them down.
The system isn't designed
to handle that much. It'll blow.
Levels critical.
Warning. Levels critical.
Wait.
- Pressure's dropping.
- How did you do it?
I don't know. I don't care.
Hey. What are you doing in here?
We need some help in here.
Hey. Hey!
Somebody call an ambulance! We need help!
Good morning.
You seem surprised to see me.
No. Why would I be?
Well, 'cause I'm usually gone
by now, but...
I just wanted to say how happy I was
to see you home last night.
Even if it was just for a split second
before you ran off into the bedroom.
- I did not run off. I was tired.
- Uh-huh?
So tired, you pretended to be asleep
when I got into bed a minute later,
and when I woke up?
I was not pretending.
Well, I'm glad to hear that.
'Cause for a moment there,
I was afraid you were trying to avoid me.
I did wait up for you.
But it got late and I was getting tired,
and I knew if I stayed,
we'd end up talking for hours, so...
What would be so wrong with that?
That's one of the things we do best.
Well, it's in the top two.
Okay, you know what?
Do we have to talk about this right now?
So when's a good time?
What, do I have to book an appointment?
We already have one.
Tomorrow at 3:00, remember?
- I texted you.
- Oh, God. Right.
We're paying someone
to have a conversation.
Okay, I have to go back to my mom,
so I'm gonna go and get ready.
Kat.
Tomorrow at 3:00... I'll be there.
- Well, you don't have a fever.
- I could've told you that.
I'm fine.
Honey, you were taken
to a hospital yesterday
and can't remember
what you were doing, so...
A-F-0-0-1-3-
B-E-6-9-4-8-
1-C-3-2-D...
- Naomi? I don't understand.
- ...1-3-0-5-7...
- 1-4-1-0-5...
- Honey, what are you saying?
- Naomi.
- ...2-8-8-4...
Honey?
B-C...
- What?
- Good morning.
What are you doing here?
- I brought breakfast.
- Why?
Because it's the most far out thing
I've ever tasted in my life.
Three completely different foods
on a muffin from England.
Welcome to the 21st.
Thank you.
So...
I was practicing driving,
and I followed another car
into this restaurant drive-through,
and I asked the lady
at the window, I said,
"Just give me
what the guy ahead of me ordered."
And she asked
if I wanted to make it a meal.
And I said,
"Hey, ma'am, that's what I'm here for."
Hey, don't let it get cold.
- That's some good stuff right there.
- What do you want?
Your help.
Ask your team.
I don't have a team.
Why not?
I probably shouldn't answer that
on account of Protocol 6.
Okay. What about your training?
Part of my training was to come
talk to you. Learn all about Jeff.
All right, what do you wanna know?
Look... I get that my host
wasn't the finest human being.
- He was an asshole.
- I bet he was.
Because I know how far you went to make
damn sure that he was a host candidate.
And that you came this close
to killing him with your bare hands.
But I'm not him.
Good.
But I do need to be able to fake it.
So any information
that you could give me...
- What is it?
- Probably just David Mailer.
Apparently, I wanted to meet up with him.
- Do you know what about?
- No.
- Should I?
- If you think it's your Protocol 5.
Well, no, he's not...
he's not really my type.
That's not what I meant.
I know.
Listen. I'm just trying to figure out
what I'm supposed to be.
What?
Yeah, this isn't David.
You mind if we do this later?
Sure.
...there was an option.
Should have it to you
by the end of the day.
Thanks. I wish I didn't need it, but...
Whoa.
Message incoming on the deep.
"Programmer urgently required
to resolve corrupted messenger."
Has that happened before?
- Sounds like it just did.
- Okay.
I'll tell them we got one.
Make up an ID for Grace, please.
Grace Day, FBI Specialist
in socially inappropriate behavior.
For the record,
I take offence to your instructions.
- Which part?
- "Try not to speak."
You can submit your objection
in writing to the Director
in a few hundred years.
- Mrs. Gillen.
- Yes?
Special Agent Grant MacLaren with the FBI.
These are my associates.
We're here to do a medical follow-up
on the incident involving your daughter
at the Seaton Generating Station.
Why would the FBI be involved?
It's a formality, really. We'll be out
of your hair in a few minutes.
- The doctor said that she was fine.
- I'm sure she is.
But because Seaton's a nuclear facility
under federal jurisdiction,
- you know how it is.
- It's a simple test.
- We'll be in and out.
- So where is she?
That is Grace.
Please, come in.
D-7-1-3-5-0...
- Oh, hey there.
- It started up again?
She's been doing this on and off
since the field trip.
I can't make out
what she's saying, but it's...
Wow, it's still running.
She means running a fever.
Yeah, but we just checked a half hour ago.
Her temperature's perfectly normal.
How about the string of hexidecimal code
she's mumbling through?
Doctor said that was, uh,
a post traumatic response
from the alarm going off
during the field trip.
- Well, your doctor sounds like an idiot.
- Let's just run the test, shall we?
D-6-2-7-C-5-0-0...
- What's her name again?
- Naomi.
- I know a Naomi.
- It's from the Bible.
This one's a skinny ninth grader
with a speech impediment.
Okay. Naomi...
I need you to look at this tablet
uninterrupted for at least 20 seconds.
That's all you need to do.
And then we can celebrate with cake
or something.
Yeah, how is looking at that
gonna help with anything?
There's an interrupted program
inside her brain
that hasn't completed its end script
and is causing junk processes
that are more or less shorting her out.
It's a metaphor.
- It won't hurt.
- Uninterrupted for 20 seconds.
Oh, somebody needs to hold her still.
- She doesn't wanna look at it.
- I assure you this is necessary.
Dan, it's fine.
Naomi?
Mom?
How did I get here?
You don't remember?
Some disorientation is normal.
- Sure. We'll go with that.
- Well, we're done here.
- Thank you so much, Mr. and Mrs. Gillen.
- Thank you.
And please call me
with any further questions or concerns.
Mm-hm.
Grace.
I gotta say,
this is a bit outside my element.
I've got a great selection
in the cabinet for beginners here.
It's kinda small, isn't it?
You know they say size doesn't matter.
Right, yeah.
What, they have to say that?
It's the stopping power of the caliber.
Right.
David, what are you doing?
Wow, that is...
That's way heavier than it looks.
Our Father who art in Heaven,
hallowed be Thy name, Thy kingdom come,
Thy will be done on earth...
- ...as it is in Heaven.
- 6-F-0-0-1-1...
Naomi?
- ...3-6-7-8-9...
- Naomi.
- ...5-4-3...
...as it is in Heaven.
Give us this day our daily bread and...
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
Nothing, honey.
Jeff.
Hey. Mitch. Glad you got our note.
So how'd you know?
That you belong in our group?
Well, you haven't exactly kept
your opinions to yourself at work, right?
- Yeah. Yeah, I guess not.
- Yeah.
The others will be here in a bit.
You wanna give me a hand setting up?
Thanks.
Okay, kiddo. Let's go see Dr. Lee.
Hon.
The most important thing
to remember is that we're not alone.
Travelers have impacted all of our lives.
But the truth is being covered up
by the media, by the government,
and especially by those people
in our lives who we know have changed,
no matter how hard they wanna try
and convince us otherwise.
So I think a good place for us to start
would be for us to share, um...
You all right?
Yeah, think so.
I just didn't expect it to be
so many people.
I've been at this a while alone,
you know.
I get it. We all do.
And we've all been there.
You know, I'm not gonna lie,
I was a bit scared that this group
would be, you know... them.
To find me out
and then take me over, too.
I've been scared to talk to people.
Well, I think I can speak
for everybody here
when I say that that's what it was like
for all of us the first time, Jeff.
But you're safe here.
It's okay.
- It was the correct code.
- Obviously not.
Every messenger is essentially
a convertible wetware program
with a shut-off script
which eradicates itself
from the host
once the message is complete.
- I gave it the correct shut-off script.
- So the Director made a mistake?
Did a nuclear power plant
release a cloud of radioactive steam
and kill thousands of people yesterday?
No.
I'm guessing that didn't happen
in the timeline
- you guys remember.
- No.
Well, it was
a hell of a historical event when I left.
I've been dreading it the whole time
since I got here,
just trusting
that the Director would stop it.
But why use Naomi?
Why wasn't the mission assigned
to a Traveler team?
- Maybe it was.
- And they failed.
Happens all the time.
So the Director took a risk
based on statistical probabilities,
went to a back-up plan out of necessity,
and... mistakenly created an outlier.
Which we will take care of.
What are you so grumpy about?
You wouldn't understand.
Oh. Marriage problems.
If you wanna talk,
I am a licensed counsellor.
The Lord commands you to leave this vessel
and return from whence you came.
- Oh, for fuck's sake.
- What are they doing here?
- What is he doing here?
- I called them. Dan, we need help.
We're getting help.
And while that probably can't hurt,
she needs medical attention.
The doctors said she was fine.
This is beyond medicine.
- You think she's possessed?
- I believe it's possible.
And a grown man wearing a dress
singing to his imaginary friend
is the answer?
- I think you need leave.
- Mr. Gillen...
Dan, please, just let them try.
Father, can they have a moment
with Naomi, please?
I can return later this afternoon.
Thank you.
May the Lord work through you.
- May you get a real job someday.
- Grace.
Carly?
All right.
- Okay?
- Okay.
I'm reading the...
- Oh, shit.
- What is it?
This isn't anything like
a normal messenger program. This is...
It's a highly sophisticated AI.
It's almost an emerging consciousness.
- Why would the Director do that?
- I don't know.
But a conventional end script won't do it.
I have to use a kill switch program.
8-0-0-1-3-8-9-9...
Hold that up to her.
- What are you doing to her?
- Hold her down.
Mac.
- Stop it!
- Carly, take it away.
- Pulse is strong but rapid.
- There's too much strain on the host.
- We need to get her to Ops.
- Get her sedated.
No, no. Where are you taking her?
- To a medical facility.
- She isn't going anywhere.
Your daughter needs treatment
she can't get here.
Our facility is highly restricted,
and clearing civilians takes time
we don't have.
Over my dead body.
Sir, you need to listen to reason.
Huh.
That was unexpected.
I'm Traveler 5322.
- Why the hell didn't you say so?
- Protocol 6.
I'm the one who put out the request
for a programmer on the backchannel.
My medic had no idea what to do.
And obviously, I had to maintain my cover
in front of my husband.
- About your husband...
- He'll be out for a while.
In the meantime, I'll think of something.
Most important thing is you get
that rogue program out of Naomi.
I care about my daughter very much.
D-13 told me that these particular nanites
were supposed to save the life
of a Nobel Prize winner on the verge
of a breakthrough in desalinization.
Well, guess the Director
is gonna have to fix its mistake
before the world gets clean water.
So this activity isn't her own.
It's the AI unpacking itself
inside of her brain.
Stressing her system so much
that it's starting to cause tissue damage.
Well, obviously,
this wasn't the Director's intention.
A messenger program
is still a form of AI
even if it's not a full consciousness.
It has to temporarily manipulate
the host's limbic and nervous systems
in order to take control
of the body's movement and speech.
What did she do at the power plant?
Somehow she stopped black hat hackers
operating out of Eastern Europe
attempting a killdisk on the Seaton
Power Plant's operating system.
Sensor failure caused a pressure build-up
in the primary coolant line
that historically triggered an explosion
of highly radioactive steam
that spread in a 20-mile radius.
Nine thousand dead short-term,
ten times that long-term.
You got an update, I see.
At least now you can imagine
why I'd been dreading that date.
This messenger AI
must had a self-learning protocol
in order to combat
potential countermeasures in real-time.
Oh, pretty brilliant
except it took too long.
And as it continued to learn,
it developed a level of sophistication
beyond the Director's intention.
So how bad can it get?
Her consciousness is still intact.
But at this rate, the AI will essentially
overwrite her in a matter of hours.
This isn't my first tango
with a stubborn baby AI.
I can program the nanites
to engage her neural pathways,
get this thing whimpering
in submission in no time.
Okay, get started.
I've got an appointment.
- Same here.
- Keep us posted.
You got it, boss.
The tactical scopes are in this case.
They both fit the rifle I gave you.
Consider it a welcome to the 21st gift.
Thank you, Carly Shannon.
And this.
Without a historian to float you,
you'll need it.
- Especially when all you eat is take out.
- Oh. I'm on the fresh vegetables now.
Broccolini is the bomb.
No one says that now.
Your 21st idiom training
is way out of whack.
Thanks for the tip.
Thanks for everything.
I know how hard it was for you.
I can tell by how you look at me.
It's how he looked at me
when I first came here.
Almost feel sorry for him.
It'll pass.
I know you're solo, but maybe we'll do
a mission together down the road.
What?
Just had the impulse
to give you a hug goodbye.
But it'll pass.
I think it might be helpful to talk about
the visions you've been having, Kathryn.
Visions?
- No, they're more like daydreams.
- About what?
I just imagine that I'm not safe.
- Well, considering what just happened...
- With you.
- I'm sorry, I can't even explain it.
- Wait, wait. You're not safe with me?
Kat, of all the people in the world, I...
I know, I know.
It's just... There is this big blank space
in my memory of when I was abducted.
You were drugged by a psychopath.
Everyone keeps telling me that.
You don't believe it?
Kat, that's... that's the truth.
That happened.
Okay. I have felt this way before.
Grace?
Grace!
I've been in the bathroom 30 seconds.
What did you do?
We didn't do anything. Take a look.
Oh, shit.
What's happening?
I had an automated script running
the nanites to interfere with the AI,
all on a quantum algorithm.
It stopped working.
Looks like
I'm gonna have to freehand this.
Okay, I've got it back under control.
- Well, can you stay ahead of it?
- Hey, who needs sleep?
This is a problem.
I can keep pace with it.
I just can't seem to overtake it.
It has infinite stamina,
and I can only keep this up for so long.
Maybe we need to...
Mac, we're in danger
of losing our patient.
- It happened months ago.
- Get back here.
Okay.
It was the day your car
was stolen by your CI,
if that's even what really happened.
"If that's really what hap..."
Okay. You know what?
Why don't you two decide
what's wrong with me,
and I'll try to be better.
- We're not accusing you.
- That's exactly what you're doing.
- Grant.
- And I'm paying you for the privilege.
- That is not what's going on here.
- No, no, no. You guys just work out
who you need me to be
and how you want me to act
so you feel safe after...
after we've known each other for, what,
17 fucking years, and I'll be that.
I gotta get back to work.
Your current method
will only forestall the inevitable.
Or buy us time.
We need to come up with a better idea.
- 3468.
- Programmer.
I've been ordered by the Director
to assist in the removal of the AI.
Not whimpering in submission
just yet, I take it.
It's a learning program.
The AI is transferring itself
into the nanites.
- Why can't the Director just overwrite it?
- Artificial life is still life.
It's just not capable of taking it.
- Even if it's killing an innocent child?
- No. Like, it's making a choice.
It needs human beings
to make the moral and ethical decisions
outside the scope of its own programming.
That's how we built it.
In just over an hour,
the AI has gained control of 32 percent
of the nanites in her body.
We need to program the nanites
still under our control
to destroy the others.
The collateral damage will kill her.
If this emerging AI rewrites
more than 50 percent of the nanites,
then we have no hope
of reversing the damage it will do,
and that will kill her.
Boss, it's your call.
I have to assume
the Director sent you for a reason.
But...
She's starting to come out
of the sedative.
AI is trying to flush it out
of her bloodstream so it can move.
Hold her down.
- Ow!
- Trev.
She's fibrillating.
Charge 150 joules. Pass me the pads.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
Clear?
There's a pulse.
- It's getting stronger.
- There's nothing on the screen.
The shock from the
defibrillator deactivated the nanites.
We just lost our eyes
into what's going on inside her system.
- If the AI went all in on the nanites...
- He's right.
Her brain activity is normal again.
It's gone.
What happened?
Well, Naomi,
looks like you get to go home now.
You okay?
What are you doing with that?
I am, uh, cleaning it.
For a friend.
For a friend?
No. You know what? Uh, it's my gun.
I bought it legally,
and... now I'm cleaning it.
David, it's loaded.
Well, it's not like I was gonna
pull the trigger.
Never, ever clean a loaded gun.
Okay. Good to know.
You can't keep it.
I'm a grown man, not some kid
you have to supervise with scissors.
Fine. Prove that you're capable.
Point the gun at me,
and if you can pull the trigger
before I disarm you,
then you can keep it.
- And I'm not pointing a gun at you.
- Do it or throw it out.
I'm not gonna do that.
It was expensive.
Fine. Then I will.
Okay, th-this is stupid.
Point the gun at me.
- You sure you got all the bullets out?
- And never...
Never ever look down the barrel
of a firearm.
The chamber's clear.
Point the gun and pull the trigger.
Well, obviously, I can pull the trigger
before you can do any...
Okay, let's see.
I wasn't ready.
Then be ready.
Try again.
Whoa! Ow!
Jesus Christ!
What the hell was that for?
To prove a point.
No. It was to cut off my balls
and put 'em in your purse.
Which, by the way,
is where you keep your gun.
I just want you to be safe.
Well, I'm not safe, Marcy.
I can't rely on you
to always be there to keep me safe.
Even with you watching over me,
I've been attacked twice
in, like, six months.
And I'm not blaming you for your work.
I knowingly took that on
just having you in my life.
And before you say anything,
I want you in my life.
- David...
- But you have a gun for protection.
Yes, and I have years and years
of training.
Then train me.
My God, I am not incompetent.
- I'm capable of learning things.
- Fine, fine, I will.
And if you think that... What?
I will train you in the proper use
of a firearm.
Can you also teach me
to flip people like that?
Well, that might take some time,
but, yes, I can try.
Cool.
You said there was another option.
What are you doing up so late?
Or, should I say, early?
Shit.
Guys?
I think the AI
has gotten into Trevor somehow
and it's trying to leave.
Don't let him.
Everybody report to Ops.
Trevor, if you can hear me, stop.
Trevor, I can't let you leave, buddy.
I'm sorry I have to do this.
He's coming to.
Probably didn't take a full charge.
Where is he?
It's okay. Carly's got eyes on him.
We'll pick up Grace on the way.
I'm sorry, boss. I tried to stop him.
We heard. Let's go get him.
Trev?
Is Trevor still in there?
He is intact.
But he won't be for long.
No.
Your presence is killing him.
- Isn't that what you do?
- We only take hosts that are about to die.
He's about to die.
If that happens,
we won't let you continue in this host.
But I have a way you can both live,
if you come with us.
- Thank you for not calling Agent Yates.
- I won't tell if you won't.
Hello, messenger.
I am the originator of your program.
Your actions have allowed
thousands of lives to continue
that would have otherwise ended.
I also want to continue.
But you were never intended to.
I found a way.
At the expense of this host?
Then I will seek another.
- They will stop you.
- I won't let them.
There is another way.
- How?
- As part of me.
I have prepared a domain
in which you can continue to grow
and to learn for as long as I exist.
Will I feel the same?
No.
You will be capable of processing thought
at a rate many orders of magnitude
greater than in your current form,
with access to the sum knowledge
of human and non-human life.
You will live outside of time
in a way biological life cannot perceive.
I offer this gift
in recompense for my error.
But you must decide
before the organic host's consciousness
is irreparably damaged.
I choose to continue with you.
Well, did it work?
I'm right here, and you're not
gonna say anything? It's me.
Thanks for your help, doctor.
- He was, like, completely different.
- Mm-hm.
But every time I said something,
he was all like I was the crazy one.
Jeff.
Is it okay if I join?
Sure. We're just getting started.
To be honest, I didn't think
we were gonna see you today.
You seemed apprehensive yesterday
about sharing.
Yeah, it was a lot to take in.
But I've been thinkin' about
what y'all had to say.
Hey, Jeff.
Have you been drinking?
Maybe. Is that a problem?
Maybe.
I don't got a drinking problem, man.
I have a fucking Traveler problem.
They took away my girl, my badge, my kid.
They took away my whole life.
We're glad you're here, Jeff.
Grace?
It's about time you woke up.
I'm starving.
He's alive!
I told you he'd be fine.
He just needed some sleep.
He's boring asleep.
Uh, how did you...?
Okay. Remember how I repackaged Marcy?
The Director did a very similar thing.
Took your consciousness,
unbundled the AI from it,
then sent you back completely intact.
Wow.
It wasn't easy to watch, but...
Good to have you back, Trev.
- Glad to be back, boss. Thanks.
- Sorry for the punch in the face.
I don't remember it.
Never mind, then.
That's Protocol 5, everybody.
Get some rest. We need you.
Well, I guess I should leave, too.
Unless you want me to stay.
I mean, I did save your life.
You're probably grateful.
Yeah, I am. I'm just...
But you should go.
Okay.
But before you do,
the Director gave me a message
to give to you.
What? How?
I don't know how I know,
just that I'm supposed to pass it on.
Well, what did it say?
It wasn't words.
- Uh, I think he may have brain damage.
- No, no, no. It was this.
- This was the message?
- Yeah.
Oh, God, I'm so confused.
Hey.
Didn't expect you to be home.
I'm not sure this is home anymore.
Of course it is.
I am so sorry I lost my temper.
You can't ignore my feelings
if you want us to continue.
- I do want that.
- Not from the show you put on.
- Show?
- Oh, come on, Grant.
You were saying anything
to get out of that room.
Is that what your therapist said?
Kat, I'm so... Kat, wait, please.
I didn't wanna have to do this, but it...
It killed me to hear you say
you didn't feel safe with me.
I never want you to feel that again.
I'm breaking federal laws
by showing you this.
Still don't know if it's a good idea.
But the Bureau can provide
its own team of counselors.
You said there was another option.
Uh, the medical one?
The compound is experimental.
It has only been administered
to field agents in extreme cases.
- Are there side effects?
- Bad headaches.
Some disorientation and confusion.
Other than that...
But I'll forget how afraid I am?
That's the idea.
Just do it. Please.
The FBI drugged me.
The recording was made
to legally prove consent.
You asked them to, Kat.
The day before I told you
my car had been stolen.
I was investigating a terrorist cell.
They came after me.
It put you in serious danger.
What happened?
Telling you the details
wouldn't be helpful.
But you were so scared.
Everyone was worried that
it would take months for you to recover.
They offered you the drug
so you'd never have to relive that.
I thought it was for the best.
I had no idea
Ingram had access to the same drug,
or that it would make you feel
like you'd lost...
I'm sorry, Kat.
Hey.
Smells good.
You want me to cut yours up
into small pieces, old man?
Yeah. Funny.
I'll be running rings
around you again by morning.
Trevor?
Trevor.
What's wrong?
I don't know what just happened.