Previously, on Travelers...
Where's the quantum frame?
When you reset the Director,
we lost the ability
to access the 21st.
We should be working together!
I don't think so.
The Director had its chance!
The Director's back up and running.
How many Faction are still here?
It's impossible to know
how many were sent
into the quantum frame.
Historically, Grace Day died today.
You jumped into the 21st illegally.
You took a host
that wasn't meant for you.
I had evidence that an attack
on the Director was imminent!
I had no choice but to act!
When you reset me,
you left out some things.
What'd you leave out, Grace?
Targeting far left.
T.E.L.L. established.
Stand by. Target two.
Traveler incoming on target one.
Take him out.
3468.
5401.
Yeah, he's dead.
We needed three to make it even.
He was gonna kill both of you.
Stay calm.
Stick to the plan.
I'll be right behind you.
What are you doing?
What do you mean? It's lunchtime.
You're supposed to be on sentry duty.
Oh, Jasper's still out there. It's fine.
No, it's not fine.
There could be Travelers out there.
They're in here now.
Don't.
Hands in the air.
Your protocols won't
let you take a life.
Protocol three's
been suspended
for members of the Faction.
I wouldn't risk it.
Weapons down, hands up.
Where's the quantum frame?
Not here.
Secure them.
What're you going to do with us?
That'll be up to the Director.
So death by overwrite.
You mean like you did to your hosts?
Our plan might have saved the future.
You people are pathetic.
Meaning we're capable of pity, sympathy,
or compassion for others?
I've really been enjoying
English class this year.
Yeah. I can see that.
Let's get moving.
Move.
Stay still.
Okay,
let's see what we can pull from this.
You won't find anything.
I don't know.
My people are pretty good at this.
Thanks, boss.
Be good at this.
Mm-hmm.
We can always try torture.
No, we couldn't.
They've been in hiding so long,
I doubt they know
where the frame is anyway.
Even if we knew, we wouldn't tell you.
So someone point a camera this way
and end this.
I'm good with that.
The Director has plans for them.
This is the first I'm hearing about it.
Because you are a part of those plans.
A hearing has been ordered.
Your presence,
along with 3569
and 0115, is required.
Where?
You'll receive the coordinates tomorrow.
To selling our house.
To selling our house over asking.
Yay!
We're officially homeless.
Well, I am.
Not till you finish packing.
I don't know
how you can drink that stuff.
Because I'm not allowed
to drink that stuff
and the calcium is good
for the development of bones.
You haven't touched
the almond milk I bought.
Grant, if there was ever
a time you were gonna lose
this vegan battle with me,
it's when I am pregnant.
Fair.
You know, I was thinking,
we should put some of the house money
into a trust fund,
for college tuition.
College?
That's years from now.
You need to learn to
think of the future.
Oh, I've...
uh, I have given that some thought.
And I think...
I'm gonna buy a boat with my half.
Given your history with the water,
I'd better take a life-insurance policy
out on you instead.
Ow. Break one arm one time...
Were you planning on going
back to the house tonight?
It's early.
Are you kicking me out already?
No.
I'm asking you to stay.
You haven't changed position
since I left last night.
Oh. No, I guess I haven't.
Find anything on their coms?
They've been all over the place.
This data is pretty much useless.
What about these points?
Looks like they frequented
these locations multiple times.
Maybe the frame's there.
Where the frame might have been,
not where it is now.
Well, there's gotta be CCTV
or traffic cams
in those areas.
Maybe you can pull the footage,
see if any of them picked anything up.
If the Faction left
anything on those cameras...
and hey, I wouldn't...
then the Director would've
already found it by now.
Mmph.
Something's bothering you.
Timeline has changed a lot.
My knowledge of the future
is becoming obsolete.
It's going to be hard to stay relevant.
You're more than just
the team's encyclopedia, Philip.
Who else am I gonna call
when I can't get Jeffrey's cartoons
to play on my phone?
So flattering.
Or make me music playlists.
Teach me about turtles.
The self-worth is just
coursing through my veins.
You're like the rest of us now.
Just a human being.
And that's okay.
I gotta go to work, but I'll com in.
Have a nice day.
Go for a walk!
Oh! My... God.
I guess we were making up for lost time.
Lost time?
I don't even know what day it is.
I know.
I'm gonna be in court all day, so...
I'll be hard to reach.
But I'll see you tonight?
How's that for an answer?
Grant?
I love you.
I love you, too.
3468.
Coordinates are as follows...
47.6050 degrees North,
by 122.3344 degrees West.
Why am I in the hallway?
Is it time for school?
Not yet.
Are you our new neighbor?
I guess I am.
Have a nice day, neighbor.
What are you doing here?
He asked first.
A messenger gave me
the coordinates for a hearing.
Scared me half to death.
Maybe it's their trial.
Shouldn't take long then.
All rise for the arrival
of the Tribunal Committee.
I'm Traveler 009.
You may refer to me as the Speaker.
I'm joined by Travelers 0017 and 0029.
They're programmers.
What the hell are all of you doing here?
Who's maintaining the Director?
0027.
We came to the 21st
as instructed by the Director.
Unlike yourself.
So that's what this is about?
0027...
you are charged with conspiracy
against the Director
and the high crime
of interrupting the Grand Plan.
I liked that one.
Can you add it to my playlist?
And just like that,
I am reduced to being Carly's DJ.
Something upbeat, please.
Any luck with the footage?
They wiped everything,
just like we thought.
I'm running serial numbers
of the weapons they were carrying.
Grasping at straws here.
They're bound to slip up,
and when they do,
we'll be ready for 'em.
Dropping by Ops after work?
No,
I gotta pick up Jeffrey from the sitter,
get some groceries...
bring my van to the mechanic.
I've been having trouble
starting it in the mornings.
Maybe I could be a mechanic.
I do live in a garage.
Stop it.
You are a valuable member of the team...
and a great DJ.
Next song, please.
3468, please take the stand.
Recount to us
how you first made contact with 0027.
I met Grace several months ago,
when my team was given a mission
to greet Traveler 0014,
Ellis.
Grace arrived
at the same time
and said her mission was to help Marcy.
But that was a lie, wasn't it?
No, it wasn't. I saved her life.
The defendant will
refrain from interjection.
If you refrain from leading questions!
Go ahead. He interrupted you.
Later, we learned she was actually here
to reset the Director
by taking advantage
of Marcy's new T.E.L.L.
And you were unaware
of this secondary objective?
She eventually told us. Prior to that,
we believed that
she was only here to save Marcy.
Which I did.
And for which I am deeply grateful.
You're welcome.
At any point,
did you suspect that she was
a member of the Faction?
In the future we left,
there was no Faction.
Protocol two has kept us in the dark.
We had no idea.
And who wrote protocol two?
Oh, come on! You know I did.
0027, please.
Teams in the 21st shouldn't be
made aware of every change in the future
because completion rates of our missions
would drop exponentially.
You have been asked by
the tribunal not to interject.
Operatives would
be paralyzed with the fear
of how their actions
could negatively affect
the people they left behind.
Enough!
I agree!
If I hadn't reset the Director,
the Faction would have corrupted it,
which means the Faction would
have control of the past.
What I did
was the only way
to save Marcy and the Director.
It was the Director
who ordered this hearing,
not any one of us.
Why?
It knows what really happened.
It knows what I sacrificed.
This... This makes no sense.
And yet here we are.
We will take a brief recess
to allow that fact to sink in.
Blair, hi, it's David. I...
Hi! You're still at home.
Yeah, I was just calling
to leave a message
to wish you a happy birthday,
so, uh, happy birthday.
Yeah.
Anyhoo, that's the one
and only reason I was calling,
so have a great...
A rave?
Oh.
No.
No, no, I don't, um...
I don't do raves.
It's just not my...
Tell you what, I'll say maybe.
And, uh...
Yeah. I'll try.
Yeah,
I'll-I'll try to maybe see you later.
Okay. Yeah, bye.
0115...
were you responsible
for interrupting Grace Day's
original T.E.L.L.?
I was.
Whose orders were you acting on?
No one's.
Then why'd you do it?
I didn't want her to die.
That simple.
As a Traveler,
you don't just inherit the host body,
you inherit the lives they've touched...
family, friends...
Grace Day was merely
a guidance counselor
at your host's high school.
That doesn't do her justice.
See, my host was a bully.
Cruel.
She tried to help him anyway.
She was there for him.
For me.
And historically,
she was supposed to die.
I rationalized
that one person wouldn't matter
to the Grand Plan,
but I was lying to myself.
I broke protocol
because she did matter to me...
and I'm willing
to accept the consequences.
Because of your actions,
locked out all transfers to the 21st
until she could send herself
into the host Grace Day,
halting the Traveler program
for four hours.
I couldn't just go into anyone.
Dozens of missions were canceled.
A Traveler was supposed
to arrive in Germany
and prevent
an impending train derailment.
All the passengers died.
A team meant to arrive in England
and stop a terrorist attack
was unable to transit.
I assumed the Director would choose
a new host
for the next scheduled Traveler.
The Grand Plan is fluid.
It's constantly shifting.
The Director is constantly analyzing
a myriad of outcomes
and course-correcting
to the fraction of a second.
Are you trying to school me
in the matrix of algorithms
the Director uses
to oversee the Traveler program?
For the last time, 0027.
If the crime is
disruption of the Grand Plan,
then I'm the one
who allowed that to happen.
I'm the one that should be punished.
The Director will
no doubt take it into account.
You may step down.
2103,
will you please take the stand?
Oh, seriously? That guy hates me.
Philip, I have a situation.
Hey, what's the good news?
Definitely not my paycheck.
How the hell do they expect
people to live on this?
And the capitalist-socialist
debate strikes again.
Well, this isn't enough for me
to cover my expenses this week.
Can you top me up?
Sure, let me see
what I can move around for you.
This can't be right.
What? What is it?
Something happened
to the market this morning
when I was out for a walk.
Our investments are down.
I'm scared to tell you how much.
How did that happen?
Most of our higher-risk investments
just crashed and burned.
We're in serious financial trouble.
This was a meeting Ken had
been preparing for a month.
I mean, he had...
he had note cards and everything.
And, uh...
Even had his hair slicked back,
which is a clear sign that,
you know, it's important.
You gonna get that?
Uh, no. No, I'm not.
Anyway, ahem.
So we're all sitting there,
and he stands up to do his presentation,
and his fly, it's wide open.
Oh, no.
Was his penis exposed?
Uh, no...
no, I mean, that would...
that would be...
But, anyway.
There's a window in his office,
and I think, midway through,
he must have caught his reflection...
Because he just...
he just knew,
and there was nothing
he could do about it,
but you could see him
debate it in his head, like...
"Do I do up my fly
while I'm still talking?"
Have I met Ken?
That's the funny thing...
you actually have.
You've actually
asked that question before.
Oh.
This looks good.
Blair! You're not allowed
to do this on your birthday.
He's so not worth it.
Hold onto me!
What's happening?
But, then, why did, um...
why did Ken change his mind?
I don't know.
I just, I came in
ready to pack up all my things,
and he told me I still had a job.
It's a mystery.
Do you want some more wine?
Um, maybe in a minute.
I'm just gonna use the bathroom.
Excuse me.
David, please!
Help me! Please, I need your help!
I'm locked in a stall!
They're trying to come in.
Please! Please, help me!
Uh... um.
Where are you going?
Uh...
Here, listen to this...
David, please! Help me!
Please, I need your help!
Wait! I'm coming with you.
Here.
And by a nose,
"Saladin's Vigil"
crosses the finish line.
And by a nose,
"Nemesis Star" crosses the finish line!
That was down to the wire.
"Outbreak Prime"
is well ahead in the lead
to win first place.
"Outbreak Prime" is well ahead...
but, now,
pulling up from the middle of the pack
is "Gjallahorn"!
Shit.
So what is a rave?
An illegal dance party with loud music,
drugs, alcohol.
Not that I've ever been to one.
I don't dance
so much as I rhythmically stand.
Wait...
if there's supposed to be loud music,
shouldn't we be hearing it by now?
Uh... yeah.
What, you just carry that around?
Yep.
Blair?
Hey.
What happened? Hey?
She's overdosing.
We need to get her
to a hospital and administer...
You just carry that around?
A lot of my clients
have addiction problems.
Hey...
David?
What happened?
We were in the bathroom...
People started screaming.
When I came out,
they all turned on me.
Give me your phone.
Okay, we're gonna get you to a hospital,
and you're gonna be okay, all right?
Hey...
I'm at a building at the corner
of 50th and Baker.
I don't know how they moved it so fast,
but the frame was here
less than an hour ago.
Who're you talking to?
Pull up the camera feeds.
I'll be right over.
Camera feeds?
You need to get her to a hospital.
I need to go.
Okay. Marcy!
9-1-1. What's your emergency?
They wiped all the footage
before they left again,
but we know for certain
that the frame was there.
Well,
thank God for the selfie generation.
Can you zoom in there?
Faction took everyone at the rave
except three women who were
apparently in the bathroom.
We found them overdosed,
probably a way of
eliminating them as witnesses.
And they survived?
David and I managed to save one of them,
but she didn't see anything.
But it's a safe bet
everyone else in the photo's
a Faction.
It makes sense,
but I don't know how you prove it.
Locate them, if you can.
We have to get back
to the hearing marathon.
How's that going? Can you say?
Not looking good for Grace.
Marcy...
how and why
did 0027 "repackage" your consciousness?
Well, obviously,
I don't actually remember,
but from what I was briefed on,
she showed me a code.
Something that Ellis created...
a backdoor hack,
which, during the repackaging process,
somehow managed to reset the Director.
Admittedly, a brilliant piece of work.
Thank you.
And how has that worked out for you,
Marcy,
this "reset" of your consciousness?
Uh, how is this relevant?
I restored her.
Do you feel restored, Marcy?
I no longer have seizures.
But do you feel as you did before?
No.
But that's partly
because I have no memory
of my time spent in the 21st prior.
There are... missing pieces, then?
Yes.
Marcy...
I've studied your M.R.I.s.
She had to have taken out
more than just a few months of memories.
What else did you take out?
I told you.
Redundancies, useless things.
Such as what?
Empathy? Emotions you lack?
Oh, shut up, 29.
You're practically a sociopath yourself.
How could you do that to me?
You would have died!
Yeah, but that would've been
my choice to make.
You used me.
Yes, I did!
I prevented your suicide.
Life is precious,
and so are skilled
operatives in the field.
I was just a means to an end.
Marcy, you're still you.
I swear to you.
I didn't take your soul.
How would you even know?
Carly, I think I found one
of the people in the picture.
Forget the first three.
What do you think of four and five?
Not a big fan of "Mason."
But it's so masculine.
Like a "stone mason."
It's also a jar
you keep pickles in.
What about your father's name?
Oh, Wilbur's the pig in Charlotte's Web.
And a Wright brother.
Watch out. I might be contagious.
I've built up an immunity.
How're you feeling?
Didn't you hear? I don't have feelings.
Yeah, you do.
I got you these.
What are they?
Try one. They're French.
At least if they throw the book at me,
I can say I've had
21st-century French cuisine.
Why are you being nice to me?
Do you know something?
No. No,
it's because we wouldn't even be here
if you hadn't reset the Director.
You gotta understand
that they'll come to
the same conclusion.
Trust the judgment
of those mouth-breathers?
Please.
Oh.
You need to take that?
Ah, it can wait.
Besides, I gotta do this.
Do what?
Bring it in, Grace! You need this.
I don't! Can we not...
Oh, it's happening.
Come on, there you go.
Okay. Thanks.
You can let go now.
Wasn't so bad, was it?
I do feel a slight
release of endorphins.
You see?
Do you have a regular sex partner?
You can't hate every one I come up with.
Well, we don't even know
if we're going to have a boy or girl!
You think I'm getting too excited.
You know what? You're right.
N-No.
No, I love to hear
the excitement in your voice...
when you're talking about new life.
Kat, I gotta get back into court.
Just... Just narrow it down
to the top 100 or so,
and we'll go through it tonight, okay?
Okay.
0027,
you have heard the charges against you.
What do you have to say in your defense?
I've given it a great deal of thought,
run the events over and over
in my mind a thousand times,
and to be honest...
You should all be thanking me.
Like my very dear friend
just pointed out...
Uh-oh.
If I hadn't have reset the Director,
none of you would be here right now.
The Director would be gone,
the Faction would have won,
and billions of people would
be dead from a horrible plague,
so...
You're welcome!
0027...
the members of the Tribunal
will now deliberate.
We will announce
your final verdict tomorrow.
We are adjourned.
May I help you?
Stacey Collins, we have a few questions.
How do you know my name?
You were at a rave last night.
Do you recognize this?
Where's the quantum frame?
You're standing right
beside it in the picture.
We know you're Faction.
What are you talking about?
We know you just arrived.
Maybe if you cooperate...
Who are you people?
Get away from me.
I'm calling the police.
Whoa! Carly.
She's Faction.
How do we prove it?
Who do we prove it to?
This is what happens when you improvise.
We can't just walk away.
That's exactly what we have to do.
But maybe we can follow
her or something.
Jesus! She actually called the cops!
Take care of yourself, okay?
I'll check in with you tomorrow.
Okay? Bye.
Yes, bye.
B... Bye-b...
Bye-bye.
You do know
Chinese food is my kryptonite.
Oh, I just...
I know you've been going back and forth
to the hospital all day,
so I wanted to bring you some dinner.
Yeah! Thank you.
I am starving.
How's Blair doing?
Right.
Well, we got there just in time.
It was a lethal dose of fentanyl.
On her birthday.
So they're gonna keep her
for the next couple days.
Mm.
You're looking at me funny. What?
I'm just trying to figure something out.
I'm sorry.
I wasn't 100% finished chewing.
Marcy, stop.
Why? What is it?
Let's, um...
let's not, okay?
You don't want to.
Oh, no, I do. I mean...
I really... but...
Not like this.
Not...
Not like an experiment
to see how it makes you feel.
Because I-I know...
I know how it made me feel
when we made love.
And it's as close as you can get
to another person
for 10 minutes.
I mean, an hour.
I want to feel that.
But you can't make yourself
feel something.
I mean, you either do or you...
you don't,
and I want you
to want to.
I know that sounds like a bad song title
from the '80s, but...
Should I just go?
No! No, stay.
Share this with me,
and we'll make some tea
and-and we'll talk,
like we do on Tuesdays.
What should we talk about?
With you, Marcy,
I could talk about anything.
0027, you've been charged
with conspiracy against the Director
and interruption of the Grand Plan.
You took a host
that wasn't intended for you,
and you halted
the Traveler program for...
You've already said all that!
Cut to the chase.
You've repeatedly stated
that your actions reset the Director
and freed it from corruption.
Because they did.
Then who corrupted
the Director in the first place?
The most powerful A.I. in history,
orders of magnitude more powerful
than the human brain?
Who would have that capability?
Obviously, a quantum programmer
of the highest caliber.
So only the best among us.
Yes.
And who might that be?
Don't say it.
Obviously me!
But I didn't corrupt the Director!
I was the one waving a red flag
while you three were
lining up at the yeast vats,
filling your bellies!
Traveler 0027,
your peers have reached
a unanimous verdict.
We find you guilty.
What?
Escort her to the sentencing room.
Wait! W-W-W-Wait. Wait, wait.
No, no, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no! MacLaren, do something!
I'm sorry, Grace.
Trevor, don't let them do this!
You can't help her, Trev!
But she's innocent!
Trevor! Help me!
She doesn't deserve this!
She didn't do much to help her case.
It's in the hands of the Director now.
Be seated.
Your sentencing will begin shortly.
What do you think will happen to her?
If the Director agrees
with the Tribunal,
she'll probably be overwritten.
Can I give you a ride home?
Oh, it's not that far.
I think I'll walk.
I need to clear my head.
You okay?
I'm fine.
Marcy?
May I speak with you?
Yes, of course, Programmer.
You may never get an apology from 0027,
but as a programmer,
I want you to know how sorry I am
for what happened to you.
Thank you, but that's not necessary.
Well, I think it is.
What 0027 did to you was criminal.
That sense of emptiness
that you must feel,
of not being whole...
It's offensive to me
that someone would do that to you
for their own agenda.
Well,
I guess she'll face the consequences.
But you shouldn't have to.
I think I can offer you
the missing pieces
that you've been looking for.
This is my field of expertise.
I don't understand.
My new team has been doing research
on preserving host memory.
In your case,
that would be your first iteration.
I thought those memories
were lost forever.
Perhaps not all.
Perhaps even the most powerful memories,
the most defining...
are still there,
and I can get them back for you.
When?
Well, as soon as you like.
Of course,
if you need time to think about it.
No, there's nothing to think about.
Uh...
Unfortunate, what must happen to Grace.
Is it?
In that it's a waste of intellect.
Returning to OPS now.
Bringing Marcy with me.
Half-hour out.
I'll be ready.
Are you here?
I am here, 0027.
Call me Grace.
I didn't betray you.
I would never betray you.
You, of anyone, should know that.
You are one
of four candidates,
although the probability of guilt
is
negligible.
Then why are you going to overwrite me?
Be patient.
I have not yet determined
who amongst you is the traitor.
No...
No!
Who did this?
I don't know.
Was this your team?
Well, the frame is powered,
it can still function.
I can still help you, Marcy.
We both know you're not
trying to help me.
You won't shoot.
You want Ellis's
backdoor code to take over the Director,
and you think it's still inside my head.
Listen to me, Marcy.
The future is at stake.
Drop your weapon!
What the hell happened?
Honestly?
I don't even think that he knows.
The situation
is now resolved.
0029 will be charged
with the crime of Treason
and sentenced immediately.
You used my trial
as an excuse to get
everyone here in the 21st,
to flush the traitor out?
The frame...
has also been neutralized.
You humiliated me.
I sacrificed everything for you,
I-I left everything I knew behind,
just to save you.
I'm sorry.
I hoped you would understand
it was necessary.
You're still gonna punish me,
aren't you?
I know I took the life
of this host after the fact,
I know I interrupted the Grand Plan.
Ellis is dead because of me.
But I can never go back.
Isn't that punishment enough?
More than enough...
I owe you my life.
Thank you for saving me, Grace.
I shall miss you.
Traveler 0029, you have been
charged with the crime of treason.
You're on the wrong side of history,
MacLaren.
And you have been found guilty.
And the Director will sentence you now.
Ahh!
Welcome to the 21st.
Boss?
Make every fragment
of it unrecognizable.
It's over then?
I'm not so sure.
Who killed all of them?