Previously, on Travelers...
It could correct your condition.
What about all my memories of the 21st?
Obviously, none of that.
I loved you so much.
They're his memories, not yours.
If something doesn't work out
the way you want it to,
why don't you just go
back and try again?
We can only go as far back
as the arrival point
of the most recent Traveler.
There's no do-overs.
Messengers count.
Messengers cause
the same ripples in space-time
as Travelers.
She won't be me.
She won't remember...
the most important part of who I am now.
I'll meet you outside Ops.
Copy that.
Oh! That's the boss!
Road trip.
You're such a kid.
Yeah, on the outside.
What's that? Boop!
What a freak, man.
What?
Oh...
Wow. They're beautiful.
Thank you.
Mom.
Mom remembered.
"Happy...
"anniversary...
Grant."
No service?
Not one bar.
Should've called when
we stopped at that gas station.
Told you.
Yeah, then we got lost.
How long till impact?
23 minutes, 6 seconds.
Ish?
No, pretty much exactly.
I'll have to call her after the mission.
I don't understand the big deal
about anniversaries anyway.
My father missed their 25th
a few months back.
And?
Gary paid a heavy price, boss.
Fortunately, Kat's a reasonable person.
Ah, reason's got nothin' to do with it.
You're already in the doghouse.
Oh, come on.
No, she's right.
Your window was early this morning.
It's already closed.
How do you know this information?
Covered it in training.
"21st-Century Female Behavior."
Ah. Well, I'll buy her flowers, then.
What anniversary is it?
10 years.
Yikes.
Whoa.
Ah, you're screwing with me now.
No, 10's a big one. Even I know that.
Okay, well, help me out.
What's an appropriate gift for 10 years?
Tin.
Yeah, 10.
No, "tin."
As in the metal.
Tin?
That's the traditional gift.
I'm supposed to give her
something made from tin?
If you're a traditionalist, yes.
There's a more modern
anniversary theme for 10 years,
but you're not gonna like it.
Diamonds.
Now I know you're making this up.
Technically, diamond jewelry.
Yes.
Seriously?
You might've gotten away...
With flowers, if you'd called.
"Get away with flowers if you called."
Where does it come down?
600 meters to our south-southwest,
in seven minutes, eight seconds.
There-ish.
It's amazing
this becomes a dry lakebed in 50 years.
Do we need to worry about a wave?
Nah.
Probably a splash, but it's not too big.
Just extremely rare and important
to the future.
More rare than that other mineral...
what was it?
Diamond?
That's the one.
All right, all right.
Let's get the recovery gear ready
and make sure everything's working.
The Director gave us
an important mission.
Let's get it right.
No!
Ah!
You've reached
Special Agent Grant MacLaren.
Please leave a message.
Wakefield.
This is an emergency communication,
Protocol Alpha.
Protocol Alpha? Who is this?
This is Traveler 5001.
We have less than 60 seconds
before signal loss.
I'm listening.
I need armed air assets
to the following coordinates A.S.A.P...
49.3506 degrees north,
122.8599 degrees west.
Can you do this?
Possibly. I have a helicopter
already in the air with agents aboard,
but they're not Travelers.
I said Protocol Alpha!
Can you get them to these coordinates
in 17 minutes?
Negative. Best case is... is 25 to 30.
What about assets on the ground?
25 minutes is our closest anything.
You're talking the middle of nowhere.
I do have agents on the ground
within roughly...
Hello?
Give me your keys!
Heh. Right.
How 'bout we just wait
till your little brother touches down?
It's an emergency! Give me the keys.
They're in the ignition.
Wait. What emergency?
Carrie, what's wrong?
Just tell me what's going on!
I'll drive you myself!
Carrie!
Wayne! Your sister just took my car!
You've reached Special Agent
Grant MacLaren.
Please leave a...
No service?
Not one bar.
Should've called
when we stopped at that gas station.
I told you.
Yeah, then we got lost.
How long till meteor impact?
22 minutes, 51 seconds.
Ish?
No, pretty much exactly.
I'll call her after the mission.
I don't understand the big deal about
anniversaries anyway.
My father forgot their 25th
a few months back.
And?
Gary paid a heavy price, boss.
Luckily, Kat's a reasonable person.
Reason's got nothing to do with it.
You're already doomed.
Oh, my gosh. That's a big gun.
Um...
am I on private property right now?
I'm so lost.
You... You want me to go back?
Okay, I can... I can do that.
Um, can you just tell me
where Alouette Lake is?
Are you telling me
the lake's back that way,
or are you still telling me
to turn around?
Okay.
Jesus.
Callahan!
What is it?
Where did the Fraser meteor come down?
A dry lakebed just north-east of here.
Why?
It wasn't dry this early in the 21st.
What's going on?
I just got off the phone with a Traveler
who requested armed assets
to the exact same coordinates
the meteor was historically found
50 years from now.
We got cut off,
but she said it was Protocol Alpha.
How's that possible?
What would've happened if Robert Fraser
hadn't discovered that element in 2068?
There'd be no
room-temperature superconductor
for quantum processing,
no leap in artificial intelligence,
no consciousness-transfer technology...
No Director.
Do we know when the meteor came down?
I'm no historian,
but I'm about to bet my job at the FBI
that it's sometime
in the next 15 minutes,
and that the Faction is trying
to get to it before we do.
The Director overwrote
all the Faction members.
Only the Faction members
it could get eyes on.
There could be hundreds still out there,
or worse, it's somebody else.
Hey! What the hell?
You all right?
Amazing to me
this becomes a dry lakebed in 50 years.
Do we need to worry about a wave?
Nah. Probably a splash.
Nothing too big.
Just extremely rare
and important to the future.
Even more rare than
that other mineral...
what is it again?
You mean diamond?
That's it.
All right,
let's get the recovery gear ready
and make sure everything's working.
The Director gave us
an important mission.
Let's not mess it up.
Get back from the water!
Carrie!
Carrie, what's wrong?
Buddy, open your chute...
Wayne! Open your chute!
God.
Oh, no. Oh, no, no, no, no! No, no!
Wayne? Wayne!
Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh...
Carrie!
What're you doing?
Carrie, what's wrong?
Well, then, help me out.
What's an appropriate gift for 10 years?
Tin.
Yeah, 10.
No, tin.
Like soup tin?
As in the metallic element.
That's the traditional gift.
I'm supposed to give her
something made from tin?
You cut that deployment close.
What happened?
We collided. He's unconscious,
but I managed to get his parachute open
before we separated.
If he lands like that,
he'll break his neck.
Do you have any weapons in the car?
What?
Weapons.
No.
What are you doing?
The camera saw a knife in the pickup.
What?
Carrie!
Hey. This place is where?
I'm lost. Can you help me?
O-Okay.
Fine, but... this place is where?
I need to know.
Might've gotten away
with flowers if you'd called.
Yeah, we established I made a mistake.
Now you got to get her
a diamond-something.
Really?
Explain how buying
something hard and shiny,
and artificially expensive,
because it's controlled by a cartel,
gets me out of the dog pound.
"Doghouse."
Were you trained at all
in 21st-century male behavior?
I think he's nailing it.
Historically, diamonds have always been
a rare and precious gift.
Oh, shut up.
Solve your own problems then.
Yeah,
but if it's rare and precious she wants,
I'll chip a fragment off the meteor
after we recover it.
It could come in handy
if Kathryn ever needs
a high-temperature superconductor
for quantum processing.
You shut up, too.
Hey! What the hell?
Asshole.
You've reached
Special Agent Grant MacLaren.
Please leave a message.
Hey, it's me.
Just giving you
the benefit of the doubt here.
I know you're probably busy on a case
and I married an FBI agent,
but I'm assuming,
when you write "won't be by tonight,
work"
in a text,
it just means that you're gonna be late,
because tonight, of all nights,
we should spend some time together
no matter what time it is.
Hint, hint.
Okay, so...
I'm gonna plan something for later,
nothing fancy.
You just need to let me know
roughly when that will be.
You can even text me.
I'll be here.
Bye.
MacLaren!
You're in danger!
All right, well,
let's get the recovery gear ready,
make sure everything's working.
The Director
gave us an important mission.
Let's not screw it up.
MacLaren!
Did you hear that?
What?
Your team is in danger!
MacLaren!
Run!
Carrie?
Get off the beach!
What're you doing here?
Traveler 500...
Oh, God!
Carrie, pull your chute.
Carrie!
What happened up there?
We collided.
Then Wayne must be unconscious.
Give me your keys.
Wait, what?
Your keys.
No. You're hurt!
I need to go.
No, no, no. You're not going anywhere.
You're staying right here.
The future is at stake.
No, you got a concussion.
But the faction is gonna win
if we do not act.
Okay, whatever.
Just... Just don't move, okay?
Your brother's in trouble.
He's gonna break his neck.
What happened?
Did you crash into each other?
Too much strain on the host.
What? What?
There are five people on a remote beach.
It's not far...
Who?
Doesn't matter.
Listen.
You need to help them. I can't make it.
You're not making any sense.
Everything is at stake.
You need to do this.
Do what? Do what?
I-I don't understand!
The coordinates.
Y-You need...
You... You need to...
Carrie?
Carrie.
Oh, God...
Oh, God.
Oh, God!
Well,
if it's rare and precious she wants,
I'll chip a fragment off the meteor
after we recover it.
It could come in handy
if Kathryn ever needs
a high-temperature superconductor
for a quantum frame.
You shut up too.
Are you sure this is it?
This is the place.
It sure doesn't look
anything like the pictures
when it was found.
This is beautiful.
Yeah, it's nice.
Nice? This is like seeing Niagara Falls
before it went dry,
or the Great Valley
before the domes were built.
Yeah. I said it was nice.
She's not wrong.
Car keys! Give me the keys!
Oh, my God. Wayne, she's dead.
Give me the keys!
You've reached
Special Agent Grant MacLaren.
Please leave a message.
Hello, Special Agent Grant MacLaren.
This is your apparently-not-so-special
wife of 10 years,
as of today.
10 years, Grant.
I left you a phone message
and I sent you a "Happy
Anniversary" text
before that,
but neither really cover
the range of emotion
that I'm feeling at the moment.
All I can say is,
you bloody well better be
shopping in a jewelry store right now
that happens to have
shitty cell phone reception.
Call me back when you get this.
Yeah, I said it was nice.
She's not wrong.
This is 026. Inbound with a full load.
About an hour out.
026, copy. See you then.
Piece of shit.
Got a sec?
Yeah.
Is everything all right?
If you mean with Kat
and the pregnancy...
The pills you gave me...
This isn't the time...
Or the place.
No, I know.
I was going to ask about you.
I'm fine.
I don't think you are.
Part of the team leader's job
is to have some inkling
about the general welfare...
I said that I was fine.
You're not fine.
You're unhappy.
Look, Marcy,
you can't possibly remember this, but...
I didn't want to be reset?
Someone told you?
We should just get back to the mission.
No. There's plenty of time.
Let them take care of it.
Look, I didn't see the good
in telling you that information,
and maybe I was wrong,
but it's pretty obvious to me,
and probably everyone else,
that the new Marcy is different
from the old one
in ways she wouldn't approve.
She?
That's your word.
Well, hers.
I just...
I just can't help but feel
that I'm not really...
What?
Whole.
That, when Grace
sent my consciousness to the future,
repackaged it,
and then sent it back again,
that she left out what...
made me "me".
That very day,
you told me you were afraid of losing
the most important part
of who you had become
in your short time in the 21st.
How do I even know what that is?
I don't think it's my place to say,
but...
I can give you a hint.
After that plane crash
that should've killed me,
when you and a million nanites
were trying to put me back together...
my own consciousness
took refuge in the memories
of Grant MacLaren.
Well, that's not possible.
There are none.
Only a few.
Disconnected fragments.
Of what?
Of how much Grant MacLaren
loved his wife.
Memories even his death couldn't erase.
How do I possibly access that?
You're the doctor.
Where does it come down?
600 meters to our south-southwest.
Killer day, huh?
Yeah. Yeah. It's... killer.
What's are you guys up to?
Uh, heading up to a lake,
do a little camping.
Fishing!
Fishing.
What about you? What are you up to?
About 15,000 feet.
We're going skydiving.
Oh! That sounds... terrifying.
You know, it's...
Oh, yeah. No. It'll clear up.
You know, statistically,
it's actually safer than driving.
So people tell me.
You should try it sometime.
No. I'm not...
I'm not so good with things in the sky.
Okay.
Gotta fly, Carrie.
See you later.
Yeah, have fun... Carrie.
Isn't she a little young for you?
And I'm married. I know.
Uh, speaking of which...
your wife just texted you,
saying "Happy Anniversary".
What? Shit!
You might wanna give her a call.
Didn't have any fresh fruit like
you asked,
so I got you something
called a "fruit pie" instead.
Has the word "fruit" in it.
Sure does.
Thanks, Trev. That's great.
Whoa! Turn it up!
This is my favorite part!
No, you'll just sing louder.
Don't roll your eyes at me!
Back to where I was before
Bye-bye, baby
Well, the problem is, when I said turn,
you didn't turn.
The GPS said there's no road.
Well, there's one on the map.
So we'll turn around.
Okay.
There's lots of time.
Thank you.
Are you sure this is it?
This is the place.
Sure doesn't look anything like
the pictures when it was found.
This is beautiful.
Marcy, you can't possibly remember this,
but...
I didn't want to be reset?
Someone told you?
We should just get back to the mission.
No. There's plenty of time.
Let them take care of it.
Look. I didn't see the good
in telling you that information,
and maybe I was wrong,
but it's pretty obvious to me,
and probably everyone else,
that the new Marcy
is different from the old one
in ways she wouldn't approve.
That very day,
you told me you were afraid of losing
the most important part
of who you had become
in your short time in the 21st.
How do I even know what that is?
I don't think it's my place to say,
but...
I can give you a hint.
After the plane crash
that should've killed me,
when you and a million nanites
were trying to put me back together...
my own consciousness
took refuge in the memories
of Grant MacLaren.
But how do I possibly access that?
You're the doctor.
MacLaren!
Did you hear that?
Ohh!
MacLaren!
Identify yourself.
Traveler 5008.
I'm on a Protocol Alpha mission...
We know, it's all over.
Marcy, all clear!
No, one more down the road.
I had to go around him.
I took care of him first.
We did it.
Thank you both.
That was close.
You don't know how close.
We weren't the first.
We had to keep trying.
How many times?
I was the ninth volunteer.
Jesus.
If the element ended up
in the hands of the Faction,
the whole Traveler
program might never...
See? Just a splash.
Our mission is to recover
and secure the meteorite
upon impact, so...
We'll stay here and watch
your back till you're done.
I'll have him patched up by then.
There's one other thing.
We have your next mission.