Previously on Travelers...
- [MARCY]: Who is she?
- 0092.
She's not born
for hundreds of years from now.
A few of the patients
who have gone though
your treatment haven't...
Returned to the ward?
If you're open to it,
I could use your help.
Let go of me!
There was a malfunction.
Some information was lost
during the scan.
Don't be afraid, dear.
I only want to make you whole again.
[SIMON]: Marcy?
Did it work this time?
Do you know who did this?
[♪♪♪]
[KATHRYN]: Grant...
Grant?
Mm-hmm?
Oh, Grant, we are not spending that much
on football tickets!
Have you seen the seats?
This is a bargain.
Do not get caught in a bidding war.
Kat, it's for charity.
Think of the children.
I wonder how my steak knives are doing.
No. Grant...
Doesn't cost nothing to look.
Shit, I'm sorry, that was my fault.
Let me get you another one.
Do you want another one, too?
I'm going to get you one.
I'll get us all one.
My husband doesn't get out much.
Neither do I...
This is a great event.
Do you work for the hospital?
Someone my wife was very close to
received care here.
We became supporters.
You?
We live nearby.
I donated a chair.
You endowed a new position.
[LAUGHS]
Sorry. No...
I literally gave them a chair...
I'm a designer.
Is the chair in the auction?
It is,
and I would be very happy
to show it to you, Mr...?
Ingram.
But please call me Vincent.
Kathryn.
Um...
It doesn't have any bids, unfortunately.
Well, we'll have to see
what we can do about that.
My wife always put us down
for all...
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
...all... all the auction items
that could use a little support.
[KATHRYN]: She sounds lovely.
[VINCENT]: She was. Unfortunately, she...
Forgive me, this work
has left me speechless.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Apparently, these were created
by one of the patients.
[♪♪♪]
[MAN]: Do you see a piece
you like, Mr. Ingram?
All of them.
I'll buy all of them.
[♪♪♪]
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
Beth, where's the Petrov file?
Excuse me?
All my material on the Petrov case...
it was right here.
It was reassigned.
Why?
We weren't expecting you all week.
Well, I'm here.
I can see that,
but no one would think
worse of you if you weren't.
What is that supposed to mean?
Nothing, I was just trying to be nice.
Here.
Knock yourself out.
[DAVID]: He keeps to himself mostly.
He has some issues with coherent thought,
but, hey, who doesn't?
[MARCY]: How long have you known him?
About a year, year and a half?
I met him, actually,
not long after I met you...
He's a good person inside,
he just doesn't trust many people.
Paranoid? Delusional?
Oh, yeah.
He's on a mission from the Director.
Whatever that means.
[MARCY]: Hey, here's some more.
[DAVID]: They look new.
Just finished.
Hi, Marcy.
I like your hair. It looks nice.
♪ In the shadows of denial... ♪
♪ You are hiding from the world ♪
♪ All the promise on your horizon... ♪♪
[MUSIC STARTS TO SLOW DOWN AND DISTORT]
[DISTORTED MUSIC PLAYING]
[CARLY, ON COM]: Philip?
[MUSIC SPEEDS UP, DISTORTED]
[CARLY]: Philip!
Can you change the song, please?
I'm not your DJ, Carly.
[CARLY]: This song is so slow.
- I'm not your DJ.
- [POPS PILL CONTAINER]
[CARLY]: But you're so good at it.
♪ ...Right where you belong ♪
♪ Were you too far gone? ♪
♪ Na, Na, Na, Na Na, Na, Na, Na ♪
♪ Na, Na... ♪♪
[POP TUNE PLAYING]
Thank you!
You say something?
Hmm?
I like those moves.
I'll see you tonight?
Hey.
You bring it on yourself.
You know, I should have asked
if you wanted to drive,
give you the practice.
[CHUCKLES]
In a few years,
cars're going to be driving themselves.
That's true.
You know, your mother and I
heard about what's going on
with your coach at school.
Nobody had any idea that was happening.
He seemed like a normal guy.
I hope he fries... sick bastard.
Anyway...
I want you to know
that we're here for you
if you ever want
to talk about it or whatever.
We'd feel awful if anything like that...
You don't have to worry, Gary.
It didn't happen to me.
Yeah, good.
Good.
That's what I figured.
No way, not my son.
[♪♪♪]
So strange to see these in the 21st...
I remember him from the institution.
You do?
Host memories from a long time ago.
Which means he's several years
into a psychotic existence.
Hey, Simon.
Simon, this is a friend of mine,
he has a couple questions for you.
[SIMON]: Questions, yeah, right.
You got a gun,
I can see it.
I see everything.
[MACLAREN]: And I'm on your side, Simon.
Can you tell me your traveler number?
Do you remember
any of the rest of your team
or where they might be?
[CARLY]: I checked the area
in the shelter where he sleeps.
Seems like he's been on his own
for a while.
You want what's in my head,
but there's just so much
that you don't understand.
You might be surprised
what we can understand.
Okay, so you know
that an emission of Hawking radiation
concerns two mutually
entangled particles?
Who doesn't?
And if that particle enters a black hole,
it emits a finite amount of information,
leaving you with what?
A paradox!
The monogamy of entanglement
requires that the outgoing particle
be fixed inside two independent systems
at the same time!
Definitely upper echelon.
Probably a specialist.
Is that right, Simon?
Are you a specialist?
Yes, I am,
and if you don't believe me,
ask the Director!
- Ask the...
- [VINCENT]: Simon!
Shut up.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- Hey, Simon? Simon...
- No. I can't.
He's here.
Who's here?
I can't!
That's Vincent Ingram.
[MACLAREN]: Yes, it is.
How do you know that? You never met.
There are no photographs.
He was at the institution.
He experimented on patients.
And you remember that?
He's 001.
What?
- [VINCENT]: Simon.
- I didn't say anything!
[VINCENT]: I told you, Simon.
- I was very clear.
- No!
[VINCENT]: You know what you have to do.
- I don't want to!
- You have to.
Now I have to take extreme measures...
[CARLY]: Hey, whoa, whoa!
He has a weapon!
[PHILIP]: Simon, take it easy!
Stop him!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
[MARCY]: You're okay. It's okay.
Lower him down.
You're okay.
What'd I miss?
Sorry, it's a bitch getting here.
Can we meet at an easier place next time?
Crazy how small they're getting, right?
Can I get another one next week?
Next week?
I can try, but...
I gotta ask,
what are you doing with all this stuff?
[VINCENT]: Don't tell him.
What did you just say to me?
I said just what are you building?
I mean, I just hope
it's nothing, like, illegal.
I'll see what I can find,
but I can't promise anything!
[VINCENT]: Simon...
Simon... Simon...
Simon...
Simon!
What are you doing here?
You need to leave.
Hey.
Marcy said you'd be feeling
better when you woke up,
but there's still a few hours
left to go before dawn.
You can relax now, by the way.
You're safe here.
Oh, shit.
Oh, come on.
[KATHRYN]: Grant?
Sorry. I...
It's 4:00 in the morning.
There's a sound...
What sound?
It's like a clicking. There's a clicking.
There. There.
The lamp's on a security timer.
Oh.
Now will you please come back to bed?
Yeah.
Oh, no. Shh.
We can take turns being the strong one.
Morning. I didn't want to...
That's a new interface.
It's cleaner.
And it's in color.
Color?
Do you mind if I...?
Sure...
Multi-homed...
asymmetric crypto...
Hello?
[TYPING RAPIDLY]
No...
[SIRENS APPROACHING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[♪♪♪]
[SIRENS APPROACHING]
[DOGS BARKING, HELICOPTER APPROACHING]
[SIRENS WAILING]
I surrender!
[SILENCE]
[SOBBING]
Hi.
Hey.
Are you okay?
I don't know.
Just tell me what's wrong.
Maybe I can help.
All right, I'll just get right to it.
So I've been away and you've been home,
and that's totally fine.
Yeah...
And I've been learning all this new stuff
and meeting new friends,
having these experiences,
and... it feels good, you know?
But then I come back home
and everything's the same,
but it's not.
I don't know what I'm trying to say.
You're breaking up with me.
No, I'm not...
Am I?
Yeah. You're growing...
into the woman you're going to become,
and that's exciting.
You don't have to leave.
No, for sure,
it's just that you told me
it was an emergency,
so I kinda dropped
everything I was doing...
Yeah, it's an emergency
for our relationship!
I don't even know what I want right now.
I understand.
Just take all the time you need.
You'll make the right decision.
[PHILIP]: Boss?
Go ahead.
You're going to want to see this.
[ELEVATOR CHIMES]
Agent MacLaren.
David, what do you need?
I'm just...
Yeah, I just had some questions.
They're mostly about Marcy...
Mostly?
All.
I'll ride down with you.
- I wrote them down...
- Yeah, I can see that.
Uh, has Marcy's situation
changed at work?
You know I can't talk about our work.
Right, but in general,
is she under more stress?
Maybe she's dealing with
a difficult situation?
"Have I noticed
a sudden personality change?"
"Is she giving away
any personal possessions?"
This one here seems to be...
that's more of a statement...
What is this about?
Okay, well, I've had
some training in this,
and recently,
I've witnessed some signs
of self-destructive behavior.
I'm well aware
of what happened with Marcy,
- if that's what you're asking?
- With the tub and the ice...
I know how that must have looked,
but that wasn't self-destructive,
it was experimental.
Cutting-edge science...
It was extremely dangerous...
Look, would I have approved? No.
Do I understand why she did it?
Yeah, I do.
So should you.
[ELEVATOR CHIMES]
Come on.
We have some new information.
Simon was one of the first Travelers.
004.
His mission was to set up
our communication infrastructure.
So what happened?
Schizophrenia manifests
itself later in life.
He was sent into a compromised host.
How well do you understand the Internet?
I'm good with languages.
Okay, well, broadly speaking,
there are four layers:
application, transport,
Internet, and physical.
One of the first things
that Simon did when he arrived
was create a whole new physical layer.
A dedicated backbone that piggybacks
off cell phone networks and
communications satellites.
Our back channel in the deep web.
Turns out our back
channel also has layers.
He's watching you.
Vincent's spying on us there, too.
He's using secret layers
in the back channel
for secure communication
and to spy on other travelers.
[PHILIP]: That's the bad news.
The good news is, now that we know,
we think we can use it against him
to find out where he's hiding.
Show me.
He presented very classically:
persecutory delusions,
fear of authority and surveillance...
The neuroleptics leveled him out,
and we've been working on
the other stuff ever since.
He believes he was sent from the future
on a mission to save the Earth.
He literally doesn't think
he's living in his own body.
The art therapy has been
a successful intervention.
As you know, he's a natural talent.
Simon, you have a visitor.
This is the man I was telling you about.
Hello, Simon.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Dr. Carroll...
would it be possible
for me to speak with Simon alone?
You wouldn't be in any danger,
if that's what you're worried about.
[VINCENT]: I'd like
to talk about his work
and I want him to feel free to open up.
Well, I suppose I could go
grab us some coffees.
Simon, will you be nice to our visitor?
Mr. Ingram is a close friend
of the institution.
You're not supposed to be here.
Simon, you heard what Dr. Carroll said.
You were supposed to die
in the North Tower.
You know who I am.
I know that voice,
we searched for it for years.
Then you also know
that I'm important to the program, Simon.
I'm the very first traveler.
The Director is not happy.
You were supposed to die.
Not anymore.
The Director gave me a new mission.
What mission?
The Director feels terrible
for what happened to you
and wants to fix it.
It sent me to help you.
We're going to make you
whole again, Simon.
[PHILIP]: There are
16 continental switches
on the back channel,
but only four that handle
sub-channel traffic.
Simon helped me set up alerts
to log any suspicious network activity.
So what are we looking at?
[PHILIP]: This is Vincent
communicating
with somebody late last night.
- With who?
- We don't know.
What does it say?
We don't know that either...
So where's it going?
[TREVOR]: We don't know
where it was sent or received.
Hops are encrypted along the sub-channels
as well as at both ends of the pipe.
Except for this one.
He's getting a call.
Well, grab it.
[TREVOR]: It looks like
the access point is unsecure.
We might be getting a phone number...
[PHONE RINGING]
This isn't the last phone I sent you.
Those phones are meant for
your safety as well as mine.
[DR. PERROW]: I can't find that one.
This won't take long.
Vincent, you need
a more thorough treatment regimen,
one that at least allows for
the possibility of medication.
No. I don't need drugs,
I just need to talk!
We have an appointment.
And I'm calling to cancel it.
That is unacceptable.
Vincent, I'm sorry.
I can recommend...
No. I don't want to talk
with anyone else,
I just want to talk with you!
And I will, just as we agreed!
Goodbye, Vincent.
Please don't contact me again.
[TREVOR]: Call's over.
We got the originating number.
Good.
I've gotta get back to the Bureau.
You track down that location.
Everybody else, Protocol 5.
The minute we find out
where Vincent is hiding,
we're going to knock down
his goddamn door.
Hey, Carly, hold up.
What?
I was thinking maybe you could stay.
For?
Protection?
I gotta pee.
I think you got this.
Bye, Philip!
Oh, Mr. Ingram?
Mr. Ingram.
I'm so glad I caught you.
I just wanted to thank you
for the personal interest
you've taken in Simon's care.
Oh, I'm happy to help.
But I'd also like to talk to you
about all the equipment
you've been bringing in...
Surplus electronic parts
from my various companies.
Most of it isn't even functional.
Still, Simon's convinced
it will help
with his "consciousness issue".
Is that what he's saying now?
Of course, the problem is,
we have procedure to follow...
Safety and compliance,
various approval committees...
I understand.
These things are expensive and take time.
Hopefully, this will address
the first problem.
Perhaps you can help me with the second.
This is very generous.
Not at all.
Charity is a gift you give yourself.
Have a nice weekend, Doctor.
Marcy?
In here!
I'm making dinner.
Really?
It's just, I've never seen you
cook before.
It's dinner, David,
it's not brain surgery.
It's pasta.
Yeah.
How long's this been on?
Not long enough
to boil off the water yet.
There's definitely still water in there.
I had a late lunch, so there's no rush.
You surprise me every time you do that.
Shit, I'm sorry.
You're avoiding me.
No, I'm just...
I'm...
I see it when you look at me.
I remind you of what happened.
And I'm not taking it personally,
but it does convince me
that we need this.
Take out?
This is caponata...
this is moussaka, that's for me...
And this is Mexican,
because there are
no Spanish places around here.
We just sold our house
and you have a ton
of vacation saved, so...
Palermo,
Santorini,
Barcelona.
You need a break, Grant, we both do.
We take off
for a couple of months,
spend a ridiculous amount of money,
and hit reset on our entire life.
That would be...
incredible.
But you can't imagine
leaving work for that long.
I know.
Which is why I started thinking
about a different plan,
one that costs just as much
and...
will definitely reset
the hell out of everything.
Adoption...
It's still too soon
to be diving in, I know,
but we could at least
start talking about it.
It never would have occurred to me.
Meaning what?
Meaning I think it's a good idea.
[JEFF]: Carly.
Carly!
What... What is this?
Are you drunk?
Yeah, I mean, I had a couple drinks.
What do you want? You want me
to disrespect my boss on his birthday?
Jeffery's sleeping,
and you're drunk.
I'm not dealing with this right now.
Oh, you're not dealing right now?
How long are you going to hang
this over my head, Carly?
Come on, I been good,
and you know it.
Thought you were the one
that was sleeping around.
Okay. Get out.
I'm not going anywhere.
Don't touch me again, Jeff.
Hey, come on. I been good. You owe me.
Owe you?
Am I gonna get some or what?
Never, Jeff.
Not now, not ever.
Stop it.
Okay. Okay, okay. Okay.
Stay down.
You shouldn'ta done that.
Stay down!
I said, stay down!
[PHILIP, ON COM]:
♪ When you're smiling... ♪
Not now.
♪ The whole world smiles with you... ♪
♪ When you're laughing... ♪
- ♪ When you're laughing... ♪
- Not now.
[JEFFERY CRYING]
Damn it!
♪ ...The sun comes shining through... ♪
♪ But when you're smiling... ♪
[JEFFERY CRYING]
♪ The whole world... ♪
♪ ...Smiles with you... ♪♪
Morning.
Hi.
Were you watching me sleep?
You try looking at yourself some time,
it's hard not to.
You're ridiculous.
I am ridiculous.
I'm glad you stayed.
This place is much cozier
than the place I've been staying, so.
Are you using me for my duvet?
I'm sorry it's taken me so long
to find my way back.
Well, to be fair...
I was kinda playing hard to get.
So help me understand.
How could whatever it was you were doing
make things better?
I mean, even if
you can't tell me the top-secret details.
Well, for example,
do you remember when we played
the "Operation" game
and you said you were
a better doctor than me?
Because I do.
- You do?
- Mm-hmm.
There's a lot of things that I...
I remember...
Most of which I can't tell you,
but...
I can tell you that...
I love you.
You have no idea how happy that makes me.
Do you remember that you owe me $20?
Oh, I'll go get it.
Oh, no. I'm kidding!
I'm kidding.
I wonder if that pasta is ready.
Probably.
[LAUGHS]
[DOOR OPENS]
[CARLY]: Hey, look, you survived.
Yeah.
He started seeing
Vincent again in the night,
but at least I got him
to start wearing pants.
Mm-hmm.
How about you? How are things at home?
I knew it.
Ow!
That wasn't a random call.
What? I was up! I was bored!
Bullshit.
You knew something was going to happen.
How? That's impossible.
I don't know how,
but you knew.
The timing was too perfect.
What was I going to do?
Was I going to go to jail?
Was I going to kill him?
How is Jeff?
He'll live.
Probably won't even remember it.
So what are you going to do?
[DOOR OPENS]
Hey. You got something?
The phone that called Vincent
was a burner:
paid for in cash,
no user info.
But I was able to use its IMEI
along with cell tower data
to find the neighborhood
that it was last used.
[TREVOR]: Fancy part of town.
Right, which made this next part easier.
Most people who live in this area
are upstanding citizens
who have actual names
attached to their phones.
Narrow the search to nameless devices...
and our list drops close to zero.
Simon and I spent the night
checking security footage
at these locations
and came up with our prime suspect...
Katrina Perrow:
specializes in treating panic disorders,
social anxiety and agoraphobia.
Text me the address.
Carly, you're with me.
Yup.
[VINCENT]: You've been given
every resource to make this work!
[SIMON]: We need more time.
We need to be operating
at the exascale, minimum.
- The meteor will...
- [VINCENT]: I told you... I told you...
I keep telling you...
the meteor doesn't happen for years.
Then we find another way, right?
Look, we've got the node clusters,
the math libraries,
we just need a qubit engine
and a field generator...
Where are we going to get that, Simon?
- The Director!
- Oh!
- This was a mistake.
- No...
- I've wasted so much time...
- No, we just need the plans.
No. We're finished here.
We've hurt so many people!
We hurt Marcy!
Just ask the Director for the materials!
Ask the Director!
[PHILIP]: Why didn't
the Director help him?
Afterwards, I mean?
Why'd it abandon him?
Probably for the same reason
it sent my consciousness...
yours, too, for that matter...
into a compromised host...
it didn't know.
No records from the institution
made it out of the 21st.
Vincent covered his tracks.
[SIMON]: I want to go home.
What's that?
Can I go home now?
Can I ask about...
No.
Dr. Perrow?
I'm Special Agent Grant MacLaren,
and this is my associate, Carly Shannon.
We'd like to speak to you
about one of your patients.
The FBI has been monitoring
Vincent Ingram for some time.
[CARLY]: We know all about
his paranoid delusions,
and, unfortunately,
he's starting to act on them.
[DR. PERROW]: He's hurt someone.
[MACLAREN]: Yes, and we believe
it will continue.
I didn't know.
I would have reported it.
None of that matters now.
We're just interested in stopping him.
Our professional relationship
deteriorated.
I just called him
to cancel an appointment.
We're aware of your phone call.
We want you to keep that appointment.
What?
Why?
Ingram is in hiding.
You want me to keep my appointment
and you're going to follow me?
We have a device.
It's completely untraceable,
but it will allow us to be
in constant communication.
You mean like a wire?
[MACLAREN]: Little more
high-tech than that.
Will you help us?
I just got out of a board meeting,
and they told me that
you are withdrawing funding.
I told them that this must be
some kind of mistake.
It's not a mistake.
At least give us more time.
A more gradual reduction
of funds would allow us to...
I'm sorry, I've made my decision.
The institute has come
to rely on your generosity.
Whole programs will be shuttered.
And what about the patients?
A lot of them will be put
out on the street.
Well, then it's fortunate
you care so much
and I've been able
to compensate you so well
over the years.
You can take my place as a benefactor.
All right.
This should be enough
to last you for a while.
Give us a call when you need more,
you know how to find us.
I'm glad it worked, Marcy.
Glad what worked?
The device in room 21C.
I thought you were gone forever,
but then you got better.
Maybe I can get better, too.
Okay. Take care of yourself, okay?
[CAR ENGINE STARTS]
[PHILIP]: Okay, the car's
approaching now.
Good luck.
All right, she's leaving the city.
Signal looks good.
[TREVOR]: Yeah. We see that, too.
Following at a safe distance.
[CARLY]: Dr. Perrow,
you activated your com.
Is everything all right?
It's fine.
[CARLY]: We're right behind you.
All you need to do is lead us there
and we'll do the rest.
It's a fine day out there.
[♪♪♪]
[MACLAREN]: There it is.
[TREVOR]: GPS says she's inside.
[CARLY]: I was going to say
we need to deactivate the cameras,
but I don't see any.
In fact, I don't even think
this barn has any power.
Makes sense if you want to hide
from the Director.
Why do these things
always end up in barns?
Philip, you got Perrow's com?
She's holding position.
This is a message
for Agent Grant MacLaren.
I was acting on Agent MacLaren's behalf
in an unsanctioned operation.
I was found out
and will be released unharmed,
along with my daughter...
As long as Agent MacLaren
presents himself
to these coordinates
in the next two hours.
He must come alone
and on time...
or I will never be heard from again.
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com