Previously on Travelers...
I know.
What?
That you're pregnant.
Your son was involved in a shooting.
He may not regain the use of his legs.
Ow!
Eye drops.
Synthetic compound
to help with the heroin addition.
Jenny, by the way.
Jeffrey Jr. is in the hands
of Washington Family Services.
No! He needs to be with his mother!
Destroy the device, Walt.
I'm Traveler 4112.
Artificial Intelligence
isn't supposed to be capable
of taking a life
that isn't about to end.
The Director shouldn't have risked it!
Don't you understand?
Why do you think
that they're still after you?
Because they've already found me twice.
And they'll be coming for me.
Hey. Hey.
Thanks for picking me up.
I know you're working.
No problem.
Have you told Walt?
I haven't told anybody.
[Traveler 2150]: No.
Don't. I can't. I can't.
I can't. No. I can't.
Don't.
Please!
You.
You bastard, we're after you.
No.
Please.
What?
Hit a snag in the basement.
Pipe leaking water.
Show me.
Get a sledge.
Agent MacLaren.
Alive and well.
Officer Boyd.
I'm very glad to see
your vest worked as advertised.
Yeah, you didn't have to shoot twice.
Sorry. Professional instinct.
He's with us now.
4112.
What the hell happened in there?
Exactly what happened to my team.
Except these four weren't rescued.
I can't imagine
who'd do something like this.
When I last saw you,
you said something about
some faction in the future
that exists now.
The faction's been around for years.
It started as a movement in...
Shelter 41, I know.
Shelter 41 collapsed.
Not in the future he came from.
Least it was there when I left.
Guys, I think we need to keep
Protocol 2 in mind here.
Right. Well, this couldn't be
the work of the faction anyway.
Why not?
You told me, when my team went missing,
that you'd seen this kind of thing
happening long before
I arrived in the 21st.
The faction didn't exist when I left.
I always assumed it was the Director.
There's no way the Director's
capable of what we just saw in there.
Isn't letting it happen just as bad?
When can my team have the scene?
Forensics will be
another few hours at least.
But, after that, it's all yours.
Trev?
I don't want you to feel down
on account of this thing taking months.
You shouldn't feel down either, Gary.
I know, I know, but I can't help it.
I mean...
kid, you used to fly!
If you had pressure in the pocket,
you would just put on those afterburners
and blow right through the defense.
That was a thing to watch.
Must be hard for you.
It is.
It's really hard.
You'll get through it.
I know you will.
Thanks, son.
Hey...
You too.
Know what?
This... this is good right here.
I can walk from here.
Thank you.
You okay?
Yeah, I got it.
Thanks for the lift, Dad.
Dr. Thomson,
you're needed ...in Radiology 2.
Dr. Thomson in Radiology 2.
You're up next.
Excellent photography.
Dr. Barker. How are you doing today?
Great. You?
Oh, fine, thanks.
Great. That's really, uh...
I should probably...
Oh. Yeah, uh...
Don't... Don't let me get in your way.
I was just gonna ask, uh...
You're busy,
Uh, I'll come by later.
Okay. Are you sure?
Yeah. Yeah. I've... I've got a...
But I will definitely...
Okay.
You too.
I mean, uh...
Right this way.
You don't think I would've
told you if we had a mission?
Well, maybe another team got one.
It's been a long time.
2,163 hours.
Not that I'm counting.
You really are an optimist.
Yeah. Yeah, I really am.
You can quit if you want.
Five.
Time.
All right!
We did it!
I just thought you might want
a little bit of human contact.
Oh...
Two minutes recovery
and then we go again.
No problem.
A construction site
in the area of Edmondville.
Four missing persons reports
came to a heartbreaking conclusion today
as a demolition team found their bodies
in an abandoned building.
Out of respect for the families,
police have yet to release any names,
however, foul play has been assumed.
Adena Moore is at the site now.
Adena, are you able to give us
any details on what happened there?
Well, what we're looking at now...
That's the smell of death.
Police forensics came up with nothing.
Your turn.
Trevor and I kind of
just threw this together...
But it should work.
Sorry! Set too high.
We're good.
Hey! I got a com over here.
Get out of the building now!
Go.
Go!
Go. Go, go! Go!
Morning.
Mm.
Smells delicious.
You never cooked this much
when we were together before.
You just never liked my cooking.
Oh, you're definitely a better cook,
but...
It's like you're a different person now.
Nope. Same guy.
On the outside, maybe.
Yeah, and on the inside,
nougat and caramel.
Otherwise,
I am the same guy you broke up with.
I didn't know what I had, David.
Same guy.
Hey! I'm trying to give you
a compliment here, okay?
You're... you're more confident.
I used to be able to read you,
but it feels like
there's so much more going on
in there now.
It's mysterious.
You don't know mysterious.
You know,
there's an ingredient in these eggs
that's gonna blow your mind.
You okay?
Yeah, I'll be fine. It'll... It'll pass.
Blair, this keeps happening.
Let's get you in to see a doctor.
I'm fine. Really.
Ah!
Okay, that's enough.
Let's go.
Hey, Carly?
It's hard for me to focus
with you pacing around
with a gun in your hand.
Sorry.
It's okay.
So judging by the T.E.L.L.
of these four host candidates,
I think I've figured out
who our group was.
A team of five just like us.
Which leaves one member unaccounted for.
Traveler 2192.
Let's find them.
If they're still alive.
I think I can narrow it down
by checking which candidates didn't die
the day 2192 arrived.
This com isn't telling me much,
other than it's been all over the place.
Get that com working.
Look, I'm sorry,
but we've already contacted
all of the victims' families.
But Jacob went missing
at the same time as those other people.
I mean, isn't it possible
that there were more victims?
No, there were only
four found at that location,
and none of them were named Jacob,
ma'am.
I am sorry.
Beth, Beth.
Let me. Let me to talk to her.
If you say so.
Special Agent Grant MacLaren.
Come on in here.
We'll talk privately.
Thank you.
Have a seat, Mrs...?
Ward. Sylvie.
You say
your husband's been
missing for some time?
Three and a half months.
That... That is a long time.
The police haven't been
able to find anything.
I don't even think
they're looking anymore.
What can you tell me about him?
Jacob's wonderful.
I mean,
we had our troubles through the years,
but lately,
the last year and a half or so,
our marriage has never been better.
What changed?
Before,
he was loud, he smoked like a fiend.
He wasn't health-conscious at all.
But I always knew
that he would come around,
and he did.
Almost overnight,
his priorities completely realigned.
He became more attentive,
compassionate...
Did you ever see him
in the company of
any of the other victims?
He didn't run away with another woman,
if that's what you're thinking.
That's not what I'm thinking.
I'm just wondering
if there's a connection.
Say, in the workplace?
Jacob didn't believe in bringing
his work home with him.
He said that was our time.
And you've had no communication
with your husband's cell phone?
Any activity in his bank accounts?
No. Nothing.
But I believe that he is still alive,
Agent MacLaren.
I have to.
Didn't you just take some of that?
She said to take it as needed,
and I need to focus.
Does Marcy know what's in this?
It's Marcy-approved.
Let's get back to work.
You guys there?
Yeah, boss, what's up?
I got a name on our fifth traveler.
Jacob Ward.
We're on it.
Philip, I want you to put
a tap on his wife's cell phone.
Sylvie Ward.
She just paid me a visit.
I'll text you the address.
Will do, boss.
Shit!
I gotta go.
I'm sure Carly
will be here any minute now.
Her new job's...
been a little crazy.
In the meantime, how are you doing?
Fine.
Lot of change in your life.
How's that going?
Ah, that's all good.
Just living through the changes.
When Carly's here,
I sometimes get the impression
that you're going out
of your way to agree with her.
Might be useful to use this time,
while we have it, to talk about you.
Ahem.
Yeah, I can do that.
Okay.
Do that.
How much do you know about guilt?
I am so sorry I'm late.
Hey... there she is!
Traffic was just...
Ahh!
Well, you're here now.
Ahem. So...
big week for you two.
Your final custody assessment from CPS.
How are the two of you feeling?
Good.
Yeah, it's really good.
Really good.
That's good.
Marce!
Hi!
I've been looking everywhere for you.
Uh, is everything all right?
Yeah.
Everything's fine.
No. Um...
I got back together with... with Blair.
And, um...
Good for you.
I wasn't looking for you
to tell you that,
but I think there might be
something wrong with her.
Uh, well, did you take her to admitting?
Yeah, see, that was the original plan,
but then I learned
she doesn't have insurance.
Um... But she's been having
these harsh stomach pains
for over a week now,
and I'm worried that if
she doesn't get it looked at...
David, I...
I'm just an x-ray technician.
I think we both know
that that's not true.
Besides, I think an x-ray's
exactly what she does need.
Right. Uh...
Bring her to imaging in block "C".
Thank you.
You two are really gonna hit it off.
Hey, Boss.
Hey. What have you got?
You were right. Our man, Jacob,
is definitely our missing traveler.
He went off the grid sometime mid-May.
If he's still out there,
he's good at hiding.
Any action on the wife's cell?
There's already a tap on her line.
Someone else is watching her besides us.
Trevor, you got that com working yet?
Ready when you are.
Hello?
This is Traveler 3468.
2192, are you there?
How did you get on this channel?
I'm sure you've heard by now...
the rest of your team is dead.
We found this com at the crime scene.
We want to help.
Is your mission
from the Director to assist me?
No. But my team was captured,
the same as yours.
I think it's important that...
Then stand down!
Do you have a tap
on your wife's cell phone?
What?
Someone besides us
is tracking your wife.
Is it you?
Jacob?
He's still there.
The signal's still strong.
He's cutting out his com.
Do not remove your com! Jacob!
Your wife is in trouble!
Jacob!
We lost him.
Okay.
Keep monitoring her phone.
I think I know where he's going.
Hi.
You found something, didn't you?
Uh...
The scans did show
a foreign mass in her stomach.
Oh, God, here we go.
I'm afraid to even guess at what...
You don't have to.
It's cotton balls.
Cotton balls?
How could she possibly have ingested...
It's a weight-loss thing...
It's supposed to make you feel fuller.
I don't know.
David,
I don't think that you realize how...
I know.
And not to mention
unbelievably dangerous.
I mean,
she's lucky she didn't eat enough
to cause an obstruction.
Yeah, that's what happened last time.
All right. Uh...
We'll get her stomach pumped
and she'll be on her way,
but you cannot let her...
I know, I know.
I know.
I'll talk to her.
Um...
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Agent MacLaren. Is there news?
Actually,
I was hoping Jacob had contacted you.
Contacted? I haven't heard a thing.
Mind if I come in?
Is everything all right?
I hope so.
I just have a few more questions.
I just... I'm late for an appointment.
Maybe I could drop by your office later?
How did you break this?
I told you to leave me alone!
Jacob!
I'm here to help you!
He's running! Back stairs!
Jacob!
You all right?
Stop it! I'm Traveler 3465.
We're here to help you.
And you're making that
awfully goddamn difficult.
You people have no idea what
you're getting yourselves into!
Traveler teams from all over the world
are being abducted and tortured.
We know.
The Director assigned us
to investigate their disappearances,
but they found us before we could...
It's bad.
Marcy, drop what you're doing.
Get back to Ops.
You got a patient.
Keep your eyes open.
We're getting you to our medic.
Call Sylvie.
You need to tell us what you know.
What did your team find out?
Who's behind this?
Whoever it is...
they cover their tracks.
We do know that the buildings...
every one Travelers were taken to,
all... all a-around the world...
What about the buildings?
They're owned by numbered companies.
Sh-Sh... Shells...
but under one conglomerate.
Give us a name, Jacob!
Jacob! Jacob!
His lung's collapsed.
We need to re-inflate it.
Carly?
He needs shock.
Charge?
Mm-hmm.
Clear.
Charge again.
He's gone.
Hello?
Hey, it's me.
What a total surprise.
Funny.
Hey, before I drop by tonight,
you want me to stop at the grocery store
and pick up anything special,
craving-wise?
Oh...
Um... Yes!
Some kind of smoked meat.
Meat.
I need the iron!
What's the smoke for?
Nobody craves broccoli, Grant.
You're the one who offered.
Kat, someone's on the other line.
I'll call you back.
Mm-hmm. Okay.
MacLaren.
Okay, so, the sole owner
of the company that owns that building
is Vincent Ingram.
He's got an estate
about an hour from downtown.
I let one of his people know
that you were on your way.
Okay, great. Thanks, Beth.
Text me the address.
Just did.
Hi.
Have you seen my eye drops?
Nope.
I just got here.
You were the last person
who had them yesterday,
when we were working.
I didn't take your drops, Philip. Relax.
What's that supposed to mean?
Uh...
look around.
Just give them back.
What's going on, man?
I know you're trying to monitor me.
I can take care of myself,
so just back off
and give me back my drops.
Here.
Ahem.
Jeez.
It's a good thing
these are helping with your addiction,
huh?
Jeez.
Hey. This is Marcy. Leave a message.
Hey, Marce...y.
Uh, I just wanted to say thanks again
for your help with Blair.
Uh, I really appreciate it,
and she's doing better, so...
Um...
Anyway, uh,
I was hoping that you could, uh,
you could join me...
me and Blair, for dinner tonight,
as a way to say thank you.
Uh, so if you're free,
that would be great,
to see you.
I know I just saw you,
but it would be...
it'd great to see you again.
I do, like, a fish dish now.
Uh, "Branzini."
I know you like white fish
and all those Omega-3s.
No cotton balls, I promise.
Anyway, uh...
All this to say I hope you can join me.
Us...
I mean,
because Blair will be there, too.
And you...
I hope.
Oh, for God's sakes.
But we've grown up a lot.
And Carly's an amazing woman,
and I'm thankful every day
that she's a part of my life.
How's your landscaping job going?
Still great.
I see that neither of you
have missed a session
with your counselor.
How have they been going?
Very helpful.
Good, yeah. Very.
Tell me how.
Well, I was...
angry.
And hurt.
But, by talking things through,
we found out that we were both angry.
We just didn't have
as much to be mad about
as we thought we did.
The counseling has
helped me forgive Jeff.
And to not let the past stop me
from seeing who he is now.
I have to admit,
you're doing very well
at keeping up the act.
Oh, please.
I've been doing this a long time.
You can't fool me.
Jacqueline...
But it's not necessarily a bad thing.
It means you want to try.
Most marriages include
at least a little bit of faking it,
trust me.
I can see how much this means
to the both of you,
and how committed you are.
You may not ever be great spouses,
but...
I think you could be good parents.
This way.
Special Agent Grant MacLaren.
My office called.
I apologize for the conditions
of entry into my house.
Please, don't take it personally.
That's all right, Mr. Ingram.
Special Agent MacLaren.
Have we ever met, Agent MacLaren?
Well, I usually remember
the people who decline to shake my hand.
How do you close your business deals?
Through a legal representative.
And a large transfer of money.
I'm investigating the four bodies
that were found in the basement
of the building at 46 Henderson Avenue.
Why are you speaking to me?
One of your companies owns the property.
I suppose, on paper,
that's technically true,
though I think the company
that leased it from me
would be better able to provide you
with the day-to-day operations.
Have you spoken to them?
Not yet.
If an employee of a Microsoft store
was involved in a criminal act,
even a serious one,
would most FBI agents think
to question Bill Gates?
The four victims
were tortured extensively
and over an extended period of time,
so I hope you won't take it personally
if I'm being thorough.
Well,
I don't know how much use I can be.
I've never seen the building
or stepped foot inside,
and I operate
all of my business remotely.
I never leave this house.
Never?
My therapist encourages me to be blunt.
I'm agoraphobic, germophobic,
and I don't like personal contact.
Well,
I'm very sorry that I have to be here.
You don't.
You're naturally curious
about the wealthy recluse,
and your badge gets you in my door.
That is blunt.
Please, ask your question
and get this over with.
You founded
one of the leading
digital security firms.
I am curious,
why are you so strict
about outside electronics in your home?
Well, despite the best precautions,
Agent MacLaren,
privacy is an illusion.
With cameras and microphones
built into every personal device...
My therapist says I'm paranoid,
but I think it's human nature
for us to do anything
to protect ourselves and our families.
Dad?
I'm just finishing up a meeting.
Go...
put your coat on.
I'll be out there shortly.
I try to reserve
a couple of hours every day
to play with my son.
Do you have children?
No.
Well, I'm sure
there's still time
for you and your wife.
I remember now!
We met five years ago
at a charity event.
It was before my condition
became so debilitating.
You were there with your wife...
Kathryn.
Sorry... didn't recognize you.
A stunning woman, if I remember it.
With dark hair,
and a wonderful dance partner.
In your shoes,
I would never have let a single soul
steal a dance from her.
Please send her my regards.
That is, if our business is concluded.
It is.
For now. Thanks for your time.
Happy hunting.
The event would've been five years ago.
Liberty Banquet Hall.
Looks fancy.
I have no idea,
but I'd be on the guest list.
"MacLaren plus guest."
That's you.
Yeah.
Okay. Look for Vincent Ingram.
There's no sign he was there.
Doesn't mean he wasn't.
Can you hack into his private server?
You know it.
How you doing? What's that? What's that?
Jeff!
We did it.
We deserve to celebrate. You...
deserve...
to celebrate.
You made a promise.
A couple hours ago, we didn't know
if we ever were going
to see our son again.
Come on,
I'm just trying to say thank you.
Hey, big boy!
Hey!
Come here. Come here.
I miss you.
Redundancy number six?
That's just excessive.
Just try again.
The Director didn't order us
to investigate this guy.
We're breaking Protocol 5 by doing this.
As far as I'm concerned,
this falls under Protocol 1...
The mission comes first.
The whole grand plan's in jeopardy
if we can't stop teams from being taken!
Now,
maybe this guy didn't pull the trigger,
but if he's involved in any way...
He froze me out.
That's redundancy number 7.
I thought you said you could do this!
There's a reason why
he's the best in the 21st.
Shouldn't you be the best,
considering the century you come from?
Hey, look.
Yelling at it worked.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
You look...
I can't even finish my sentence.
That seems to be going around.
Hi.
Uh, Blair just texted
that she's running a little late,
but the fish is ready,
so if you want to eat,
we could eat.
Uh, let's wait.
Yeah, you know, we probably should.
I wasn't, uh...
I wasn't sure if you were
actually gonna come.
Well, you invited me.
How's your therapy been going?
No more panic attacks.
I still find it hard to fall asleep
when I'm in bed with Blair, but...
You know, I didn't mean it like that.
Not like we don't, we do,
but just, you know...
you know, not excessively,
just a normal frequency.
Not like...
What was I talking about?
How you can't sleep.
Right!
Uh, she snores.
Ahem.
Hey...
would you do something for me?
Anything.
Tell me about me.
Like, things you don't remember, or...?
Okay, um...
I used to call you "Batgirl,"
from you running off at all hours,
fighting crime.
Uh...
you liked listening to country music.
Which country?
No, it's a... it's a genre.
Um, you like honey in your tea,
but not...
No, I mean, uh, what I was like.
Oh. Okay.
Um...
stubborn.
You drove me crazy sometimes.
I'm not gonna lie to you.
Uh... fierce.
Little yell-y, now and then.
Generally... amazing.
I'm not really sure
that's what I'm asking.
Um...
I'm just trying to find
the missing pieces.
All I tell you is what you did to me.
How I felt
whenever you would walk
through the door...
every time.
Like butterflies...
that feeling in your stomach.
Even more so when you'd go out again.
Someone like you
does not happen to someone like me.
And I know that doesn't
answer your question
and I know that you're just
trying to remember
the missing pieces, but...
Maybe someone is best defined
by how they affect
the people around them.
I think I just made that up,
but I think it may be true.
Hey, guys.
Um, I'm so sorry I'm late.
That's okay. We were just, uh...
Marcy, Carly...
I need you back at Ops, right now.
Um, I actually need to go,
something just came up.
Oh. No, really?
You don't need to...
I do.
Um, thank you for the wine.
Bye.
There's a file for each of us.
I can't believe we found him.
Open mine.
We take him tonight.
Before another Traveler dies.
You're fucking right we do.
Let's gear up.
Okay, we go in quiet and fast.
Kill him and get out.
Boss, I don't agree with this.
Yeah? Well, we're going to need you.
How about you, Philip?
Oh, I'm in.
All right,
there are four armed guards outside.
Here, here, here, and here.
I don't know how many staff inside.
All right.
Let's park behind this tree-line
and proceed on foot.
And, after lunch,
Miss Henry let me read
from The Chrysalids.
She said I had
a very impressive vocabulary.
Go get it!
Good for you.
Come on. Come on, boy.
Taylor?
Good boy. Good boy. Come on.
Taylor!
Not so far. Not so far!
Come on.
Traveler 001...
Traveler 3468, you are off-mission.
Stop your pursuit of Traveler 3468
and his team immediately.
Stand down immediately
or face repercussions.
Where's my mom?
Dad? What's wrong?
Come back inside.
Quickly. Quickly!
It's all right, sweetheart.
I'm a policeman.
Boss?
What do we do?
Taylor and I are leaving tonight.
We won't be returning.
Stand down.
What?
The Director must have a reason.
The Director is the one
who wanted him found!
We found him! Let's finish it!
It's not our mission.
Not tonight.
Come on, sweetheart. Let's get you home.
Come on.
Do you know your address?