- _
- Come on.
You're having fun with this one?
Okay.
And then he... he very
quickly realizes that
the cup is nowhere near big enough,
but he can't stop at this point.
And so there he is,
he's stuck in traffic,
and he's peeing into a coffee cup.
And the level is slowly rising.
... continue to search for answers
in the wake of the worst
nuclear attack in history,
which shook the lives of hundreds
of thousands of people on Tuesday.
There's been no information
as to which terrorist
group is responsible...
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
Thanks.
- Shit's gotten pretty crazy, huh?
- Yeah.
Always figured Omega
was the one protocol
we'd never have to worry about.
When you consider the amount
of potential revisions
and possible outcomes,
the Director's probably abandoned
millions of timelines.
Good chance there's a version
of us in most of them.
- Yeah, but I live in this one, so...
- Yeah.
Yeah.
What's that thing stuck to your head?
Brain implant.
- For?
- Temporal aphasia. Early onset.
Cool.
We'll file the missing
person's report in 24 hours.
It will have been given by
3569 after she's gone home.
He didn't come home from work.
That's all she needs to know.
- We'll take care of the rest.
- I'll tell her.
They'll blame us, you know that.
I'm surprised Yates
hasn't called already.
I should probably go into the office.
- Can you tell her it was Faction?
- I did.
But after this, they're never
gonna trust a word we say.
Yeah. After this, I'm
not sure I blame them.
Yeah, I still get locked
in once in a while.
The device is just a temporary solution.
There's no cure even in the future.
Switch hosts enough times,
it becomes inevitable.
So you've switched
hosts that many times?
Yeah.
I was an early test subject
for consciousness transfer.
So, you're like really old, then.
Yeah, yeah, I'm pretty fucking old.
I'm not even sure what
I'm supposed to do now.
What do you mean?
I'm a cop? That's it?
It was fine as Protocol
5, but I'm a doctor.
- We still have a mission.
- Do we?
Maybe the Director
abandoned this timeline,
but that doesn't mean we have to.
We can't just go around
making up our own missions.
Why not?
Because it would make us no
different than the Faction.
Then we still have a mission
to complete. Find 001.
And how are we supposed to do that?
He could've jumped into anyone by now.
- Without the Director's help...
- I don't know. I just...
We... We have to try.
I'm gonna take off now.
You're bleeding.
- Mm, shit.
- Here.
- I can bandage you up.
- No, no, no.
- Y-You don't gotta.
- Just come here.
Come here.
What?
I'm just so sorry, that's all.
Can I ask you something?
Whatever. Sure.
The future hasn't gotten
any better, has it?
- Protocol 2, Marcy.
- Protocol Omega, Jeff.
Truth?
Nothing the Director's done has
made one bit of difference.
But I still think that
we can change that.
Hey, how about if I finish up? Yeah?
Okay.
- Where you headed?
- Home.
- I'll give you a lift.
- No. You're just gonna wanna talk.
- It's good to talk.
- I already know what you're gonna say
because I've been trained
to say the same thing.
And you'll feel better
because we're told
that it helps people, but it doesn't.
- Marcy.
- David...
David was the kind of man who
made humanity worth saving. He...
He literally represented that.
And he's a better human being than
every fucking person in this room.
And the Director did
nothing to save him.
So I'm done.
You want me to go after her,
make sure she gets home okay?
No. Let her go.
Agent MacLaren.
Officer Conniker.
- Thank you for the rescue.
- You stay in touch.
I will.
Sir...
I have reason to believe
that yesterday's attacks
were not caused by the Travelers.
Well, then I have reason to
believe you're one of them.
There is a resistance
group called the Faction.
Oh, I know all about the
Faction, believe me.
That is their political distinction.
It doesn't change the fact
that the uranium used
in every single one of those nukes
had just been traced back to the
exact same mine in this country.
I was there with Agent
MacLaren and his team
when he disarmed the fourth device.
Okay, so we're supposed to convince
the Russians and the Chinese
that although every one of the
nukes that went off yesterday
has been traced back to us,
the one that was successfully disarmed
just happened to be on U.S. soil?
'Cause the good Travelers saved us
from the bad Travelers, is that it?
Does that sound like a
compelling argument?
No.
Every one of the groups we're
monitoring keeps saying the same thing.
"Protocol Omega." What is it?
- I'll ask MacLaren.
- Find another way. I don't trust them.
Get it right, please.
Right now, we're one nervous
general away from nuclear war.
Do you ever think about
what you would've done
if you hadn't volunteered
for the Traveler program?
No. Never saw myself
doing anything else.
Yeah, me, too.
But I'm not sure I'd
make the same decision,
knowing what I know.
- There was another option?
- Yeah. Life.
Life not solely devoted
to training and combat.
Life without Protocol 4.
Stuck in domes, heated
by a failing reactor,
on a diet of yeast and recycled water?
We were barely clinging to
life, Carly, not living it.
Yeah, well, tell that to
my mother and sisters.
They still found a way
to laugh every day,
fall in love, make families.
Hey, at least you still got
your wife to go home to.
Traveler team report to the
following coordinates immediately:
47.2531 degrees north,
122.4523 degrees west.
What the hell was that?
One way to find out.
- You can't be serious.
- Why not?
You know for a fact that that
message wasn't from the Director.
It's obviously a trap
set up by the Faction.
And if the Faction is working with 001?
Then we're the next ones
behind a brick wall.
We'll take precautions.
Carly, what the hell else
are we supposed to do?
Literally anything else.
We can do whatever we want.
I can't order you to go
with me, but I'm going.
Trevor, are you there?
I could use your help.
Coverage continues today of
the deadly terrorist attack
that took place in...
Nearly 48 hours since
the initial attack,
very few questions have been answered.
The authorities administrated...
- Hey, Trev?
- Yeah, bud?
Where's Marcy?
She left a while ago.
It's just you and me.
So, Marcy went home?
Why don't we meditate for
20 minutes? Clear our heads.
Hi, this is David Mailer.
Please leave a message.
Hey, taxi!
Marcy?
Oh, my God.
Philip, what are you doing here?
I'm sorry.
Okay, just...
Go into the living room.
I'll be right there.
Carly, you got anything?
Nothing yet.
Hold up. One man walking
out from the boat.
Agent MacLaren. I'm pleased
you were able to make it.
Okay.
Do the names "Vincent Ingram"
or "Katrina Perrow"
mean anything to you?
Just wanna have a conversation.
Oh, you better start talking
'cause you've got about ten seconds
before I order your head blown off.
- I wanna cut a deal.
- Eight seconds.
I will turn myself in to the
Director and face the consequences
if you will fill me in on the
details of Protocol Omega.
Fill you in?
It was not a protocol in
the time I was sent back.
Really?
That's what you're going with?
Yates, is this you?
- How did you know?
- Seriously?
Why didn't you just give him an
eye patch and a cat to stroke?
I need you to come talk to my superiors.
They're my superiors, too.
Why not just text me?
Because they don't trust you. Three
nuclear devices just went off.
And you watched us disarm the fourth.
How could you possibly... ?
You know what? Fine. Let's go.
- All of them. Including the sniper.
- Uh, no.
Carly, you and Trevor head back
in my car. This won't take long.
Copy that.
Happy to go with, boss.
This is my Protocol 5, remember?
Okay, fine.
- Who did you get to play the messenger?
- Johanson's kid.
Wants to be an actress.
She's good.
So I would recommend not
doing this to someone.
But make a claw with your
left hand, like this.
And then so when you come down...
- Oh! Shit.
- Oh.
Ah.
Now you can't expect
beginner's luck to last.
- Gin.
- I didn't...
That's your shirt.
- Ah, well, rules are rules. All right.
- That's your shirt.
Oh, man.
Whoo.
- Aw.
- Right?
- All right, one more round and then...
- Okay. Keep going.
Philip.
Hey, Philip. Hey.
Hey.
You saw something in the
bathroom, didn't you?
I would never do that.
You know that, right?
I don't really.
I know you don't wanna
rely on the drugs,
but if those pills are helping,
- you need to keep taking them.
- I can't. I threw them away.
And only an archivist can give me more.
Anyway, I'm glad you're okay.
Hey, please... please
take care of yourself.
Yeah.
David was a really good guy.
Excuse me, what are you doing in... ?
What are you doing?
Stop! Stop it! Stop it!
Carly!
Renovations?
- Everything needs to be hard-wired.
- Because?
We've built our version of
what you call an S.T.A.,
Space Time Attenuation field generator.
I'm told it'll make it impossible
for the Director to see us.
It's under guard on the floor below
if you're thinking of
looking for the off switch.
That precaution really wasn't necessary.
Director Stevenson, it's
an honor to meet you.
Turn off your comm device.
My comm?
Okay.
- It's off.
- Good.
Jesus! Okay, okay, okay.
It's off.
Give me one reason I shouldn't
round up every one of you.
The nuclear devices were
built by the Faction.
They're still out there.
Protocol Omega, what does it mean?
It means the Director will no longer
be intervening in this timeline.
- What does that mean?
- No more messengers, no more missions.
Those who are part of
the Traveler program
are free to live out their days,
such as they are, as they see fit.
- Why would the Director do that?
- It's impossible to say for sure.
Venture a guess.
It could mean that we've succeeded
and we're now on the optimal
path to a better future.
It could also mean there's no
possible way of saving the future
no matter what you do.
That's true.
Why should we believe
a word you're saying?
That's your call, sir.
But I'm willing to help in any way I can
and I'll tell you
anything you wanna know.
Jeff.
Hey, just wanna check in on you,
see how's it going.
I brought you something.
It's water flavoring made of leaves.
You just add boiling water.
Yeah, yeah, I know what tea is.
I've developed quite a
taste for it myself.
Hmm.
Uh, do you wanna come in
and have a cup with me?
If... If that would be cool.
- But I don't wanna...
- Come on. Come in.
Take a seat.
Looks like you've been
doing some cleaning.
Yeah, just trying to keep busy.
I'll be okay. I just need
some time, you know?
Time, yes.
Don't we all?
I know what you've been through, Marcy.
You do?
Well, not everything.
I can't imagine what it must
have been like for you,
to go through your reset,
to lose all those memories.
The Director took my wife from me, too.
You mean your... your
wife in the future.
Death by messenger.
Just like David.
Precious life, snuffed out
right before my eyes.
But we have no right to complain.
We forfeited that right
when we made the decision to put our
fate in the hands of a machine.
Um, I'm sorry you went through all that.
Is another reset possible, I wonder?
Is Ellis's backdoor code to the Director
still buried in there somewhere?
I don't think so.
Oh, I think so.
I really do.
Anyway, it's... it's just good
to see you whole again, Marcy.
I should get that.
Let me help you.
Guys!
001 went into Jeff!
He's after Ellis's backdoor code.
He thinks... He thinks it's in my head.
Guys, I need your help!
Marcy?
Mac, Trevor? Can anyone here me?
Sorry, I must've got
locked in for a sec.
I didn't catch it all,
but Marcy's in trouble.
Meet me at her place.
Ah!
Ugh. Mac, I have 001.
The gun isn't loaded, Marcy.
I could never risk what's
in that pretty little head.
Ugh.
Take her.
It's the end of the world, brother.
We're all gonna die now.
Before I agree to let you do anything,
I wanna know about the future.
I can only tell
you about the time I left.
It's changed because
you changed history.
Not necessarily for the better.
From what little I've heard,
even after all we've done,
humanity is still on the
brink of extinction.
A more recent Traveler might
be able to tell you more.
Just tell me the history you
remember. What went wrong?
The decline took years, but this
decade was the turning point.
Once climate change became
unstoppable, it led to mass migration,
severe overpopulation in
urban centers, famine.
Ancient diseases became
unlocked as polar ice melted,
which exposed humanity to viruses
for which we had no immunity.
That led to mass death, collapse
of governments, resources,
war over what was left.
Eventually, nuclear winter.
How the hell were you
supposed to stop all that?
Our primary mission
was to prevent a massive
asteroid strike in the Atlantic.
Helios.
When an x-ray laser's fired toward
a previously undiscovered asteroid
from within the continental
United States,
now that tends not to go unnoticed.
We should prove our good
intentions. Helios killed millions.
The Grand Plan was supposed
to erase all that.
- Why didn't it work?
- I honestly can't answer that.
Only that the Director kept trying.
Till today.
Agent MacLaren, today, this country's
been accused by my counterparts
in Russia, China, even by our allies,
of detonating nuclear
devices on their soil.
I told you that was the Faction.
- They don't know that.
- Well, then let me tell them.
Let me tell them everything.
We can still fix this.
I can reach out. We'll need
to arrange translators.
That won't be necessary.
Carly, I'm at the apartment.
I'm still a few minutes
out. Is she there?
No. And the place is trashed.
Oh, God. Marcy, can you hear me?
Say that again.
Come in, Marcy. Marcy, you there?
Ah, shit.
I found her comm. It's been cut out.
He's taken her.
You said you didn't catch it all.
What did you hear her say?
Something about Ellis's backdoor code.
What good is the code without
access to the Director?
Boss, we got a problem.
Philip, Mac's turned off his comm.
Okay, I'm close to his house.
I'll try to find him.
Carly, meet me out front. I
know where they're going.
Marcy, I'm sorry.
I thought the Director would
stop them. They drugged me.
Grace, what did you tell them?
Boss, are you here?
Oh, okay.
Oh, boy. Oh, boy. Oh.
That's good, huh?
Uh, I'm... I'm gonna...
I'm just gonna... gonna go.
What is the number of
Travelers in my country?
Each Traveler team is
forbidden by our protocols
to communicate with each
other unless directed.
We have captured several
Traveler cells in Russia.
They told us this Faction
originated in the United States.
They first came en masse
from the future to the U.S., yes,
but they have since spread
out to many countries.
Having consolidated their
power in your country.
- My team is on their way.
- Protocol Omega.
Why do you think that this
code is still in my head?
Actually, Grace told me.
Even told me how to use
it to hack the Director.
- I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
- What if she's wrong?
Then nothing happens,
and I'm disappointed.
But if she's right, the Director
becomes permanently disabled
and the future belongs to humanity.
- Oh, you mean the Faction?
- Yes.
- Led by you?
- So I'm told.
This reset will take away all
those painful memories, Marcy.
Memories of who I am now.
The Director allowed the man
that you love to die horribly
when it could have saved him.
How can you forgive that?
By doing this, we'll
both get what we want.
All right, let's get this over with.
Don't shoot her!
You want what's in my head?
You can't have it.
No!
The other way is gonna
take so much longer.
Travelers will cooperate, I promise you.
We can even help find
members of the Faction
responsible for the nuclear devices.
Then will you share your
advanced technologies?
Our engineers have been
creating materials and...
and building devices for a decade.
I think if our technology
is shared equitably, we...
Sir, we're making progress.
This isn't the time to
be negotiating access
to future technologies
with foreign powers.
If we're to trust each other, we...
- What is happening?
- They're being overwritten.
- The Director's not doing this...
- Then who is?
I don't know. But it's impossible...
... for the Director to
take life in that way.
Stevenson.
When did this happen?
All right, keep me up to date.
The president and most of his cabinet
just screamed in pain and collapsed.
Oh, my God.
They all claim to be fine now. This
happened to the Speaker as well.
This is a coup.
I need to get back to Washington.
Arrest this son of a bitch.
Put your hands on your head.
- Jo, you gotta believe me.
- Now!
- Listen to me.
- Shut the fuck up.
The same thing that
happened to the president
is probably happening to other
world leaders right now.
Let me help you.
I need to talk to my team.
Guys, it's me, what's happening?
Where the fuck have you been?
001's taken Jeff as a host.
No.
The rescue was just a set
up to get access to Marcy.
Why Marcy?
So he could use Ellis's backdoor
code against the Director.
Through Ilsa. He's taken her to Filmore.
Yeah, that's our guess, too.
- We're almost there.
- Boss, I could use a pick up.
Okay, I'll get you on the way.
You're not going anywhere.
Guys, am I the only one seeing this?
_
No. We see it, too.
You need to get out.
I have to go see my son.
Filmore's not far from here.
Carly, there isn't much time.
I know. Go.
Boss, Carly's out.
Protocol Omega. I'll
meet you at Filmore.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll try and get the Director to safety.
NORAD's detected a
massive missile strike
from both Russia and China.
Tell me why this is happening.
The first ever Traveler 001
has taken over in the future.
Don't ask me how.
- He launched the missiles?
- No.
That would likely be the generals
following standing orders to launch
in the event their
leadership was overwritten.
But he is still the cause.
NORAD said we were targeted.
Jo,
you can either come with me or
you can shoot me in the back.
Bye, Marce.
I'm sorry.
Trevor! What are you doing?
001 must have uploaded his
consciousness into Ilsa.
No, he's not in there.
Grace.
Grace, hey.
He wasn't able to use the
backdoor code either.
Marcy... took that from him.
Then where is he?
Ugh. He's everywhere.
I don't understand.
001 transferred his
consciousness first into Ilsa,
and then out to the Internet.
By now, he's parsed
himself into computers
and servers all over the world,
just waiting for the future to arrive,
and then he can take over.
I didn't think it would
matter if I said anything.
I just thought the
Director would stop him.
I just was waiting.
He won.
What?
Then why did we come here?
I'm sorry, Jo.
It's over.
Maybe not.
Maybe everything we need to fix
this is right here in front of us.
Maybe the Director is just
expecting us to see it.
How many timelines are
you seeing right now?
Just one. The only one left.
And it's gonna end unless
one of us goes back.
Back in time?
Whoa. Guys, even if one of us was able
to upload their consciousness into Ilsa,
and even if Ilsa had the
electrical and processing power...
Which it does.
The Director's made sure of that
by downloading the program into
Ilsa in the middle of the night.
Even then, we could only send
someone to a point in time
after the most recent Traveler.
No, from 431 years in the future,
that's true, absolutely,
but not from now.
The amplitude of space-time distortion
is directly proportional to distance.
How far back could one safely
go from this point in time?
Twenty years, easy.
All we need to do is go
back before 001 arrived.
That's why the Director's been silent.
Because it knew we would think of this,
and it sent us what we
would need to do it.
I'm sorry, I do love this idea,
but we'd still need a TELL.
It's a time, elevation,
latitude and longitude
to send a consciousness
into a specific host.
You can't just guess.
It has to be exact.
August 18th, 2001, Whytecliff
Park, exactly 3:00 p.m.
When and where my host met Kat.
Okay.
And I have one last objection,
but it's a big one.
If this works, I'll be
ending Grant MacLaren's life
17 years before his
historical death, I know.
But maybe I can give those
years back to someone else.
So...
until we meet again.
That's a very interesting possibility.
Well...
if we're gonna do this,
hurry the fuck up.
I'll find the coordinates to Whytecliff
and the IMEI of MacLaren's cell phone.
Trevor, help me load the program.
- See, Jo? There's still hope.
- Hope?
Mac,
you did this.
You people didn't stop the
collapse of civilization.
If anything, you sped it up.
Where are you going?
To look at the sky.
Beautiful view, isn't it?
- Oh, God.
- Sorry. Ha-ha.
Didn't mean to sneak up on you.
No, it's all right. I was just
expecting someone. He's late.
Some people are late people.
- Almost an hour?
- That's pretty late.
Hmm. On my birthday?
- Oh, he's in the doghouse.
- Yes, he is.
John's an artist. He gets
caught up in his work.
Is he any good?
He's brilliant, actually.
Maybe he's painting a portrait
of you for your birthday.
There are enough of those portraits
around the house, believe me.
Ah. Wow.
As intriguing as that is, we just met,
I should probably leave it alone.
I love him, he just does this too often.
So set him straight.
Tell him if he respects you,
he won't keep you waiting,
and that he's goddamn lucky
to have a woman as beautiful
and charming as you in his life.
What?
I'm can't tell if
you're flirting with me
or telling me to give
him another chance.
Well, if I was him, I know
I'd want another chance.
But I'm not him.
Happy birthday.
_
Hey!
Who the fuck is this guy?
Sorry, I just wanna make sure
you're on the right bus.
This one's headed to kind
of a rough part of town.
I know.
I didn't like the way my
patients were being treated
at the old hospital I worked at, so,
I'm starting at a new one on Main.
Oh. I take some of my clients
there. I'm a social worker.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
- Are you doctor or a... ?
- Uh, nurse.
- Nurse?
- Nurse, yeah.
Right.
Oh, it's a... it's a
pretty busy hospital.
Just to warn you. A lot of tough cases.
- Well, I'm pretty tough.
- I bet.
I just wanna help the people
who really need it, you know?
Yeah. Yeah, same.
My name's David.
_
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --