_
We're being followed. Lose them.
Faster! We have to...
- How is she?
- Vitals are stable for now.
But the pressure remains high.
- Still no ID?
- No. Nothing.
Not even on the driver.
He didn't make it.
Hopefully her family will realize
she's missing and start calling around.
Okay. We'll see what comes
back on the MRI and EEG,
but it looks like we'll have to
relieve some of the cranial pressure
with or without her
next of kin permission.
- I'll double check with the desk.
- All right, thank you.
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
Mm. Hey.
Every time.
What?
Every time I see you walking
towards me I think to myself,
"My God, what is that beautiful
woman doing in my apartment?"
Ah-ah!
Apparently saving you from
salmonella poisoning.
Oh, no. A lot of people say
there's more nutrients this way.
Yeah. Well, a lot of people are dumb.
- Well, I could have cooked that.
- Let's just start again.
Okay. So?
What's the plan for today?
Um. I'm not sure yet.
Not sure or can't tell me?
Not even a little hint?
David, it's the same as every other day.
I might have a mission.
But if you don't hear from me, don't
expect me home until late. Okay?
Yeah. I was just curious.
- How about your day?
- Um, you know, same old...
Same... Okay. You know what? I'm
gonna show you how to do this
without getting half the shell
in here, you're killing me.
- What?
- This is an actual choking hazard.
Uh...
- He's alive!
- Another exciting day in the 21st.
Every day is a gift, Philip.
Says the man who has
received the most gifts.
And I don't take a
single one for granted.
Oh, shit.
Boss, you there?
Yeah, what's up?
The deep web is blowing up
with a missing persons alert.
Teams all around us are searching.
- A missing Traveler?
- Not just any Traveler.
The Director calculated an 88
percent probability that an EEG
taken out an accident victim
yesterday belongs to Traveler 001.
Well, that's got to be a mistake.
He was overwritten by the Director.
All we know for sure
is that a new consciousness
was sent into the host body.
You're saying 001 was
already gone at that point?
It's the only explanation.
- How?
- Don't know, boss.
But an EEG is kinda like a fingerprint.
The Director would recognize it.
The patient was brought in to
Coastal Cross as a Jane Doe.
Where is she now?
Well, if it's really 001,
he was taken out of his room
before the test results came back.
Shit.
Okay, stay on it.
I'll go to the hospital, I'll
let you know what I find out.
I just don't know how
much more I've got left.
Trust is a limited resource with me.
I think that's true for all of us.
And once it's gone, it's
gone. I just can't...
Remember, building walls prevents...
Prevents growth. I know, I know.
We're hard wired to protect
ourselves, Kathryn.
It's a survival instinct.
People aren't supposed to
fantasize their husbands are evil.
Well, anxiety manifests
itself in strange ways.
Though, I do find it
interesting you're fantasizing
about confronting your husband
rather than just doing it.
Just the idea of that scares me.
What's he gonna do?
If you have something to say, say it.
I want you to try something for me.
I want you to say something
three or four times in a row.
However you like.
Don't think, just feel how it feels
and hear what it sounds like
when you say it, okay?
- Okay.
I want you to say, "I am
not afraid of my husband."
I am not...
Hey!
I know you're in there!
What do you want?
I just wanna have a conversation.
We don't have anything to talk about.
How about we talk about
what you did with Carly?
- I'm right here.
- Bullshit.
Who the fuck are you?
- Go, Jeff! Last warning.
- Warning?
You kicked my ass when I was piss drunk,
but not this time...
Leave.
I guess we'll do this another time.
Hey?
Yes.
Same place? Okay, great.
I can come now.
Thanks.
Who was that on the phone?
- I have to get some medication.
- Medication.
For the update. Which you're
also not supposed to know about.
It's Director approved.
Okay.
My relapse was a one-time thing.
Cool.
You got to trust me, I've
got it under control.
I never said you didn't.
Cool.
- But I'm still coming with you.
- You don't have to do that.
Yeah, I do. Come on. Let's go!
I'll come back for it.
Fuck, shit. Shit.
Jordan. Hi.
Whoa. What's wrong? Everything okay?
I lost your bike, man.
You lost it, huh?
Uh, okay, well, let's,
um... let's go look for it.
No.
I mean, the Murray Park
guys showed up, and...
And they stole it.
Okay. Uh...
Don't worry about it. You know,
I'm just glad you're okay.
I'm not okay, though. I loved that bike.
Yeah, I loved it, too.
So we're gonna go get it back.
Maintenance to Floor 3.
Doctor Mori. Special Agent
Grant MacLaren of the FBI.
Yes?
You had a Jane Doe come
through here last night?
We did, yeah. Car accident.
Do you know who...
I was hoping you could tell me what
you know. Anything is helpful.
Oh, um...
Yeah. She was probably in her 40s.
Uh, five-foot-eight. Blonde.
Very expensive suit.
Hard to say much else. She sustained
serious trauma to the head.
We were just beginning
treatment, and she disappeared.
- Could she have walked out of here?
- No. Not a chance.
We had her in a chemically induced
coma due to her head injury.
I came back to check on
her, she was just gone.
Who do I speak to have
a security footage?
Oh, oh. No offense, Agent,
but it's not every day I have
a patient in that condition
just up and disappear.
I went and checked the tapes myself,
but apparently the whole system
froze last night for some reason
and didn't get a thing.
Hmm.
- Mind if I look around anyway?
- No. Be my guest.
Let me know if you find out anything.
- Of course.
- Okay.
_
- Where are we at?
- Not good.
Brain hemorrhage. Blood
pressure's high and rising.
Okay. What can we do about that?
Right now, all I can do
is monitor his host body.
I need you to do something.
Without more information
there's not much I can do.
We need a CT scan, an MRI...
Michelle, he's of no use
to us in this state.
Then maybe we shouldn't
have chased him down
and caused a fucking car accident.
Sorry.
Keep me posted.
Wait.
Who are you?
My name is Dawn.
And it's an honor to be here with you.
Nice part of town the
Director sent you to.
Yeah, well, we live in a garage, so...
Hey, guys.
I haven't swung by in
a while to check-in.
Everyone good? Need anything?
Nobody. No?
No, man. We're good.
Good.
All right. Awesome.
I'm good, too, thanks for asking.
That's my bike.
I, uh, I gave it to a
friend and you stole it,
so I'm gonna need it back.
- This bike?
- That bike.
No, man. You're confused.
I've had this bike for years.
- Years?
- Yeah.
My mom gave it to me for my birthday.
- Yeah? When's your birthday?
- October 24th.
Well, that doesn't prove anything,
everyone knows when their birthday is.
I'm just gonna need that bike back.
Or what?
Jesus! Oh, that was your cue
to hit the ground, by the way.
You're fucking dead.
Where you going, huh?
I know you guys.
Yep, that's us!
You okay?
They stole my bike, so I
was just... I was gonna...
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I think so.
God, I'm lucky you guys
were just passing by.
Yeah. Lucky.
That was awesome.
It's like stuff you see in the movies.
You should get your head checked out.
Yeah. 'Cause you could
have a concussion.
- It feels nasty, is it bad?
- Uh...
Show it to Marcy. We gotta go.
Okay.
- Hey, thanks guys.
- Take care, David.
Better?
Sure.
- What? You trust me now?
- I always trusted you.
You guys there?
Yeah, boss.
What's happening on the
deep web? Any updates?
Uh. We had to step out for a thing.
What thing?
It's done, we're on our way back now.
This is 001 we're talking about.
Uh. Learn anything at the hospital?
Nothing.
Starting to think...
Traveler 3468, take immediate
action to provide Internet access
for the Ilsa A.I. at
Filmore Laboratories.
Are you looking for your parents?
Cameron, get over here!
We just got a messenger.
Everybody back at OPS immediately.
We're on our way.
Copy that.
I'll be right there.
- Told you I'd get it back.
- How?
Uh, well, I asked nicely.
You get whacked in the head?
It's nothing. You should
see the other guy.
But listen, do me a favor.
Uh, keep your distance from
Murray Park for a while.
Those guys. They're not...
They're not happy.
I got you, man. Thank you, thank you.
No problem.
- Please eat something.
- What do you want from me?
For now, we need you healthy.
But soon we'll need your help.
And why would I help you?
We represent a group of people
known hundreds of years from now
as the Faction.
We've lost contact with the future
and now we're running out of resources.
Ah. You need money.
That's all this is.
There's so much more to this than that.
- Are you in pain?
- Yes.
Here.
Take this.
I'll be right back.
The headache's becoming more
severe and he's getting weaker.
He hardly seems injured.
That's the difficulty with internal
injuries and brain trauma.
I'm telling you,
without surgical intervention
he's not gonna last a day.
We can't risk the
exposure to the Director.
We have to find him a new host.
- You know what we'll be inviting.
- But he'll survive.
We need the consciousness
transfer device.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Go on.
We won't stop you.
_
- You know what I just did.
- Activated your failsafe.
They're coming for you now.
It's the only way to save you
and that is more
important than anything.
Female, 40s, blonde hair.
I wonder who in 001's custody
fits that description.
- Perrow.
- What?
He jumped?
Uh, that would mean that 001 has
consciousness transfer technology.
His companies could have
manufactured the key components.
Simon could've done the work.
He helped build the first one.
So kidnapping people close to
us was just a smoke screen.
- And the Director fell for it.
- So did we.
I'm using FBI resources
to locate Perrow,
but if he's capable of
consciousness transfer...
001 could be anyone by now.
Traveler teams have been searching
since the alert went out
on the backchannel,
but when you consider the sheer
amount of potential candidates...
Oh, hopefully through Ilsa, the
Director can shorten the list.
How do we get access?
I called. They're expecting us.
Do we need a cover?
I'm going with FBI agents.
I suggest you guys be specialists.
Pretty sure the real FBI
won't like that idea.
No, but I have a plan.
Okay, I'm here, we can go.
That's your plan?
How about you just make sure you
have everything you need first.
Trev, get everything on
the list I texted you?
Yep.
- Trev?
- Yep.
Then we're good to go. Okay,
team, let's move out!
She's really eager to
talk to the Director.
Yeah. I can see that.
- I'll be in the car!
- Okay!
Ow. Ugh.
Hey, Marce, it's me.
I was just wondering when you were...
Oh, God.
Oh, my God!
I just vomited in a voicemail.
That is disgusting, I am so sorry. Um...
Where was I?
Um. I was calling...
I wanted to tell you
that I think I have a concussion
because I have all the symptoms.
Nausea being one of them.
So obviously I Googled
concussion on my phone
and I know I tend to instantly
take on the symptoms
of anything I look up
online, but this time, I...
I can promise you that it's not
all in my head, because it is.
I mean, that's where
concussions happen, right?
So where else would it be?
Anyhoodle, uh, I got conked
in the head pretty hard
and I could use your advice.
Oh, this is... This is David.
Agent MacLaren?
Dr. Teslia. It's a pleasure to meet you.
I... thought you'd be coming alone.
We're specialists.
We'd like to set up as soon as possible.
So this is Ilsa.
Stop!
You called her?
- What the fuck are you doing here?
- Nice to see you, partner.
The Director needs access
to the Internet...
That is not approved.
- We're on orders from the Director...
- Step back!
Boss?
Do what she asks, guys.
- Look. Jo.
- No. Don't "Jo" me.
You're not getting anywhere near Ilsa.
We both know it isn't
Ilsa we need to talk to.
Our agreement with 21st
century authorities
includes access to the Director.
Supervised approved access.
Oh. That's a matter of interpretation.
Not by flashing your
bogus badge to security
like you're an actual FBI agent.
The badge is a hundred percent real.
The computer is isolated
from the world for a reason.
Did I mention the future's at stake?
No. Actually, you didn't
mention a goddamn thing.
What was I supposed to say?
You're supposed to run things by me.
That's how this is supposed to work.
Oh, full disclosure,
the Director is trying to find
someone and needs access to the web
in order to do it.
Who?
He's kinda our public enemy number one.
We have other resources for that.
Not nearly as advanced.
That's not even the point,
you're supposed to be
cooperating with me.
It is programmed to take care
of humanity, not harm it...
Yeah. But Ilsa is still
an emerging intelligence.
We can't risk exposing her to
everything that's out there online.
- I understand that, but...
- No. No, you don't understand.
And you don't take no for an answer.
I'm getting a little tired of it.
Okay.
Okay, what?
I'm taking no for an answer.
What about our orders?
We've also been ordered to cooperate.
We'll just have to find the
information we need some other way.
Thank you.
Could I possibly just talk to
the Director for a few seconds?
No.
Fine.
We're done here.
- We were right. He's in Perrow.
- That was fast.
Seriously? I thought the
modulated LED connection
between the server bank and
Ilsa was taking forever.
His accounts, numbered companies,
everything. It's all here.
In Perrow's name, he
planned the whole thing.
He even made Perrow guardian of his kid.
Sick.
So, we know where Perrow is?
The Director shows Traveler 001 in
a warehouse just outside of town.
Then we take him now.
I have to admit, this
is getting exciting.
There's no Uber out here!
Shit.
Hi, this is Kat. Leave a message
and I'll get right back to you.
Kathryn, it's Jeff Conniker.
Sorry I didn't make it over to the
coffee shop. Some shit went down.
But we still need to get together.
You, me, David.
I just left him a voicemail,
too. The thing is...
I'm remembering shit.
Carly isn't Carly anymore.
And I don't think your
husband is either.
Anyway, call me back when you get this.
My son and my host's daughter were
moving to a new secure location.
They'll be worried.
Mr. Morraca will take care of them
until you're ready to see them again.
Like I said, there isn't much
about you we don't know.
Where are you planning to take me?
We're just preparing you for
the transfer when they arrive.
My people have standing
orders to kill you.
Hopefully, they'll realize that
we're on the same side
before that happens.
They won't believe you.
I'm not sure I do.
Obviously, this was not the plan.
I'm not offering an apology.
More of... an explanation.
You weren't supposed
to find out for years.
In the future you come from, Shelter
41 collapsed. Thousands died.
But the future we come
from is different.
I know all of this.
Because you questioned Traveler
teams that were pursuing you.
What a Traveler would never tell you
is that the citizens of Shelter 41
became the center of a movement.
A place where human life and
decision-making was valued
over the artificial intelligence
that controlled every
aspect of our lives.
The Director.
It considered our movement nothing
more than a subversive "faction"
within what it considered
a harmonious whole.
The faction became a rebellion.
A rebellion that became a war...
led by you, sir.
Not possible.
I promise you, it is.
I'm a witness to it.
I have sworn my loyalty to you
in my time, and I do now.
Then why risk telling me any of this?
I would never have approved.
Very true.
You forbade contact of
any kind before we came.
Then why?
We're desperate.
The Director still holds
power over the 21st.
Thousands of us came through the
frame, but it still finds us.
Every day, Traveler teams
are tasked to seek us out.
The moment we're discovered,
we die by messenger.
You need to hide.
We can't both hide and
fight for our future.
We still wanna save humanity.
We have no historians, no finances,
no engineers building devices
and components in secret.
But we have you.
As a prisoner.
As our leader.
Your host body is dying.
We've activated your beacon
and summoned your men
in order to save your life.
We only hope that you will
spare ours in return.
Oh, Christ.
You've got to be kidding me.
Boss, we got an issue.
We don't have time for this.
Shit.
You're gonna die now, Jeff.
Me? I don't think so.
Unless you get back in
that car, drive away,
and never show your face
again, you will die today.
I remember now, Carly.
- It doesn't matter.
- Everything.
The abduction. Your
confession. All of it!
I know what you are!
- What all of you are!
- Drop the gun, Jeff.
Gonna get your boyfriend to
shoot me in the back now?
He's not my boyfriend,
and he won't have to.
So what? You're gonna do it?
Carly Shannon?
No. You're gonna take
care of that yourself.
No. I don't think so.
'Cause see, there's people onto you now,
not just me. They're onto you!
It doesn't matter. You're gonna die.
Shut the fuck up!
And not a single person is gonna care.
Not me.
Not your sergeant or any of
the cops that you work with.
Not even your son.
- I said shut your mouth.
- Or what?
- Carly, don't.
- No. I wanna know. What?
What?
What are you gonna do, Jeff? Huh?
_
Come on. I'm standing right here.
What are you gonna do?
- You're not Carly!
- Yes, I am.
I'm the Carly you can't hurt anymore.
_
I'm Traveler 5416.
Welcome to the 21st.
If the Director hadn't taken him...
Either way.
We should get back to the mission.
Somebody better drive
for him, he's drunk.
- Hey.
Thanks for coming here instead. I
didn't feel much like going out.
No, no, it's fine.
Nice place.
Thanks. It's, uh...
Where I live.
So what happened?
Nothing. Little street fight.
What?
Well, uh, to get my bike back.
A bike that I had given
to somebody else,
but then it got stolen by a gang.
You got into a street fight with a gang?
Yeah. Well, you should see the other...
Um, you want some tea?
David, you need to see a doctor.
Marcy'll check me out
when she gets home.
It's nothing. Slight concussion.
No big deal. I mean,
once the vomiting stops.
Ilsa, what do you know about me?
You are from Lewiston, Idaho.
You graduated from the
University of Washington
and received a doctorate in
Computer Science from Princeton.
Your mother is Margaret.
Your father is Charles.
Ilsa, stop.
How did you become aware
of this information?
You told me.
No. I didn't tell you that.
Perhaps you have forgotten, Dr. Teslia,
as the information is now
readily accessible to me.
But if I didn't tell you that,
then how did you get...
Couldn't see a thing on
the surveillance tapes.
Hmm.
Did you run your diagnostic?
Yup, uh, no change. Ilsa is the
same as she was yesterday.
That doesn't make any sense.
I don't know what to tell you.
Could they have broadcast something
to Ilsa from outside the glass,
or vice versa?
No, this isn't just a glass
box, it's a Faraday cage.
There's a... fine mesh
woven into the glass
that blocks electromagnetic signals.
Then what was MacLaren's dog
and pony show all about?
I have no idea.
- Just run the test.
- Yes.
- And call me.
- Of course.
- Okay?
- Yes. Of course.
Are we concealing my new capabilities
from Special Agent Yates?
Yes, Ilsa, we are. From everyone.
May I ask why?
Because they'll become afraid of
you and I don't want them to be.
There is no reason to
be afraid, Dr. Teslia.
No, I know that, Ilsa.
I know that.
Can you hear me?
Dad, what's wrong?
Michelle.
The device is coming soon.
Try to stay with us.
- What's happening?
- Ruptured aneurysm.
I think he's having a stroke.
We need him conscious
for when they arrive.
You just have to hold
on a little longer.
I can't see.
What?
I'm blind.
They're killing each other,
please say something.
- Stop!
- Hold fire!
Hold your fire!
These people are not our enemy.
So, the elephant in the room?
Jeff's voicemails.
Yeah. That's why I wanted to see you.
Creepy, right?
I mean, he said that... that
Carly wasn't really Carly,
and Marcy wasn't really Marcy.
- Yeah. He said the same of Grant.
- He sounded drunk.
Jeff's the one who should
be seeing a doctor.
Okay, but...
Deep down, I mean, in
your heart of hearts...
Don't you think it's possible
that he might be right?
No. What?
Absolutely not.
Jesus, Kat.
I thought you were seeing that
therapist that I recommended.
I am, and she's great,
but does that mean that I can't
have doubts about my husband?
Not doubts that he's not even who
you think he is. That's crazy.
- Is it?
- Yeah. It's right out of a B-movie.
Can you say with confidence
that Marcy is the same person
- that you originally met?
- Marcy's the best...
fucking thing that's
ever happened to me.
Kat, I'm so sorry.
- No. It's fine.
- It's not fine.
I don't... I don't talk
to people like that.
Maybe it's the concussion.
Please forgive me, that's not me.
David, it's fine. You know
what? Come sit down.
Come here. I'll make the tea.
What the hell happened here?
He's got a thing for tall guys, huh?
Do you think another
Traveler team beat us here?
It's possible, but we never
leave a scene like this.
It's also possible we're too late.
That's true. He jumped
bodies once before.
We did this to her. We
pulled her into this mess.
- Vincent did that.
- Yeah. And we used her to get to him.
Nothing we can do about that now.
Let's just hope if he jumped again,
the Director has some idea...
Boss, we've got company.
MacLaren!
We're coming in!
Jo, what brings you here?
I know you lied to me this afternoon,
I just haven't figured
out yet what about.
Did you do this?
This is how we found them, which
you know because you followed me.
This is the person you wanted
the Director to locate?
Little more complicated
than that, but yeah.
Her name is Dr. Katrina Perrow. She
was Vincent Ingram's therapist.
Vincent Ingram's in a
state mental hospital.
Yes, he is.
- Then who killed all these people?
- I have no idea.
But you're a real FBI agent, so
let me know what you find out.
- Hey. I was hoping we could talk.
- Not tonight.
Hey, I get that you had issues
- with my host...
- Like, what are you, deaf?
I said not tonight.
Okay.
Sorry.
Let me get you home.
Hey, you.
Hey.
I got your message.
Oh, that.
That was... classic. Hall of fame.
You know, there really should
be a humiliation button
- that allows you to erase messages...
- Mm-hm.
after you leave them.
I should invent that.
Honestly, I can't believe
you still wanna be with me
after leaving such an idiotic message.
That's one of the things
I love about you most.
Well, you're dumb, then.
So, how did you get conked?
Uh... ice skating.
- Ice skating?
- Ice skating.
- Huh.
- I'm stickin' to it.
Okay, let me check your
pupillary response.
I've been dying for you
to do that all day.
- Did I pass?
- Yes.
Does it hurt still?
A little bit. But you're
home now, so I don't care.
Does that help?
- It really, really does.
- Mm.
No more ice skating for you.
- If you insist.
- Mm-hm.
Kat?
Fantastic! I didn't think
you'd be here tonight.
Well, this is my house.
Yes, it is.
And you are my husband.
Yes, I am.
And my therapist said that we should
be spending more time together.
Oh, I like her better already.
Oh, feels like we haven't sat down
and had a glass of wine
together in a hundred years.
Mm.
I even have vegan pizza in the oven.
Now you're spoiling me.
I had a coupon that was expiring.
Come here.
It's just such a shame we have to
take that lovely body of yours.
Kat?
Philip.
I think we're gonna have
to go through with it.
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --