Previously on Travelers...
My team has been tasked
to prevent the military from building
the most powerful weapon
of mass destruction in history.
We just saved 11,000 people.
You know, a phone call to 911
could have saved his life.
That's cold, Philip.
With just four dead...
How could you have possibly
known that was going to happen
unless you had something
to do with it happening?
You've got a wife
you've got to go home to
and meet for the first time.
- Where are you going?
- Out.
With that guy?
You know, we could've taken the bus.
I need to improve my fitness.
Fitness. Good.
Been working out a little bit myself.
You know, "Last Week Marcy" was chatty.
Was she?
Okay, here's my theory.
Tell me if I'm close.
You've been undercover
with an FBI task force
on some kind of mission this whole time.
You needed a cover.
That's very close.
Really?
Hey, David, when we get to the hospital,
it's really important
that you help me convince the doctor
to give me an MRI.
You mean another MRI.
What?
Well, the other day,
when you had the seizure,
Dr. Lee ordered an MRI.
Why didn't you tell me?
Well, number one, you were unconscious.
Number two,
I'm pretty sure that Last Week Marcy
wouldn't know what an MRI was,
not to mention the fact
that you escaped the hospital
like you were Papillon.
You're certain that the MRI was done
at the hospital that I woke up in?
Yeah, I was in the waiting room.
Thank you.
Uh, that's all I need!
I'll see you back
at the apartment later.
Wait! Marce, no, we had a deal!
Ecclesiastes tells us
that "There is a season for everything,
"and a time for every event
under heaven...
a time to be born, and a time to die..."
For some of us,
death comes at the end of a long life,
but, for many of us,
as it did for Stephen,
death is an unexpected visitor.
Only God can cut the thread.
We must trust in God's plan
for each one of us.
How could you come here?
I thought it was important
to say how sorry I was.
How sorry I am.
You were his best friend!
Was I?
Are you high right now?
Did you come to my son's funeral high?
Marion, it's not worth what you're...
You were there!
The police told me!
You could've called 911!
You could've saved him!
Philip?
Philip! It's time to go!
Come on, man. Coordinates.
I need to know where we're going.
Did you just...?
Yeah. Just a little. I had to.
Are you gonna be able to work?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
This should help.
It's...
Don't you want to know what that is?
Whatever.
Hey, when you have time,
I need you to download
this file from the hospital.
Doctor's name's right there.
And what kind of file is this?
It's an MRI, actually.
Mine.
Yeah, sure. Done.
Okay. Everybody ready?
Just need the where-to.
33.2507 degrees by 74.1003 degrees.
All right.
The incoming traveler arrives at 21:33,
and it's at least an hour away.
Hey, are you...?
Traveler 3468.
Transition of
incoming Traveler canceled.
Resume protocols.
How did I get here?
I don't know,
but it's a little late
to be riding your bike.
I'm not supposed to talk to strangers.
Are you a policeman?
- No.
- Yes.
Yes. Yes. And you should be at home.
You know the way?
That was creepier than I imagined.
Only pre-pubescent brains
are malleable enough
to receive and deliver messages
without damage.
I know. Still creepy.
The new traveler was supposed
to give us our next mission.
Well, plans change.
You know, we could
still go to the T.E.L.L.
and save the guy
from getting hit by a bus.
That's what happens to the host...
actually, now he's some poor guy,
after 21:33.
Protocol 3, Philip. We can't interfere.
Two minutes ago,
we were interfering a lot.
A traveler was going to
take over a man's life...
Because the Director
had plans for the new traveler.
The host was going to die either way.
Not "was going to". "Is".
It hasn't happened yet.
All we have to do is drive by and say,
"Hey, man! Look out for the bus!"
And he gets home to his wife tonight.
All right, Philip, that's enough.
You know better.
Yeah...
I know better.
Mm-mm, no.
You are not leaving this house
wearing that tie again.
Why? Why?
What's the matter with it?
Nothing's wrong with it,
but you've been wearing it
for three days.
Even on the weekend,
which is kind of weird.
Please tell me you've been
changing your underwear.
Underwear... right.
Um, you know, I think...
I think I might go tie-less today.
You?
Well, if you do,
make sure someone takes a picture,
'cause that'll be a first.
I was thinking maybe we should
try something vegan for dinner tonight.
Vegan?
Yeah, you know,
food not sourced from
animals in any way.
Yeah, babe, I know what vegan is,
but you are my tie-wearing carnivore.
Doesn't hurt to try new things.
Ah, I kind of like the sound of that.
But wear the tie.
Have you tried this vegetable?
Corn?
Mm-hmm!
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Mm...
Wrong table, bro.
Hey, babe.
Oh, my God. You okay?
She broke my phone.
I'm so sorry. Here. Let me help you up.
It's okay. Come here.
I'll get your bag for you.
We're
getting a description now.
Now it looks like
we've arrived at the area
- Workin' hard?
- Every day.
We just got this security-camera footage
from outside the library
the other night.
Two assaults, same assailants.
There's an interesting twist
a few minutes in.
What?
You'll see.
At least two people are dead
after the Madison Bridge
suddenly collapsed early this morning.
...Emergency crews set up detours
as they continue to search
for survivors.
...Continue
to search for survivors.
And in other news,
Florida is on high alert with...
Tropical storms.
...storm. Winds are gusting...
You got some explaining to do.
What?
Look, if you weren't gonna show,
you could've at least let me know.
Squash, Saturday morning.
Squash...
You forgot, didn't you?
Uh, s-sorry. How was it? Squash?
You know,
it's king of a hard game to play alone,
but fortunately,
I found a playing partner
who is actually a challenge.
Um, hey, did you change
the password here?
How many times did you punch it in?
Twice.
Well, we better get it
right the third time,
or we're gonna be locked out.
What ever happened
with our cyber terrorist?
Oh, uh, dead-end.
Yeah, it was just a bunch of kids.
You probably got the caps-lock on again.
There!
All right. It's time. Let's go.
Where?
It's Monday. Gun range?
- Right!
- Right.
You okay?
Absolutely.
It's Monday. Let's shoot guns.
Hey.
I went shopping.
Did you sleep?
A little bit.
Yeah?
Sit down, sit down.
I'm fine.
You're taking too large a dose.
No more than eight units. A quarter up.
Okay?
Sterile water,
alcoholic wipes, syringes.
Used syringes in there.
Okay?
We're not gonna save the world.
Why do you say that?
'Cause it doesn't want to be saved.
So we'll save it anyway.
You know...
depression
is a side effect of heroin addiction.
I'm not depressed.
Mm-hmm. We're just sitting here...
waiting for orders from the future.
Protocol 5.
"Resume your host's life."
My host is a junkie.
What about yours?
We're talking about you right now.
We could be doing so much more, Marcy.
We're doing what we came here to do,
and we knew, going into this,
that we couldn't fix everything,
that we're not supposed to
fix everything,
and if we do,
we could make it
worse without even knowing.
I know.
I know you know.
No more than eight units.
Just enough to be functional.
Any more than that,
I know it's 'cause you want it.
I won't stand for that. Okay?
See ya.
People drop their phones all the time.
She said you pushed her.
I don't even know her.
Why would I push her?
That's my question, Rene.
You know, phones break, not a big deal.
What is a big deal is bullying.
You know, you make
your own choices, guys.
For example, you could choose to be a...
what's the word?
Douchebag?
That works. Or...
you could choose to be nicer
to those who aren't as blessed
with popularity as you.
- It's not hard.
- I'm totally nice!
I'm sorry. You're not.
What?
Okay, you can contemplate
your choices in detention.
Ms. Day...
I apologize for my involvement in this,
and I'd like to offer
to replace the girl's phone.
I think she'll appreciate that.
May I go?
Yes.
What is wrong with him?
I don't know.
Hey.
Calculated Chaos.
What's that?
A horse.
Put it all on "Calculated Chaos".
All of it?
Keep 30% of the winnings.
Distribute the rest, 50/50
to these addresses.
Look, Phil, if you owe
some money to a dealer, I...
It's not a dealer.
It's Stephen's mom.
And Gower's family.
The cop?
Why? What do you owe him?
Huh?
Hey, I'll give you
some advice as your lawyer.
You're not my lawyer.
Okay, free advice anyway.
Start throwing money at these people,
it's not the brightest of ideas.
Makes you look guilty.
Make it anonymous.
Put it in their mailbox.
I need you to do this for me.
So, uh...
I have a kid...
who hates me.
So you know what I do
for his 18th birthday?
I buy him a car. New freakin' car.
Well, newish. You know what he does?
Doesn't take it?
Oh, no, no, no, he took it,
'course he took it.
He's not stupid.
- But still hates me.
- Make the bet.
Drop off the money.
Keep the change.
So these anonymous tips started
coming in early this morning.
One of them led to this whacko
planning on shooting up
this bank in San Fran later.
Where are they coming from?
Well, they're searching
the I.P. address now.
Well, when it comes in,
we'll check it out.
Since when are you a perfect shot?
So how long have you been
her social worker?
Uh... over a year.
And when's the last time you saw Marcy?
A few days ago.
Hmm.
I went by her apartment.
The building manager said
he hadn't seen her around.
I went by the library,
same story.
You have any idea where
she could be hiding?
Hiding?
What for?
I don't know.
Well...
if she does show up,
let her know I'd like
to speak with her about
pressing charges.
She won't be pressing charges.
But we have...
...their faces.
Yeah, she wants to move past this.
Did she tell you that, David?
Yeah, she did.
Well, did she tell you
that she kicked the shit
out of those boys?
You knew she was capable of this?
Hmm?
Well, I-I think that, uh, when people
are in fight-or-flight mode,
that they're capable of...
"Fight-or-flight"?
Yeah, it's instinct. People
either fight, or they...
you know, fly.
Has Marcy
been acting differently lately?
Like a personality change?
No.
Well, all right.
Well, if you do notice anything,
I'll leave my card.
Hey, you hold on to those photos.
Marcy might want to have to take a look.
Thank you.
This is not good, Marcy.
He can't know you've been staying
here, not even for a few days.
It's completely inappropriate.
I'm your social worker, for God's sake.
So we don't tell anyone.
Here's another one, Mac.
An Islamic extremist in Chicago
is planning on bombing
the train to O'Hare.
They checked it out,
the guy's apartment was full of I.E.D.s.
Really?
And that, uh, I.P. address, that tip,
is 10 minutes from here.
Let's go check it out.
It's my wife.
Hey... Honey.
I got a messenger.
We have a mission.
"Sweetie."
Tell her I said "hi."
Forbes says hi.
Awkward.
She says hi back. What is... What is it?
We've got a mission. Now.
Okay, I'll meet you at... home?
Uh, Carly's.
It's closer to where we need to be.
I'll be right there.
She's not feeling great, wants
me to take her to a doctor.
Is it serious?
I doubt it, but, you know.
Yeah, of course, yeah, go.
Don't worry about it.
I'll check out the address myself.
I'll call you later.
Thanks.
Hey!
You don't think I'm nice?
Do you think you're nice?
Well, I'm nice to you.
Trevor.
Trevor?
Please stop.
What is wrong with you?
Are you even listening to me?
Who's texting you?
Trevor! Who's texting you?
I got to go.
What's the message?
Rescue an abducted boy
before he's murdered.
That's it?
I can't remember it verbatim.
You can't remember it verbatim?
Aleksander Andrieko.
10-year-old Romanian immigrant.
He went missing walking home
from school two months ago.
Why save him?
I assume he's important to the future.
I've never heard of him.
Well, he's 10, so.
The messenger didn't go into details.
You can't exactly chat with them.
This one burst into tears and ran away
the second he delivered his message.
Why did the messenger come to you?
Oh, not you, you mean?
I don't know, probably not a lot
of pre-pubescent children
walking around an FBI office.
Maybe it's time-sensitive.
Why are you taking it so personally?
I'm not taking it personally.
Okay, what do we know
about the abductors?
There are two of them. Man and a woman.
I know from historical records,
the victim's body
was found in the basement.
They're dangerous.
You keep a gun in your diaper bag?
Because I can't keep all of this...
You've been shopping.
A traveler team
dropped off our armament
package yesterday.
You guys pick out what you want.
I'm going to see
if my babysitter's home.
Hey. Hey, guys, w-we're saving a kid,
not invading Normandy.
You've reached
Special Agent MacLaren.
Please leave a message.
Hey, partner, it's me.
The first address was an empty building,
so our tipster's obviously
scrambling their I.P.
We got it narrowed down
to a handful of local servers.
I'm going to go over my half of the list
of possible addresses in the area
and I will text you the other half,
so we can cover more ground.
Call me when you're done
at the doctor's.
Com-check.
Yeah, we're up.
Everybody clear on the plan?
Trevor drops us off, we go in back.
Keep the engine running.
Will do.
Assume they're armed.
What do you think?
We've got
a vehicle approaching.
Yeah. We see 'em.
Allan and Cathy Whiteman?
Yeah, we are.
FBI. How's your day going so far?
We'd just like to ask
you a few questions.
FBI?
Yes, ma'am.
Do you mind if we come inside?
Well, that's where we're going.
Dammit, Cathy,
you'd better put that out.
You don't want to get a fine
for smokin'.
Aw, that's a whole other bureau.
"Tobacco, Alcohol, and..."
Never mind. Please.
Sorry about the mess.
We don't get a lot of company.
Come on.
What is that smell?
Chickens.
In the house?
No! 'Course not.
The basement.
We let 'em come and go.
You get used to it.
How can we help you?
We're investigating some suspicious
activity in the area...
Well, Glen and Shirley Duran,
just south of us...
and you didn't hear it from me...
they hire migrant workers.
Cath!
Let 'em ask a damn question
before you go hang the neighbors.
It's all right,
we're not here about them.
Well, it ain't right.
I mean, there's people
around here need jobs.
A boy who went missing two months ago
was reported seen in the area,
so we're checking with the locals.
Do you know
anything about this?
Haven't heard a thing.
'Course we only go to town
for groceries.
Not in the house.
Sorry.
I'm trying to quit,
I am, but I-it's so damn hard, you know?
I wonder if
your son has heard anything?
I noticed his sneakers
in the front hall.
Oh, uh...
I don't think he'd know anything.
Probably not.
I'd still like to ask him, though.
All right.
Patrick!
Philip,
slow down, we're making noise.
Patrick!
Oh, shit.
We found a body.
A child, maybe 10 years old.
I'll, uh, I'll just go and see...
Ah...
This man would like to ask you
some questions, Patrick.
Hi, Patrick.
I'm with the FBI.
Do you know what that means?
A policeman?
That's exactly right, yes.
What school do you go to?
I don't go to school.
We homeschool him.
Nothing wrong with that.
Gets a good Christian education.
I'll bet he does.
No.
What are you saying to him?
Allan!
Traveler 3468,
you are off-mission. Abort immediately.
What the hell's going on?
We're leaving.
We are not leaving him!
Stand down!
There's one child dead already!
He's next.
And another three children after that.
We are preventing this!
We're off-mission!
Stand down!
We're not leaving him.
He's our son!
Philip!
You're okay.
We need to clean up Philip's blood!
I'm on it, I'm on it.
Trevor, get everybody
out of here and back to Ops.
Okay. I got him. I got him, I got him.
Aleksander, are you hurt at all?
Are there any other kids here?
Just me.
Okay.
I'm going to get you home to your mom,
but I need you
to do something very important for me.
Okay?
Police officers will be here soon.
They're gonna ask you what happened.
It's really important you tell them
I was the only person here.
Okay?
You asked me for help.
They got afraid and started shooting.
You understand?
That's what happened.
Right?
Yes.
Good.
Forbes?
You should've called for backup.
It was supposed to be
a routine I.P. address check.
Got out of hand real fast.
So our vigilante's fake I.P. addresses
led us to these abductors?
That's a crazy coincidence.
Unless he wanted us here.
Another tip, if you think about it.
So how does one person have
all this information?
Explain that.
I can't.
At least the boy's okay.
Yeah.
You get my message?
Been a little busy.
Yeah.
I was just starting
on your half of the list
when you called.
Yeah? Where's that?
Old garage, downtown.
Fourth and Millwood.
I'll, uh, check that out
on my... on my way home.
You sure?
Yeah, yeah, you go. I got it covered.
All right.
Oh, um... how's Kathryn?
Hmm?
She went to the doctor's?
Oh. Yeah. She's... She's fine.
All right.
It's okay. Come here.
The Director doesn't know.
- What?
- What it's like.
Ah! Ah!
- It's okay.
- Okay.
Is he gonna be okay?
Hold him still.
I got him.
Trevor. Door.
Hold on!
You're going to be okay.
Hold him still!
Carly, lift his shirt up.
Okay. Apply pressure there.
Okay.
Whoa, Philip...
10-year-old
Aleksander Andrieko,
abducted two months ago,
was today found by the FBI
and reunited with his grateful mother.
Authorities say
his abductors were killed
in an exchange of gunfire
with FBI Special Agent...
Do you guys wanna head out?
We're not going anywhere.
There was no messenger.
No.
You've been sending tips to the FBI.
Yeah.
Jesus, I don't even know
if I can cover this up.
We have all of this knowledge
and we do nothing.
What is this?
Deaths.
I've memorized all of it.
Why can't we prevent some of it?
Because there are rules!
"Don't take a life"...
I get.
But what's wrong with saving one?
An innocent kid?
You can't tell me
we didn't just do a good thing!
It's not up to us!
A boy almost died.
Yeah! I know that!
And we saved him.
I'm not ashamed of that.
We don't get to decide.
Every change we make
has the potential to alter the future.
Isn't that what we're here to do?
The FBI found you in one day, Philip!
One day! Because you
think you know better
- than the Director.
- The Director.
Who the hell do you think you are?
Nobody.
I don't think I have any other choice.
He's addicted to heroin.
He's what?
He inherited it from his host.
Why would the Director put you
in the body of a heroin addict?
The historical record
said that he died after
the first time that he used.
His parents were probably in denial.
We were trying to manage it,
and I-I thought it was under control.
It's so hard.
Yeah. I'll bet.
Who else knew?
Just me.
You can manage this? Wean him off it?
In time, yes.
Well...
Time, I know something about.
Don't you have a test
in the morning, or something?
Yeah, but I don't got to
study for this one.
It's history.
Here.
I've developed a new appetite for life.
You just inhale the intoxicating aroma.
Meat?
Oh... it's ground meat.
You know they don't actually
grow that in the ground, right?
I'm not asking any questions.
I'm embracing the 21st century.
Save it for later.
This you want.
Mm!
So...
This is the list of
potential host candidates?
Yeah.
Not all of them, obviously.
Then all these people are gonna die?
Yeah.
Why? What's wrong?
I know this person.