Agent MacLaren never did
explain before they left how my...
teapot got smashed.
I don't suppose you...
Yeah. Doesn't matter.
I just dipped the bags in the cups.
Careful, that's hot.
What is this?
Really?
Wow. It's, uh... It's tea.
He said you wouldn't remember the events
of the last few months, but I...
didn't expect that.
It's good. I like it.
Yeah, I know you do.
Blow on it, though, so you don't...
burn your tongue.
So this experimental procedure
that they gave you...
uh, what was that all about?
- Did it hurt?
- I... I can't tell you that.
Because you don't remember.
I don't, actually,
but that's not why I can't tell you.
Because it's a secret.
That part you remember.
All right, you know, it doesn't matter.
It worked.
And to be honest, Marcy, I'm just...
I can't tell you how relieved I am.
Why can't you tell me?
Oh...
Well, I can.
What did MacLaren tell you about me?
Uh, everything.
That you knew me on a professional level
while I was undercover,
but that we were friends now.
I've been staying here temporarily.
And that's it?
There wasn't really that much time
to brief me before you came home.
Yeah. No. I just...
Yeah.
He said the most important thing
was that we were close.
And that I can trust you.
When I was in college,
I learned all about amnesia
in one of my courses.
I don't remember which course,
ironically...
but I do remember learning
that in a lot of cases,
memories come back.
That's what I'm hoping for.
Charlotte, what's wrong?
Did you have a bad dream?
It's all right. Your mom's here.
Charlotte?
Is everything all right in there?
No.
You should come in.
What are you doing here?
Hi. Thought we could, uh...
work out together, and then...
go somewhere for breakfast.
No, Grant. I mean,
what are you doing here?
What do you mean? I wanted to see you.
What's wrong with that?
I'm not doing this here.
Doing what?
Step off that thing for a second.
Come on, let's... let's talk.
Oh, now you want to talk?
What happened? Did she break it off?
- What? Who?
- Don't insult me.
What's her name?
You want to do this here? Fine.
What's her name, Grant?
You want to talk,
let's start the conversation with that.
How did you know?
I didn't, really, not for sure,
but I guess I do now.
Kat, I...
If you want to know when,
it was the last time we had sex,
after your surprise party.
At the time, all I could think of was,
"Wow, where the hell
did he learn how to do that?"
Then afterwards, I realized
there was obviously only one explanation.
It was like you were making love
to a different person.
You were a different person.
- How do you think that made me feel?
- In a way, I was.
All I can tell you is that I'm here now.
And I wanna stay.
I'm not sure I want you to.
David?
Yes?
- Oh... hey.
- What are these from?
Uh... what am I looking at?
These scars on my chest and my neck.
These wounds are fresh,
and it looks like
it was done by a scalpel.
Right. Yeah.
You, uh...
You performed minor surgery on yourself,
installed something called
a vagus nerve stimulator,
supposed to help
with the seizures you were having.
Uh, by myself?
Why would I do that?
Yeah. That's what I said.
VNS therapy would have never worked
in the case of pre-existing damage.
Yeah, that's what you said. Right after.
I was apoplectic.
There was blood everywhere.
Obviously, I took it out.
The only thing that seemed to help,
or at least bought you time,
was the, uh...
lumbar punctures.
You made some sort of serum
out of the fluid.
I couldn't have done that by myself.
You didn't.
I helped.
Do you mind if I have some coffee
before we continue this conversation?
Do you have any medical training?
Nope. You taught me.
Do you remember coffee? Do you...
Do you want some coffee?
If those treatments
really did buy me time, then...
I owe you my life.
No. You don't owe me anything.
You could do me a favor, though.
You could... You could...
You could do up one or...
two of those buttons
on that shirt that I laid out
for today, which, that...
I mean, that's fine.
Is it bothering you?
Bother's the wrong word.
Better?
I don't know.
David... were we intimate?
See, the thing about that is...
you'd only have my word to go by,
which forces my inner boy scout
to not take advantage.
If that was a test, that wasn't fair,
'cause I wasn't ready.
That was to thank you for helping me.
I thought maybe you remembered something.
Oh, there... there is one thing.
What? What is it?
That you're a reporter.
A social worker.
- But that's okay.
- We'll work on it.
I'm here.
Hey, it's me.
- I need your help.
- What is it?
It's Jeff. He's...
I've left you messages about this.
He's got me backed into a corner.
He wants custody of my son.
- Your son?
- Yes.
What do you want me to do about it?
Talk to him. With...
with your position at the FBI,
you can... You can help...
I spoke to Jeff, Carly.
Or rather, he spoke to me.
- At work.
- He did?
God, I want to bury that man.
You need to get this situation
under control.
That's why I need your help.
Does Trevor call me every time
he's got trouble with his parents?
No, but you don't sleep with Trevor,
do you?
Fight your own battles, Carly,
just like the rest of us.
And then Rene said that all my pictures
should have hashtag,
boob job won't fix this on them.
So... you didn't retaliate?
What?
This is your problem exactly.
You let people walk all over you.
You need to establish dominance.
Next time Rene says something to you,
disparage her home life.
Her mother's had a DUI.
Alternatively,
you can just accept the fact
that you're less attractive
and uninteresting.
That option may even be more realistic.
Uh... I'm gonna go...
Good talk.
Um, Ms. Day, can I talk to you
for a minute?
Let's not pretend I have a choice.
What is it?
Um, I have some forms for a field trip
I need your signature on.
Shouldn't your parents fill those out?
They're dead.
What?
Jesus.
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Hey!
Hey! What are you doing?
- She tried to kill me!
- I can tell!
Let me go! I'm on a mission!
- Go after her!
- And do what? She's a kid!
- A kid who tried to stab me to death!
- Why? What'd you do?
What did I do?
There's something more going on here.
- What?
- I can't stay here. She'll be back.
- I have to get to Ellis.
- No, no!
You're not going anywhere just yet.
Guys, it's Trevor.
We have to meet up at ops.
A traveler just tried to kill Grace.
Sorry.
I had a hard time finding the place.
I should have picked you up.
It's fine. I'm here now.
Not a single SOS that I can see.
Maybe she was just targeting you.
Of course she was targeting me.
Are you sure it wasn't just a student
with a bone to pick?
No, I was there.
You remember the family
who had their historian misfire?
I'm pretty sure it was the daughter.
The girl I took to her grandma's house?
Don't look at me.
Charlotte.
She said she was on a mission.
She was taken as a host anyway.
Why would the director want you dead?
The director didn't send her.
I've already told you,
there's a faction in the future...
No one but the director
has the capability to send travelers.
Tell them what you did.
Tell them! Or I will.
I reset the director.
What?
Rebooted its OS through a virus
in order to protect it
from corruption by the faction.
What would they say in the 21st? Uh...
"Control, alt, delete."
That's impossible.
Well, the director is a highly advanced
quantum AI program
and I'm the lead programmer,
so, no, not impossible.
You reset an AI that's been running
every facet of our lives
since long before I was born,
and not to mention every mission...
Before you were born, maybe.
But not me. I helped create it.
- No one else could've done it.
- How?
She uploaded a command
while pretending to save Marcy's life.
How?
When she saw my code,
it was sent back as visual information
through the quantum bridge created
during transfer of consciousness.
You mean you used me?
I saved you,
and I'm saving the director.
Where is the gratitude?
What is wrong with you people?
What's happening in the future
while it's offline?
Chaos, probably.
A temporary power struggle.
The faction doesn't believe
in the grand plan.
Even before Helios had basically
no effect on the future,
they had already started a mission
to abandon ship.
Your team knows firsthand
the brutality they're capable of.
You mean they're the ones
who put us in those cages?
Tortured us?
To test your loyalty... and to make sure
you couldn't complete a mission
they disagreed with.
That was the first real proof I had
that they'd managed to implement
some of their agenda.
So I came back here
into the 21st to stop them.
What do we do now?
The director will come back online
more secure than ever,
and soon,
everything will go back to normal.
"Thank you for saving us, Grace."
Please take me to Ellis...
before one of you gets overwritten
and tries to kill me.
What makes you think
you'll be safe there?
He's taken precautions.
Boss?
Yeah, get her outta here.
But don't let her out of your sight.
"Thank you for saving us, Grace!"
Is this yours?
Uh...
Yeah.
I inherited it from my host.
Historical record was wrong.
You know, we should spend
some more time debriefing you.
- There are a lot of...
- What?
You just kept taking it?
You were helping me wean off it,
but I had a little bit of a setback.
Well, we're starting again.
No more than eight units.
If you take more than that,
it's because you want it.
And I won't stand for that.
And from now on...
I'm keeping track of how much you dose.
You're the doctor.
And you're the historian.
We need your mind clear.
Ellis!
- Where is he?
- Not here.
So you are gonna be hanging
with the babysitter today.
Huh?
Just gonna hang tight, little man,
and I'll come back and get you
after work, okay?
Hmm?
You wanna fly? You wanna fly?
Hey, it's okay.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Hey, guys.
You okay?
Are you...
- okay?
- I'm fine.
I had no choice.
She was gonna shoot you.
- Yeah, she was.
- You saw that, right?
Carly, what the fuck are you doin'?
Carly! You need to stay put!
Carly!
Where the hell were you?
It's dangerous out there!
I had to run out for a few supplies.
What do you want now?
The faction sent an assassin after me.
Not a very good one, apparently.
Oh, fortunately,
I was there to stop her.
- Where?
- At the school.
Any of 'em follow you?
We're alone.
You can stop worrying about yourself.
Were you a part of the reset, too?
- Reset?
- Of the director?
- That is too far.
- It was the only way.
Not by a long shot!
My God, the ego of this woman.
When?
When I sat Marcy down at your computer.
Right in front of me.
- Give me a hand with this.
- What is all this?
Are these SQUID transistors?
You think you're the only one who
figured out what the faction is up to?
Look, have a little faith.
The director had its own contingency,
although you've probably screwed
that all up.
Wait, what contingency?
Me... and this.
I was sent back to assemble this.
The director's had teams working
on core elements for months.
First components arrived
the day I came back to the 21st.
- This is a quantum frame.
- Yes, it is.
If things get bad enough
that the director has no choice
but to escape the faction,
it can send itself here to the 21st.
Agent MacLaren.
Officer Boyd. How can I help...
Jesus, what are you doing?
- What'd you do?
- What?
What did you do that would make
the director give an order to kill you?
How did you receive the order?
By messenger. Don't change the subject.
What did you do?
I think you already know
I didn't do anything wrong,
or we wouldn't be having
this conversation.
Your orders didn't come
from the director.
- What does that mean?
- What was the message exactly?
"Kill 3468," so not a lot of room
for interpretation.
Another traveler I know had an attempt
made on her life earlier today.
By who, if not the director?
According to her,
another faction from the future.
I don't know about any faction.
Well, neither do I...
but apparently,
things have changed since we left,
and not for the better.
That's not good enough.
It's all I got.
I only know what she told me.
That's a problem.
It doesn't have to be.
- Does it?
- Yeah.
It does.
Take a step back.
Take a step back, MacLaren!
- Hello?
- Hey, Marce.
David?
I'm glad you recognize my voice.
So here's something awkward...
There's a man in my apartment
who's looking for you,
and he has a gun.
Has he hurt you?
Uh... little bit.
A little bit,
but he said he'd do a lot more
if I didn't phone you right away.
He did point the gun nozzle...
You know, I know it's not "nozzle,"
but I can't think of the word right now.
I wanna say barrel?
You know, it's not coming to me,
but he's got it pointed
at the back of my head
right now, so if you can imagine that...
that's what's happening,
and that's why I'm calling you.
Against my will.
Kat.
Grant? What are you doing here?
Sorry to just show up like this,
but it's important.
- How did you find me?
- I'm FBI.
And I need you to go home right now,
pack a bag,
go to your mother's for a few days,
maybe a week.
What? What's going on?
- I'm dealing with a situation at work.
- Work?
- It's not safe.
- Tell me what's happening.
- I can't.
- Are you safe?
Look, I know it's not
the ideal time for me
to make demands of you,
but I need you to do as I ask.
If something happened to you
because of me...
I don't know what I'd do.
- You're serious.
- Yes.
All right, don't worry about me.
I'll go right now.
Just tell me that
you're gonna be all right.
I'll walk you to your car.
Come on.
Carly, where the hell are you?
I am in some serious shit.
I need you to meet me down at the station
and help me.
You were the only witness
that saw that I killed that girl
to save you!
You just can't run off
to leave me to deal with this!
Call me back.
- Yes?
- Excuse me.
- I'm here about your east wall.
- What?
The building manager notified you, yes?
I just need your cooperation
for a couple minutes, okay?
- Building manager?
- Yeah. He should have contacted you.
I just need you to step aside
for a moment,
and I will be
out of your way soon, okay?
Hello?
Answer it.
- Hey, Marce?
- Duck.
- What?
- Duck down now.
Oh, God.
Marce?
Marcy? You shot him.
What did you expect me to do?
He was gonna kill you right after me.
I need you to go somewhere else
for a couple nights, until it's safe.
Okay?
Go somewhere?
Marcy, there's a dead guy
on my living room floor!
I gotta call the police.
If you insist on bringing them
into this...
I need you to tell them that
you don't know where the shot came from.
- You want me to lie?
- No, David.
I want you to go somewhere safe,
but if you're gonna bring the police
into this then, yes, lie.
We'll have to cover this up later.
I need to go.
Marcy?
Hello. You've reached
the confidential voicemail
of Special Agent Forbes.
Please leave a detailed message,
and I'll get back to you.
Hey, Walt, it's Kat again.
I'm sorry to keep calling,
but I really need to talk to you.
What's going on? I'm worried.
Please call me back.
It'll be a tight fit, all right.
Do you even have a plan
for when this is all ready?
I figured I'd flip the switch
and see what happens.
- You would.
- No, this one here.
Plan for what?
For when the director is ready
to send itself here.
As of right now,
this entire farm is protected by
a space-time attenuator field.
Covers the whole farm
in a 100-yard radius.
Nothing will penetrate it.
No electronics, no GPS,
no telemetry of any kind
in the 21st or the future.
So we're invisible
to the faction right now.
And to the director.
It won't be able to send a messenger
or consciousness here,
let alone itself.
As soon as we know the director's
back online, we'll be safe
and we can turn off the defenses.
Then it can either come back to the 21st
or stay where it is.
Either way...
I'll have to feed the pigs
and milk the cow in the morning.
It doesn't make any sense.
Why would the director want
other teams to take each other out?
Maybe Grace was right.
Maybe it's the faction.
Or maybe we're being punished
for helping her.
Sorry, boss, nothing.
No other teams reporting
that they've encountered this.
Everything looks normal on the deep web.
Well, there's nothing to report
if you don't survive.
Trevor, come in.
Trevor?
He could be in danger.
We have to warn him.
Get down!
Go, go, go!
Why are you looking at me like that?
Nothing. No, I'm not.
Don't tell me you had a thing for her.
- Who?
- Who do you think?
Ew, don't tell me that's why
you took her out into the woods.
Grace Day was a lovely human being.
She didn't deserve to die,
that's all it was.
I'd prefer if you'd refer to me
in the present tense.
You know, if you're gonna
go on pretending to be her,
you've got a lot of work to do.
Look who's talking.
What's that supposed to mean?
Your school record says
your previous self
was a recalcitrant bully
whose only redeeming quality
was a gift
for something called... football.
Trevor Holden wouldn't have
given Grace the time of day...
She didn't deserve to die.
Oh, but Trevor Holden did?
Is that what you're saying?
Existence should be based on merit?
You're a hypocrite.
How's our progress?
I need to check in with my team.
Just get to the farm.
We'll be right behind you.
- Oh, no.
- What is it?
I left Poppy behind.
- Who's Poppy?
- My turtle.
You mean it belonged to your host?
No, I just bought it as a pet.
You know, for company.
A turtle.
Yeah. That was a lot of gunfire.
What if she got shot?
You think she's gonna be okay?
I do.
You're a little different.
It's weird.
Than what?
The Marcy I know.
Knew.
I don't even know if that's possible.
I'm not saying that you're not you.
Obviously, you're you.
How... how am I different?
If I had to sum it up into one word,
I would say that Marcy 1.0...
was more fragile.
Maybe because you knew
you were gonna die.
You don't have the same burden.
You don't think it's a burden
coming into a team who already knows you,
but you don't know them?
I mean, other than the time
that you trained together.
- I'm sure it is.
- It's me, Philip.
Just give me some time to catch up.
Mr. Mailer,
I've got someone coming
to escort you to the station
so we can talk further
while the investigation...
I told you, the shot came outta nowhere.
Well, not nowhere.
It came from your neighbor's apartment.
We're gonna take a statement
from your neighbor.
Maybe she saw someone.
I don't have anything
more to add that...
You've been under duress.
We're gonna give you some time to think.
Seriously, I'm fine.
Sir, a man was shot in the head
in your apartment,
and you're obviously
holding back information,
including the nature
of your two cell phone calls
prior to your calling 911.
Head on downstairs, please.
Something wrong?
Stop the car. I need to do something.
What?
We gotta stop doing this.
- Doing what?
- All of it. Any of it. I can't...
We're fooling ourselves thinking
that we could bring to the 21st
what should have been left behind.
I mean, Protocol 2...
"Leave the future in the past."
But we both decided...
We can't make exceptions
because it's convenient, or personal.
I mean, this relationship...
we've been holding on to all this time,
it's jeopardizing our team,
our covers, our mission.
And the mission comes first, right?
You know it does.
Look, I just... I think
we're better off...
I get it.
You've got your life
you gotta make work.
I said I get it.
You don't have to say any more.
Drive.
Stop! Stop what you're doing!
- Stop what?
- Look at this.
Look at this.
Mission abort?
The director must be back online.
That message could've come
from your girlfriend for all we know.
She doesn't call me 0115.
Well, then it must be the faction.
They're on to what we're doing.
Or the director knows what you did
and communicated to me
the only way it could.
You jumped into the 21st illegally.
You took a host that wasn't meant
for you. You uploaded a virus...
- All for the greater good.
- According to who? You?
Listen, I told you that I had evidence
that an attack on the director
was imminent.
I had no choice but to act.
Well, all I can tell you is...
my mission didn't come to me as a text.
It came from the director, personally.
- Before the reset.
- What?
You received that mission
from the director
before I was able to send the reset.
Obviously.
I got here before you did.
What difference does it make?
It was still vulnerable to corruption
by the faction at that time.
You two can argue all you want.
I got my mission,
and I'm seeing it through.
Then I'm just gonna have to stop you.
Trevor...
Trevor, just...
- Hey!
- Whoa, guys!
Good luck with that.
They're not in the house.
Okay. Well, let's have a look around.
Trevor!
In the barn, guys!
What's going on, Trev?
Oh, we were just having a conversation.
At gunpoint?
You're not going to shoot anyone, Ellis.
Put the gun down.
I've got a mission to get done,
and this young man objects.
Were you given a mission
to assassinate Trevor?
What? Where the hell did that come from?
His mission was to build this.
What is this?
Has to be a quantum frame.
The director wanted a fail-safe
in the event it had to come back
to the 21st.
And I just received a mission
from the director to destroy it.
- By messenger?
- Text.
I went out of the range
of the attenuation field
to report in,
and this message showed up.
Bah! That could be sent by anybody.
It is pretty unorthodox.
Or it was the only way
the director could communicate.
There's no kids within miles.
That message could have just as easily
come from the faction.
Or the faction gave you
the order to build the quantum frame
for their own purposes.
Well, both can't be true.
Let's figure it out, 'cause so far today,
every member of my team
has been targeted by assassins.
More proof that the faction
is behind this.
That's not how the director does things.
Unless the director sent the assassins
because we helped you.
How can the faction possibly
send messages to the 21st
without the director knowing about it?
The director was offline for a short time
after I sent the reset command.
Or the faction
has its own transfer system.
There were rumors they were trying
to build one of their own in Shelter 41.
Shelter 41 collapsed when I was a kid.
This is something you remember?
We all remember.
It was a structural flaw.
The weight of the ice was too much.
So we're setting aside Protocol 2 now?
It collapsed at exactly 0600
as the reveille bell rang.
Thousands of people died.
It was horrible.
Well, now, the people
of Shelter 41 are very much alive
and the founders of an underground
movement against the director,
which eventually became known
as the faction.
- This is news to you?
- To all of us.
Well, apparently your work in the 21st
has been a greater agent of change
in the future than we thought.
I'm just tryin' to get my head
around this.
Yeah, you too?
So you're telling me the future you left
wasn't divided into two camps?
One loyal to the director
and the other believing
that decisions should be made by people,
not a machine?
No, and that kind of division is what
got us into trouble in the first place.
The world we left was loyal
to the director and the grand plan.
Looks like all the grand plan
has done so far
is screw things up worse than before.
How do we know they're not right?
What?
Don't be ridiculous.
Humans make decisions based
on greed and desire... hate.
- It's been proven.
- She's right.
The director saved us
from the brink of extinction
and created the grand plan,
we have to trust that.
- Is that what you believe?
- Of course.
All of you?
I wish I could. But then again,
the director didn't send any of you
back into the body
of a young man addicted to heroin.
Listen, we cannot second-guess
what we came here to do.
There is too much at stake.
We have to have faith that the director
is working toward the greater good.
So we should follow the director,
no matter what mission we're given.
- Is that right?
- What are you doing?
Carly?
Even if it's the hardest thing
you've ever had to do?
"Kill 3468."
That's what it says.
That is the mission
I was given by the director.
What do you think I should do?
Well, if you're asking...
I prefer that you didn't.
But it's not up to me.
What the hell is that?
Someone's on the property.
Perimeter breach.
- Assassins?
- The faction probably followed you here.
Marcy, Philip, since you're not occupied
with gun pointing at the moment,
would you go have a look outside, please?
Go over there.
I don't see anyone.
I saw movement over by the house.
We have to destroy the quantum frame
before they get here.
- Don't do it, son.
- Boss?
You know what you have to do.
We don't have a choice!
They're gonna be here soon!
- Don't.
- There's another way.
It went right through her.
- Marcy! Help Trevor!
- Put the fucking gun down and help me!
Philip, what's going on out there?
- Philip!
- You'll be okay.
Keep applying pressure.
She's a doctor. You'll be okay.
Turn off the defenses...
Drop the attenuation field.
The director could still help us.
Okay.
They're getting closer.
The director's coming!
Traveler 3468.
Mission abort.
Destroy quantum frame immediately!
They're surrounding the building.
We need to get them out of here!
They're coming in!
Freeze! FBI! Drop your weapons!